It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
Please! I just need 10,000 yen!
I don't got any money to lend you.
Both our home and our household
belongings were seized.
I promise I'll pay you back!
I'm begging you, Yuji!
You've got no right to call me "Yuji,"
like you know me.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Wait!
I treated you guys all those times!
You better not say you've forgotten!
So what about it?
I've got no use for you
if you don't got the money.
We hung out with you
because you were a rich kid!
Figure it out for yourself, moron!
Moron.
"The site you are looking for was not found.
Keyword: Hell Link Search"
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
There it is.
"Takashi Inagaki"
Just you watch, Inagaki!
"Send"
"Your message was received.
Hell Girl"
All that remains is for you to decide.
"Broken Threads"
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie this red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and you will wander for eternity
in pain and agony.
I'll go to Hell, too...
It's been 3 days since then.
What do you think?
I don't know...
Which do you bet?
I've got this much that says
he won't untie the thread.
You idiot! This isn't a game.
Oh, hey, wait.
Sheesh, the woman can't take a joke.
You heard that?
"Shibata Family's Grave"
Huh?
Must be Tsugumi.
"Shibata"
Ayumi...
Oh, darn it!
Shut up, you little bastard!
"First Citizen Corporation"
"Conference Room 1
In Use"
Sorry for calling you up when you're busy.
Damn straight.
How does it feel to be back
in your old workplace?
The atmosphere's as oppressive
and unpleasant as ever,
Mr. Chief Editor Inagaki.
If you'd stuck around,
you would've become an
assistant editor or thereabouts, too.
So I wouldn't have gotten
past assistant editor, huh?
I hear your sales have been up lately.
"The Other Face of the
International Philanthropist"
I hear your sales have been up lately.
"The Other Face of the
International Philanthropist"
Well, we've got a lot to be thankful for.
"The Money-Driven Life of
the Heiwa Party's Yozo Kataoka"
Well, we've got a lot to be thankful for.
When did the sober politics
and economy magazine
stop to becoming a scandal rag?
Ever the wise ass.
"The Other Face of the
International Philanthropist."
"The Money-Driven Life of
the Heiwa Party's Yozo Kataoka."
We merely exposed the truth.
I heard Kataoka got arrested
based on this article.
Worthy of a
Superintendent-General's Award.
Would you have been able
to write a better article?
I'm not coming back.
That's not why I called you.
Then shall we have a blast
reminiscing about the past?
I want you to do a job for me.
"First Citizen Corporation"
I want you to keep an eye on
Kawarazaki of the Nationalist Party.
"First Citizen Corporation"
What for?
He's involved with a woman
with dangerous connections.
Huh.
I'll pay you a suitable fee.
"Conference Room 1
In Use"
Some dirt to threaten him with, huh?
Watch what you say.
It's just a trump card.
We've got info on him taking bribes,
but Kawarazaki's an SOB.
Attacking him fair and square
will only get us so far.
You'll do it, won't you?
I don't feel too hot about it, though.
Thanks.
Get me whatever material you've got.
What's the limit?
-Within a week.
-Got it.
Oh, if it doesn't look like you'll
be able to catch him in the act,
just fudge it.
You telling me to fabricate it?
That'll be plenty effective, too.
Hey, where're you going?
I might be down on my luck,
but I'm still a journalist.
Don't misjudge me.
Shibata.
If you want to fake it, do it yourself.
Don't act so righteous. I checked into you.
I hear you're selling the
pictures you secretly snapped
back to the people you photographed.
Sit back down.
I'm asking you to help me out
for old time's sake.
You gonna threaten me now, too?
This isn't a threat.
You've fallen, Inagaki.
Shibata.
So you're even just as gutless
as you used to be?
And here I thought you
might've grown up a little,
since you've had a
taste of the lower class life.
You can have this back.
Guys like him never
move up in the world.
We don't care about him.
What's more important is...
I know, Mr. Target, right?
Give me a break!
There's no way a shallow article
like this is going to grab the readers!
-Isn't it good that he's
so easy to understand?
-Copy that doesn't sell
-Isn't it good that he's
so easy to understand?
-Is the same as trash!
"First Citizen Corporation"
Man, what a day.
You come in here without permission again
and we'll turn you in
to the police! Got that?!
Let me see Inagaki!
If you want to see him,
get an appointment!
If I could, I would've!
Then get lost, you piece of trash!
"First Citizen Corporation"
Wh-What're you doing?!
You bastard!
What were you trying to accomplish?
You had some business
with Inagaki, right?
I used to work there, too. With Inagaki.
Not interested in talking?
What kind of guy is Inagaki?
He's a nasty bastard.
What's your name?
Kataoka.
Kataoka?
What?
So that's it. I knew you looked familiar.
So you're Yozo Kataoka's son.
That Heiwa Party man, who was
caught for accepting bribes.
Huh. You're the son that
led to Kataoka's fall, eh?
The one that was into drugs...
That was made up!
I've never done drugs.
I was framed by Inagaki!
True, I hear the drug test the police
administered came back negative.
But the media reported that
some evidence had been seized...
No such things exist!
That bastard... Inagaki just
wrote that article on his own!
They printed a correction right away,
but by then, the news of my old man
accepting bribes had gone public
and it had become this huge deal...
So it got lost in the
shadow of the bigger story...
I see. I didn't notice
the correction, either.
That Inagaki must've
had it all planned out.
All our assets have been seized
and my family has been torn apart!
It's all his fault!
Just to corner my old man,
Inagaki went so far as to
use the rest of the family!
It's unforgivable that
he's living a comfortable life!
After he took everything from us!
So...
So?
You tried to kill him?
Even if you managed that,
you'd just end up paying for it.
I know that.
That's why I put out a request.
But...
Request?
Revenge doesn't give rise to anything.
I understand how you feel,
but use that energy to fuel yourself.
Anger can be pretty useful
in making your way through life.
Think it over. It's too early
for you to abandon your life!
What the hell do you know?!
Hey! Wait!
I treat him and he gets pissed at me.
Talk about a bad return
on my investment.
Murder for hire, huh?
But there's no way he has
that kind of money right now...
Can't be...
It's excellent.
Really?
I'm impressed, Tsugumi.
With a taste like this,
I could even serve it at my place.
I only made it exactly
the way you told me to.
I bet your father will love it.
I hope so.
Wha...
Tsugumi!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just getting started here.
Okay, I'm gonna take
Yoko and Azusa with me.
Come on, let's go to one more place.
Okay!
Then we'll be going, Ma'am.
Hey, get a hold of yourself.
What? I've got a hold
of myself, you dummy!
-If he really made the request...
-Come on, let's go.
Who's calling me at a time like this?!
"Tsugumi"
Tsugumi?
What is it?
Hajime, I saw it again.
What? Really?
Where was it this time?
I couldn't tell.
It's somewhere that's bustling.
Bustling?
Any kind of landmark type of thing?
"Snack Bar
Blue Sapphire"
Any kind of landmark type of thing?
"Snack Bar
Blue Sapphire"
Snack bar? Blue Sapphire?
Which means, it's really...
Oh, crap!
Over here, over here.
Inagaki!
Huh? Who the hell're you?
Y-You're Yozo Kataoka's...
Because of you, my family is in ruins!
In ruins? You moron, of course it is.
It's what you get for all the
bad things your old man did.
If you're gonna get mad,
get mad at your old man.
You used me to expose
what my old man was hiding!
Used you? I don't know
what you're talking about.
You bastard!
You brat!
Come on, let's go.
What was with that guy?
Hey, you okay?
You picked a bad opponent.
Inagaki's got a black belt in karate.
Is the one you made
the request to Hell Girl?
That bastard.
He's a nuisance.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
You go back to your bar.
You still have to clean up, don't you?
I'll be fine. Let me get you some water.
Thank you.
Who are you?
I wasn't sure I believed it at first.
I thought there was
no way she could exist.
But she does!
Hell Girl really exists.
What kind of girl is she?
I don't know.
Where did you meet her?
You asked her to kill Inagaki?
But you're still taking action yourself.
After you've already asked
Hell Girl to get your revenge. Why?
What's that?
It symbolizes the covenant.
If I untie this thread,
the covenant will be established.
Thread...
But...
I see, so it's still not too late, right?
What?
All right.
Don't untie the thread.
I'll make Inagaki apologize.
Inagaki's death won't resolve anything.
We'll publicize everything that he's done.
I'll write the article,
so don't untie the thread.
Got it?
Hell Girl...
I don't know who you are
or why you're doing this.
But I can say one thing for sure.
You are...
...wrong.
He left? Alone?
With someone.
Yup. With a really gaudy woman.
Yup, yup. "Come on,
let's go to my establishment."
"Oh, okay, let's go," is how it went.
"Let's go," my ass!
-Just who does he think we are?!
-A woman?
What's this? It's in an
awfully run-down area.
Isn't it great? It's so shady!
I guess.
Here we are! There, please open the door.
Yes, Ma'am.
Wh-What the?!
Man, he reeked of alcohol.
"Depraved Journalism
Behind the Truth!!"
Let me out!
Hurry up and let me out!
"Depraved Journalism
Behind the Truth!!"
Hurry up and let me out!
I said, let me out! Hey!
Feel like repenting
for your crimes now?
Crimes?! What crimes?!
All I did was expose the truth
that was hidden away!
I was even commended for it!
I've given no cause for
anyone to call me a criminal!
I see, so if it's for the
sake of this so-called "truth,"
are you saying it doesn't
matter what you do?
The truth that gets exposed is justice!
And as you see it,
that's what journalism is?
That's right!
What the masses want are
sensational stories called the truth!
I'm satisfying that desire!
I've done nothing wrong!
So he says, Miss.
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Where am I?
Where do you think you're going?!
Turn back the boat!
I consign this grievance to Hell...
You untied the thread?
Why?!
Even if everything is made public,
what good will that do now?!
What's been destroyed
can't be restored anymore!
You've got family, too, don't you?
You should understand.
Kataoka...
"Masaya Kataoka"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Akane Sawai.
You believe that man's actions
are not sincere?
He's not thinking about me at all!
He's doing it all for himself!
In truth, he wishes a failure
like me would just disappear!
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Spilled Bits"
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Spilled Bits"
Next time, "Spilled Bits".
"Hell Girl
Spilled Bits"