It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
Sentaro...
Tsugumi, what's wrong?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
I'd like these.
"Rain of Remorse"
Man, sorry about last night.
I didn't have time to call...
...and I ended up drinking
until morning.
There's...no breakfast, right?
Then, we can go downstairs...
Thanks for the food.
Go like you're supposed
to this year, okay?
What're you talking about?
Never mind!
I'll go by myself!
"Ogawa"
Coming!
Welcome, Tsugumi!
We've been waiting for you.
Is Hajime...
Tsugumi bought this?
A photographic collection?
Something this expensive...
"Japan's Cherry Blossoms"
"Photographed at Mutsumi Village"
A-Ai, you have another message.
Moody, isn't she?
Doesn't it sort of make
you feel uneasy?
It makes me realize...
I guess it's already been
that long since Ayumi died.
Yes, it has.
After all, Tsugumi was so
little back then, but now...
Look. She made this beautiful
dish of rice with chestnuts.
Isn't today the anniversary
of your wife's death?
The wife I split up with.
But why are you asking that?
Tsugumi came by yesterday,
asking about how to make
rice with chestnuts.
Because it was her
mother's favorite dish.
I didn't know...
You guys knew each other since
you were students, right?
And you even had a kid...
It was one of those so-called
youthful indiscretions.
The report on the faculty meeting
is the next issue's special feature!
Who the hell backs down without a fight
just because you got turned away?!
I heard Shibata got shot down.
-Hey, you sure you guys
aren't getting soft?!
-So that's why he's so pissy.
-Hey, you sure you guys
aren't getting soft?!
So who shot him down?
What's she like?
-Miss Ogawa,
-A journalist takes a stand for
the reader's right to know!
-A quiet girl who used to be the same...
-A journalist takes a stand for
the reader's right to know!
...language class until last year.
-A journalist takes a stand for
the reader's right to know!
Do you get that?!
M-Miss Ayumi Ogawa,
please go out with me!
Her personality is the total
opposite of Shibata,
but it was love at first
sight for Shibata...
...and he expressed the feelings he's
had these past two years today, but...
If you've got time for idle
chitchat, go check the copy!
You better keep me company
until morning tonight.
We know.
Shibata...
Yes!
About what happened earlier...
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
I mean, being confronted like that
so suddenly in front of everyone...
I'm sorry!
I hadn't thought about that.
I'll never show my face
around you again. I promise.
Oh, um, that's not it.
What?
That is...if you would have me...
Of course! It's totally okay!
I never expected Shibata would be
the first of us to get married.
Surprising...but I guess, not really.
He fell head over heels for Ayumi,
after all.
Hello?
What? Really?
Has something happened?
The Tokyo Public Prosecutors
went in...
...to former Prime Minister
Takenoshita's private residence.
It looks like this
is going to be big.
I'll go, too.
Sorry!
Maybe that was the first
stroke of bad luck for us...
Noriko Hayashi.
"Central Hotel 7"
Central Hotel 7...
Tsugumi? Tsugumi?
Are you okay, Tsugumi?
Oh, yeah, I'm okay.
But you look pale.
Maybe we should go take
a little break.
Hell Girl's notified me again.
This time, I know both
the place and the name.
"Cafe New Deen"
If I tell Hajime, he's sure
to get in Hell Girl's way.
"Address List / Hajime /
Grandpa / Grandma / Yuko"
If I tell Hajime, he's sure
to get in Hell Girl's way.
"Address List / Hajime /
Grandpa / Grandma / Yuko"
But...
"Address List / Hajime /
Grandpa / Grandma / Yuko"
Maybe he'll understand that
Hell Girl is doing the right thing.
Are you not feeling well, after all?
What?
You don't seem to have much
of an appetite, either.
Oh, th-that's not true.
Tsugumi?
I'm going to go make a call.
"Answer
...Tsugumi"
It's Tsugumi.
You'd better apologize properly.
It's never quite
as easy as that...
Hello?
Noriko Hayashi.
Central Hotel 7.
What?
Was it Hell Girl, Tsugumi?
H-Hey!
Put it on my tab!
So anyway, Noriko's bored
of the current condo.
And it doesn't have a good view, either.
All right, all right. I'll buy you one.
Honestly, you sure are spoiled, woman.
But that's because I can
always depend on you, Keiichi.
Central Hotel 7?
Please hurry!
It's an emergency!
Sure, sure.
But you know,
my motto is safe driving.
The fastest you can manage is fine.
Sure, sure.
"Central Hotel 7"
Oh, dear, we're stuck
in a traffic jam. See?
Are you with the media?
Something like that.
I knew it.
I've only been driving
a taxi for half a year,
but I can always spot
the media people.
Is that right?
Charging around late at night
and early in the morning.
No time to pay
attention to family.
That's the kind of vibe
they give off.
I bet you've got some
troubles at home, too, right?
Hello?
I understand. I'll be right there.
You're going out?
There's apparently been an
accident at some power plant.
I'll call you when
I know what's going on.
Oh, you can stay in bed.
Look after the house
while I'm gone.
"I'll be back by 7.
I'll call."
When she's born...
Maybe things will change a little...
Even after Tsugumi was born,
Hajime didn't change, did he?
Not only that,
but now that he had a child,
he threw himself into his
work even more than before.
I wonder how Ayumi must have felt...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Then, shall we go?
Central Hotel 7.
Oh, that's it there.
Are you going to stake it out?
I don't know.
That day...
As usual, I hadn't returned
home in days,
continuing a stakeout...
It was because it was rumored that a
politician popular for his integrity...
...was having a torrid affair.
But...
H-Hold on, Shibata!
What's wrong?!
Please let me go, Mr. Murai!
Hey, wait, Shibata!
Who're you?
You bastard!
You bastard! You bastard!
Stop this, Shibata! Hey, quit it!
The wife of the man pursuing a story
about an extramarital affair...
...turned out to be having
an affair herself.
It wasn't even funny.
Oh, Sir, your receipt!
"Central Hotel 7"
Noriko!
Don't do it!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Central Hotel 7"
Ai, I'll leave your
under-kimono here.
Do you know what
it is that you've done?!
You've sent a person to Hell!
I loved her...
But to her, I was nothing but...
No, all men were nothing
but deep pockets to her.
How could I forgive
a woman like that?!
How could I forgive her?!
While I was working,
she was fooling around
with other men!
You saw her, too, Mr. Murai!
Not to mention leaving Tsugumi
alone while she was out!
But think about Tsugumi.
She still needs a mother.
She does not need a mother
who is unfaithful!
Shibata...
I'm the one suffering
the most here!
She's been the only one
for me since college!
If this was what she was
going to put me through...
I wish I'd never met her.
So I wanted her
to be gone for good...
That it served her right
to go to Hell...
What is this? What's going on?!
H-Hey, you there!
You called?
My friend just suddenly...
...turn into money or something?
What?
How splendid for you.
To you, men are...
...money, right?
Nooo!
You there! Please help me!
Money, is it?
If 5 yen will do...
What is this?!
What's going on?!
What a stupid thing to do...
What do you know?
Hajime...
What're you doing here?
I want to start over.
How can I trust someone who's
already betrayed me once?!
Is there no way?
No.
And I have no intention of
letting you see Tsugumi, either.
Go on.
Don't show up around here again.
It can't be...
Nooo!
This way. Over here.
This is...
A place that has your beloved money.
However, you'll never
be getting out of here.
Beware of fires...
Nooo!
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Nooo!
Men are just...
They're the ones that
flock to me.
So why does this have
to happen to me?
No one will flock to you now.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Nooo!
Hatred will only make
you feel empty...
That's why revenge...
...is something you
must never take!
To say nothing of exacting
revenge at someone's request,
which is something that
should never be condoned.
"Shibata Family Grave"
Who in the world would have...
Hajime...
"Goro Suetsugu"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Tsugumi, is it really her?
That girl, who's loved
and adored by everybody,
is going to be banished to Hell?
That girl, who's living so
earnestly for the sake of others...
Your grievance has been heard.
Why did it end up this way?
Hajime, I don't know anymore!
"Hell Girl
The Light of the Hospital Ward"
Next time,
"The Light of the Hospital Ward"
"Hell Girl
The Light of the Hospital Ward"