It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
"Silent Friendship"
"Do you know Hell Girl?"
Hell Link...
A black magic site that
"An urban legend currently
a hot topic among teens,
A black magic site that
"An urban legend currently
a hot topic among teens,
you can only get to at midnight.
The terrifying agent of revenge,
'Hell Girl'!"
It's said
that only those filled
with resentment can access it.
"Hell Link
Search"
"Search Results 4 Matches
1. Hell Link
2. First Avenue, Hell"
"New Urban Legend"
Well, hello.
Please.
Welcome.
I won't be staying long.
Don't be in such a rush.
Why don't you at least have a
cup of coffee, Ms. Seira Yamamoto?
Don't call me by my name!
The photos and the negatives.
May I count it?
Don't be ridiculous.
Celebrities are always in the public eye,
so it must be inconvenient
when you want to have fun.
This is all of it?
I would like it if you would
trust me on that score.
Please be careful in the future.
Scumbag.
Oh, have you heard of Hell Girl?
Apparently, she'll avenge your grievances.
That attitude hurts.
Right on the dot.
I guess it won't work
for people who cause grievances.
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Goro Ishizu
Send"
This was the right thing to do.
Yuko, I'll make sure you're avenged.
What's the matter, Ai?
Guess what, Grandma? I met a girl.
A girl?
Yes.
It felt like she was a dear
old acquaintance for some reason.
A dear old acquaintance?
You say such odd things, child.
Odd? You're right, it is odd.
Well, it seems you have another message.
Ow!
Don't use the computer while you're eating!
It's bad manners!
Throwing a boiled egg is
bad manners, too, I'll bet.
All right.
They say the top reason
why kids become delinquents
is because the parents
lead dissolute lives.
Oh-ho, then we've got
nothing to worry about.
After all, look at what a
wonderful dad you've got.
I'm kidding.
Oh, yeah, Tsugumi,
have you heard of Hell Girl?
Hell Girl? The agent of revenge?
Yeah, that's it. Do any of your friends
know anything about it?
You know, like someone who's seen
the Hell Link page or something.
Are you going to write an article on it?
Yeah. "The truth behind
the agent of revenge!"
Sounds like a seller, huh?
Tsugumi?
You'd better not.
Huh? Why?
Tsugumi?
Hey...
Care to give death a try?
Tsugumi!
You okay?
Tsugumi, hang in there!
Hey...
Hell... Girl...
He's laughing...
That bastard...
Why? Why won't you come, Hell Girl?
"Amano"
You using the Internet?
Yes. Thanks to this sucker,
doing research has gotten a lot easier.
Tsugumi wasn't very energetic today.
Oh, she was just in a bad mood.
She's getting to be at a difficult age.
I'm sure it's tough,
since you've got work to do,
but why don't you take her to
an amusement park for once?
I wonder if she'd enjoy that.
She's precocious.
She may seem that way,
but she's still a kid at heart.
Right, then maybe
I'll do that next weekend.
Amusement park, huh?
I seriously doubt she'd enjoy it.
"28: Name Notable Mr. Noname
No way she exists.
27: Name Nararihyon
The media's just intrigued
and making a fuss about it."
28: Name Notable Mr. Noname
I wanna go to Hell's hot spring!!!! ( `;)"
"29: Name Kurikuri Boy
Sounds kinda hot!
30: Name GBC39
I went to Hell Link. I sent them an e-mail,
because I wanted retribution,
but there's been no response."
"31: Name Notable Mr. Noname
Don't lie!
32: Name Notable Mr. Noname
You must be a lunatic!"
GBC 39...
"Search"
"1. Hamburger Chain GBC
Serious burger shop
Homepage (for latest info)"
This shop seems far removed
from anything vengeful.
Maybe this wasn't it.
Yuko...
Last stop.
Wh-Where am I?
I'm here.
What?
I am Ai Enma.
Hell Girl...
You hate that man?
Yes.
Enough to want to kill him?
I mean...
Because of him, Yuko is...
Wanyuudou.
Yes, Miss.
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
To Hell...
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
We're talking after you die.
You'll never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
No!
No! H-Help!
Help!
All that remains is for you to decide.
"Tasty Milk"
I left you some milk.
I don't want it.
Drink it. Or you boobs won't get bigger.
That's sexual harassment!
It's parental love.
You're still looking into it, huh?
Huh? Into what?
Hell Girl.
N-No, I'm not. I'm not
looking into it anymore.
Liar.
It's true.
I checked your browsing history
while you were taking a bath, Hajime.
Well, if you want to keep
researching that much, that's fine,
but be careful, okay?
Y-Yeah, I'll be careful.
Give me the milk.
Sure.
Tsugumi...
H-Hey!
I-I can see...
What?
A hamburger shop...
Welcome!
Tanuma, didn't you quit?
I came to see the manager.
Is he here?
Yeah.
Boss!
Yeah. What's up?
Oh, it's you, Tanuma.
What is it? The last of your pay
should have been deposited already.
Could I have a moment of your time?
You really saw the number 39?
Yeah.
You dummy.
I told you to stay home,
but you just had to come along.
But... you can't see it...
I'll... take you to
an amusement park sometime.
Huh?
You know, an amusement park.
What is it?
What's this about?
Dragging me out here like this?
Oh, yeah, how is Kido doing?
I was so shocked when
I heard she'd jumped.
She didn't seem like she had such troubles.
Did you find out why she did it?
Was it disappointment in love
or something like that, after all?
You pushed her.
What?
Don't play dumb! I know!
Come on now, what are you saying?
That's an awful accusation to make.
Yuko had told me about it.
That you were cooking the books
and stealing money from the store!
Yuko had feelings for you,
so instead of reporting it to the police,
she said she was going
to talk you out of it.
That she'd get you
to return all the money,
so it'd be like it never happened!
She called me on my cell phone that day.
That she was on her way to see you.
Yuko seriously loved you, you know!
And yet...
You've got it all wrong, Tanuma.
I never pushed her.
Don't lie to me!
I was watching!
That day, I was worried,
so I went to the building...
And then...
No, that wasn't me.
It was you.
You have proof of this?
I don't care about proof.
I saw you. That's more than enough.
It won't do you any good
to go to the police.
I've got an alibi for that day.
I'm not going to the police.
What do you plan to do?
I'm going to have Hell Girl
get revenge for me.
Hell Girl?
That thing that everyone's
clamoring about online?
You seriously believe that?
What are you, stupid?
There's no way she really exists.
She does.
Before I had Ai Enma get revenge for me,
I wanted to ask you one thing.
I wanted to know what you
thought of that day.
I understand well now.
That was no accident.
You don't care one bit about Yuko!
I understand well now...
Poor Yuko...
Chie...
Chie, the truth is,
you're the one that I've always...
Don't play with me!
What kind of person are you?!
I never thought you were
this kind of person!
You're disgusting.
What?!
That's some friendship.
But you were too honest with me!
Hey!
Stop it!
Your grievance has been heard.
Ow...
Hajime!
Hey, you okay?
Somebody!
Over here.
Over here!
Wh-What's going on?
Hey, where in the world are...
Yuko!
Oh, I missed you, Goro!
Quit it!
Y-You idiot! Stop this!
Why? Let's fall together.
Come, we'll both go this time.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Betray another's affections, and you
will be judged by those affections.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Hajime, did you find anything?
No, nothing.
So, he disappeared...
Yeah...
Hajime...
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
I'll give you a ride home, too.
That girl...
You know her?
Ai Enma.
What?
She's Hell Girl.
What?!
Here.
Yuko, I had feelings for him, too.
That could have been me, instead of you.
So, I...
Don't give up!
"Search Results: The site you
are looking for was not found.
Keyword: Hell Link Search"
"Chie Tanuma"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
ltsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Yuka Kasuga.
You were deceived?
All because I trusted that bastard,
Sis's dream is...
He'd been waiting for
his chance to get his revenge.
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
Next time, "Sweet Trap".
"Hell Girl
Sweet Trap"
Next time, "Sweet Trap".
"Hell Girl
Sweet Trap"