It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
"Spilled Bits"
Sawai!
Sawai, why don't you come to school?
Everybody's worried.
Could I at least just talk to you?
If you won't say anything, we can't
even find a way to resolve this.
Come on, Sawai!
Sawai!
Mr. Fukazawa, that's enough for today...
But...
It is true that she isn't feeling well.
Sawai, I'll come again tomorrow.
Well, then, please excuse me.
"Secret Place"
I have found a very wonderful place.
I have uploaded a picture
of it to the message board,
so please take a look at it.
It truly is wonderful.
I would like to go there.
I ended up staying home
from school again today.
The teacher has no regard
for my feelings, either.
I just cannot bring myself
to like my teacher.
I can't understand why he
goes to such lengths for me.
It makes me uncomfortable.
"Anemone"
Come on, Sawai, could I
at least just see you?
Sawai!
The teacher must have
his own various troubles.
I go to that place often myself
on my way home from school.
It brings me peace.
I could never tell anyone
things like this in real life.
This is our secret,
just between you and me.
A secret just between the two of us.
Please promise me.
Sawai, at least let me hear your voice!
-Sawai! Sawai!
-It's so strange.
That such a place could bring such peace.
I would like to go there, too.
Lately, I feel like I don't belong,
even in my own house.
Sawai! Sawai!
I am writing this e-mail
in the yard of that abandoned house.
Something bad happened at school
that has made me depressed.
Maybe I'll stay home
from school tomorrow, too.
Do you know about Hell Link?
Sawai! Sawai!
I've heard of it.
That if you write in the name of
the person you have a grudge against,
Hell Girl will supposedly avenge you.
I found the site the other day.
I cannot make up my mind whether
to write in my teacher's name or not.
Sawai!
I think it would be okay to write it in.
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
Are you feeling sorry for your teacher?
You never know, the teacher might
be wishing for it to happen, too.
"Yoshiki Fukazawa"
"Send"
You called?
Well, I don't know if someone such
as myself could be of any use to you.
Mr. Kashiwagi told me you were
an extremely passionate teacher.
Being passionate does
not mean I am capable.
I will not trouble you overly much.
Ah...
This is it.
Okay, everyone, quiet down!
This is Mr. Shibata and he's a journalist!
He's researching educational issues,
so all day today,
he'll be observing class
and talking to you guys,
so everyone be sure
to cooperate with him.
Got that?
Um...
Uh, um, I'm Hajime Shibata.
Uh, I'll try not to get
in your way, so I hope we can...
Come on now, be quiet!
Curses come home to roost...
Ai.
What's the matter, Ai?
No, it's nothing.
It's nothing at all.
You're all so quiet.
It's just that you seem so normal now.
When you were so noisy this morning.
That's kind of like socializing...
Socializing?
Right?
If your friends talk to you, you sort of
end up paying attention to them.
But I mean, your teacher was talking.
The teacher is an adult,
so we think he'll be able to take it.
We're kids, after all.
If we quietly listened to
what the teacher was saying,
you never know what people
might say about you later.
You're fine with this, Mr. Fukazawa?
Well, children these days
are all pretty much like this.
By the way, you guys,
have you heard of Hell Link?
I have, but...
It's just a rumor, right?
I tried searching for it,
but I didn't find it.
Have you heard any rumors
of any kids who have accessed it?
We're all stressed out, so...
Everyone's got one or two people
they feel like cursing.
Maybe that's the reason
a rumor like that has spread.
They're good kids at heart.
You try not to be
too impertinent, too, eh?
Yes, Sir...
"Fire Hydrant"
Did you know about Hell Link,
Mr. Fukazawa?
Oh, I had heard about it in a casual way.
You've never seen it?
Why do you ask?
Well, I thought you might have one
or two people you'd like to curse, too.
Mr. Shibata, are you sure that wasn't
what you were really researching?
Oh, no, not at all.
Someone I'd like to curse, huh?
Well, there might be those
who'd like to curse me, though.
Thank you very much.
-Please excuse me...
-Mr. Fukazawa.
I hear Sawai in your class
still hasn't been attending.
We cannot have this. We need
you to counsel her properly.
Yes, Sir...
She can stay in the
nurse's office if she attends.
Attendance is attendance, after all.
Non-attendance is an issue.
It affects the reputation of this school.
Can't we just dismiss her
from school, once and for all?
Guess I got nothing.
Akane.
Everyone lives a life where
not everything goes their way.
And that applies to you
even more at your age.
There's no way you
can keep this up forever.
You know that, too, don't you?
Why don't you come to school?
If you come, you'll feel that much better.
You'll wonder what you'd been
agonizing over all this time.
That's just how it is.
In point of fact,
you behaved cheerfully early on.
Please say something.
I won't know anything if you won't talk.
Even if I told you...
What?
Even if I told you, I don't
think you'd understand.
Why not?
You can earnestly do your work
without any doubts
and live a normal life,
and I don't think someone like
that could understand my feelings.
The social environment of
the classroom is very hard.
Even if I know it's wrong,
I still have to do what's expected.
Even if I know it's bad,
I still have to play along.
Over and over and over.
That's what I don't like.
You've never even imagined it
might be like that, have you?
You thought everyone behaved
whatever way they wanted, right?
People might seem to be having fun,
but that's just appearances.
That's why I say you can't understand.
Please leave me alone already!
Why do you bother with me so much?!
Isn't it because it's a problem
for you that I don't go to school?
If you have a student who doesn't attend,
it damages your position, so...
Don't talk like you know anything!
Don't think you're the
only one who's special!
I'm sorry.
It's exactly as you say.
I wasn't thinking of you,
but of my own position.
Even today, the reason I came here
is because the vice principal
pressured me about you.
It's about appearances...
It's all about appearances.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
What?
I'll come again.
You shouldn't worry
your mother too much, okay?
I do not know what I should do anymore.
Am I in the wrong or are
those around me in the wrong?
I don't know anymore.
What a coincidence.
I was thinking similar thoughts.
I do not know what I should do.
Maybe I really will quit going
to school, once and for all.
"Faculty Room"
I was surprised.
I'm the one who kept
pestering you to come to school,
but when you actually came,
it made me feel even more worried.
How stupid is that?
What is it? Did something happen?
I don't really know myself...
what I should do, so...
But...
Because you revealed how you honestly
felt yesterday, that's why...
I'm sorry.
Mr. Fukazawa.
Hold on a minute.
Can you guess where I am right now?
At school! I can't
believe it myself, either.
I'll e-mail you again when I get home.
"I'll e-mail you again when I get home.
Anemone"
"Anemone"
What are you doing?
Did you know?
Were you exchanging e-mails with me,
knowing that I was Anemone?!
What?
What is the meaning of this?!
W-Wait a minute.
Well, what about it?!
No, that's not true!
What?
That's not true.
I'm shocked.
I had no idea you were Anemone.
I didn't mean to trick you.
Please forgive me.
I had no other outlets.
It was the only way
I could take it anymore.
When I was a student,
I couldn't understand why
someone wouldn't come to school,
but when I became a teacher,
I understood for the first time.
It's so ironic.
But my correspondence
with you was my salvation.
Same here.
I'm sorry. I wrote in
your name on Hell Link.
You met her? You met Hell Girl?
What kind of girl was she?
Somehow, she seemed
like a lonely person.
I see.
I wish I could meet her, too.
Say...
Won't you send me to Hell?
What?
I'm tired. I want to be out of my misery.
I'm sick and tired of it all.
Please.
If you really want retribution,
untie this red thread.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
Fukazawa's so pathetic.
He acts like he's understanding,
but he's sort of off the mark.
Seriously, it's like, stay away from me.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
So how many times must I tell you?
Being considerate of your students is fine,
but what the parents are most
concerned about is career paths!
If you cater to the bad students,
and the entire class's grades...
All that remains is for you to decide.
Your grievance has been heard.
This is...
I can go straight to Hell from here, right?
I'm right, aren't I?
Mr. Fukazawa...
Do you know the meaning
of what you've done?
What?
Look.
Sawai...
Any human who has entered
into the covenant with me
will never see Heaven,
and after death, their soul will
wander for eternity in pain and agony.
You didn't know that, did you?
You were too wrapped up in yourself.
Thinking you'd take a
pleasant trip out to Hell?
No...
Sawai...
Mr. Fukazawa, I will
be coming later as well.
So please wait for me.
In the depths of Hell...
Sawai...
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Missing?
Mr. Fukazawa is?
Yes, and he was such
a passionate teacher, too.
Perhaps he took things too much to heart.
I hope he does not do anything misguided.
How'd it go?
I guess you can never tell with people.
They say that enthusiastic
teacher's gone missing.
And he seemed so earnest...
Maybe the kids these days...
Tsugumi?
Hey, you okay?
Tsugumi?!
Is it all right this way?
With Hell being Heaven...
What?
It's all right, Ai.
If they're all right with it,
then it's all right.
There's no need for you to
give it any further thought.
But...
It's so strange.
That such a place could bring such peace.
This is our secret,
just between you and me.
A secret just between the two of us.
Please promise me.
Your grievance shall be avenged.
"Akane Sawai"
ltsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Tsugumi had another mysterious vision.
Not only that, but this time,
it wasn't of a future incident.
The man wrote that story
shortly after the war.
Did you meet her?
And did the same thing happen to you
as what happened in the story?
Please tell me what
happened 50 years ago.
Tell me why Ai Enma
has her gaze on you now.
"Hell Girl
Purgatory Girl"
Tell me why Ai Enma
has her gaze on you now.
"Hell Girl
Purgatory Girl"
Next time, "Purgatory Girl".
"Hell Girl
Purgatory Girl"