It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
"When will the cherry blossoms flower?"
"When will they flower
in the mountain village?"
"When will the cherry blossoms
grow fragrant?"
"When the laughing child
of seven plays"
"When will the cherry blossoms
dance about?"
"When the singing child
of seven goes to sleep"
"When will the cherry blossoms
wilt away?"
"When the dead child of seven ascends"
"Home in the Twilight"
Tsugumi!
Huh?
Look at this!
Isn't it awful?!
What happened?
The boys! It's the boys!
That Suzuki guy yanked on it.
And it broke...
Yup! But Suzuki just
laughed and ran away!
It's unforgivable!
Right?
Why don't you grab him
and make him apologize?
Apologizing won't do any good.
That's right, because he broke it.
I know, let's send him to Hell.
Oh, great idea! Let's do that!
Let's get Hell Girl
to send Suzuki to Hell!
He's a nasty guy anyway.
I'd be happier if he weren't around.
You gave me one hell of a scare.
I'm sorry.
I thought my heart would stop when
I got the call from the hospital.
Sorry...
He was a good person, wasn't he?
That driver...
It was my fault,
but he was apologizing so much...
Oh...
"Reception"
lf...
If I'd died in that accident...
Would you have hated that driver?
Y-You dummy, what're you saying?
He was a good person, wasn't he?
But if I'd died, wouldn't you
have thought about killing him?
I don't know...
I don't know anymore...
I owe you an apology.
I'll stop now.
Hell Girl...
From now on, I'll never
even mention her around you.
So, you forget about it.
Hajime...
Here, wipe your tears.
O-Okay...
"Japan's Cherry Blossoms"
Yes, that's right.
Oh, I see.
How does the schedule look
for the other party?
-Yes. Yes, yes.
-Mother...
Okay, then please take care of it.
Is it okay?
Is it really okay for it
to just end like this?
Is it okay?
Hey, good news.
What?
I'm going to Hawaii to cover a story.
Hawaii?
It looks like I can fudge the expenses,
so let's go together.
It's a simple story,
so it'll be like going on vacation.
You can swim in the ocean, Tsugumi.
Hajime...
What's wrong? Don't wanna go?
It's Hawaii!
Of course, I'll go.
Yeah? Okay, it's settled.
Then I'll make the arrangements
for the tickets right now.
Let's see...
I'll go make some tea.
Sure.
Huh? That's strange...
I was sure I'd saved that
crooked travel agent's number...
Crooked stuff is wrong.
Tsugumi?!
You know Sentaro?
What?
You know him?
Hell Girl...
Tsugumi!
Please stop this...
Come on, please, just stop it!
I won't get in your way!
I won't chase after you any more!
So release my daughter!
I'm begging you!
Stay away from us from now on!
"Japan's Cherry Blossoms"
Hajime...
Tsugumi, you're back?
We can't leave it like this.
We won't be able to end it like this.
To find out why...
To find out what she wants to tell us...
We have to meet Hell Girl.
Tsugumi... But you...
I want to know the answers, too.
Ai, what's the matter?
It's nothing, Grandma.
Are you troubled about something?
No, I'm fine.
Could it be that you're...
I'm fine...
"Japan's Cherry Blossoms"
Mutsumi Village, huh?
They were here.
Hell Girl and that boy...
Sentaro...
Who is he?
How is he related to Hell Girl?
Why would she ask if you know him?
She's there?
She's not?
Don't scare me, damn it!
"Yamano Inn"
We almost never have any guests here
during this season.
It's cold and if it snows,
it blots out the beautiful view.
Ah, I see.
We've usually had snow by this time
every year, so you're very lucky.
Oh, it's started.
Huh?
Snow...
Oh, you're right.
I can't believe it,
just as we were talking about it.
Is the bath ready?
Yes, please help yourselves.
Tsugumi, go take a bath.
Alone?
What?
Oh...
Sorry, that was a weird thing
for me to say.
Huh? No...
Then I will show you the way.
See you later.
What am I supposed to do
in situations like that?
Do you feel it?
Do you feel something when
you look at this view?
I'm coming in...
Tsugumi, Father's here...
Hajime...
Do you feel something
when you look at the view?
That's what she asked?
Yeah.
What does that mean?
This is the first time we've ever been
to this out-of-the-way place.
Thank you. You're such a darling.
It's nothing.
Isn't it great that
the weather has cleared?
And there isn't too much snow
on the ground, either.
Yes.
Whereabouts do you plan to visit?
If you'd like,
there happens to be a place behind us
that offers a great view.
Ma'am, is this place far?
What?
Oh...
Well, it's about
20 minutes from here, but...
Oh, really?
Please tell me how we can get there.
Um, but it's winter right now...
Local stories?
I'm not originally from around here, so...
Oh, why not inquire at the temple?
The temple?
It happens to be right on your way
to the waterfall.
The head priest there
may know those kinds of things.
"Shichidouji"
Please. It's just stem tea,
but it will warm you up.
Thank you for the tea.
You have certainly traveled a long way,
coming from Tokyo.
And at this time of year...
Covering stories for a magazine
sounds like hard work.
Yes, well...
"Freelance Reporter
Hajime Shibata"
Mr. Shibata...
"Freelance Reporter
Hajime Shibata"
But what a coincidence...
Oh?
Old stories, is it?
The truth is, I am not exactly from
these parts, either.
I was hired for the job,
if you will.
I had no idea.
I am sorry I could not be of help.
Oh, not at all.
That's brown sugar candy.
They're delicious.
Brown sugar candy?
It's a time-honored flavor.
You're right, it's really delicious.
Isn't it, though?
Oh, yes. I just remembered something.
Do you know of a practice
called Seven Sending?
Seven Sending?
It is apparently a practice that was
once observed in these parts.
In order to ask for good health...
...and abundant harvests
of the mountain god,
once every 7 years, they supposedly
made a sacrifice to the mountain...
...of a girl that just turned
seven years old.
A child of seven to the mountain?
That's the same age as me.
"Seven"
Seven is a number that represents
the yang of ying and yang,
"Seven"
so it is an auspicious number.
So it is an auspicious number.
In other words,
it symbolizes auspicious events...
...and in turn,
it is also said to be the number
that invites auspicious events.
So, to invite auspicious events
to occur in the village,
they sacrificed a seven-year-old
child to the god?
This temple was supposedly built...
...to appease those young souls
wandering in the mountains.
Hence, the name...
"Shichidouji"
Yes, and the man who
built this temple...
"Shichidouji"
...is actually the founding owner
of this brown sugar candy maker.
It was built over 400 years ago
in the Azuchi-Momoyama period.
The owner was supposedly
originally from around this area,
but left due to some circumstance...
...and later went on to succeed
as a brown sugar candy maker.
Though, I understand...
...that no one related to the founding
owner works at the shop anymore.
But even now, several times a year,
they send us these candies
as an offering.
What is the shop called?
Yes, that's the coincidence
I mentioned earlier...
It's called Shibataya.
What?
Shibata?
So that was it...
That was it.
Head Priest, what was the name of
the founding owner of Shibataya?
"Shichidouji"
I'm told that his name was Sentaro.
From the way you look, I guess
you couldn't find her, either.
You struck out, too, huh?
We sure are a hopeless bunch.
Don't say that.
Honestly!
Where could the Miss have gone?
It's not even for any jobs.
She's just been disappearing
without warning lately.
Well, you know,
the Miss is a young lady...
Ouch!
You think this is a time
for joking around?!
You didn't have to throw that at me!
That hurt!
Oh? Back again.
-What?!
Oh...
You meant that one...
Hold on...
Just maybe...
Is this the place?
The view that you saw?
Someone piled these up?
This is...
Hey!
Ai Enma?
Gotcha!
No! Let go, Sentaro!
-Sentaro?
-You can't catch me!
-Hell Girl and Sentaro...
So, the two were childhood friends...
You're here.
Hell Girl!
It still remained.
The abominable bloodline
had not died out.
It was that blood
that led me astray.
Abominable? What in the world
are you talking about?
Stop!
Stop...
Please! Stop!
Please!
Stop, Sentaro!
Tsugumi, you okay?
You were buried...
What?
You were buried?
Were you? By Sentaro...
What?!
Do you mean to kill me once again?
Transcending time...
Again, like you did then?
Though I have accepted it all...
I will not be killed!
Be gone!
She's here, just like I thought!
You can't, Miss!
Stop this! You mustn't kill
at the behest of your emotions!
You will be banished to Hell!
Even so, I do not care!
This is bad. Her heart
is completely ruled by hatred!
Run!
What are you doing?! Hurry!
Miss, stop this!
Be gone!
Miss!
-Miss!
I do not care.
So be it!
Consign this grievance to Hell!
Ltsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Miss, you've done nothing wrong.
It's the same in every era.
Humans are creatures that hurt
others for their own happiness.
By covering their sins with other sins.
And when they do, bitter grudges are born.
Yes, just like with you, Miss.
"Hell Girl
Hell Girl"
Yes, just like with you, Miss.
"Hell Girl
Hell Girl"
Next time, "Hell Girl".
"Hell Girl
Hell Girl"