It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
For a while there,
I thought she was finished,
but I'm really glad
Ms. Kurenai made a recovery.
She must've found new enthusiasm,
now that she has a successor.
Yes, I imagine so.
Ms. Kurenai, my apologies
for not keeping in touch.
Hello. And who is this?
I am pleased to meet you, Ms. Kurenai.
Haven't I seen you on TV?
Yes, she's one of the
talented girls we represent.
My name is Kaworuko Kurushima.
I am Kurenai. Nice to meet you.
I'm a huge fan of yours!
I heard we'll get to see your play,
"Lady Detective", again,
and I'm already looking forward to it!
Thank you.
I wish you all the best. Please excuse us.
Well, Ms. Kurenai, I will see you around.
She's so wonderful!
As youthful as ever and...
What an adorable girl.
More importantly, Ayaka,
with someone
"already looking forward to it",
we cannot afford to
put on a shabby performance.
O-Of course.
"Kurenai Theater Studio"
What are you doing?!
This will not do!
You are a weeping willow on the street!
So why are you swaying
when there isn't even a breeze?!
I-I know, I'm sorry!
Now, one more time, from the top!
Yes, Ma'am!
I am a willow...
A serene willow by the river.
Honestly! How many times
do I have to tell you?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Maybe she adopted her, not to make her
the future face of the studio,
but so she could abuse her.
No, that's not possible.
But it might be hard to
fault people for saying so.
I feel bad for Ayaka.
Please...
Please!
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
"Cracked Mask"
"Midori Kurenai"
"Send"
Who are you?!
You summoned me, remember?
I am Ai Enma.
Hell... Girl...
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
However...
What?
...once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell.
Hell?!
Change your mind, after all?
Wait!
Let me think about this a little. Please.
She adopted me
because she supposedly
recognized my acting skills then.
So what's with the way
she's treating me now?!
I can't take it anymore!
Go to Hell!
Yo, if it isn't Ayaka.
Takeshi.
Playing with dolls at your age?
Whoa, that's a freakish one you got there!
You gonna curse someone
to death with that?
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Let's see it.
Quit it! Give it back!
Wow, this is well-made.
Cut it out!
My bad.
That was close.
By the way, Ayaka,
could we borrow some money?
About 100,000.
What do you need a fortune like that for?
Don't be such babies!
You're the daughter of
a well-to-do family now.
It should be a cinch for you, right?
You damn leeches.
I know!
Forget about Hell Link. It might be
better to ask these idiots instead.
I'll consider lending it to you,
but on one condition.
Woohoo! That's our Ayaka!
Always willing to negotiate!
We'll do whatever you want!
Good evening!
Evening!
Who are you people?!
Hey, old lady, give us some money.
We're starving.
Get out immediately, or I will scream!
You just try it. I'll smash
your face in before you do.
Bitch! How dare you!
Be good now.
Hurry up and fork over the money!
Ayaka!
Why you!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do you
think you're doing?!
Shut up! Get out or I'm calling the police!
Damn you! Just you watch!
You'll pay for this!
What a woman.
Young men these days are so spineless.
Are you hurt at all, Mother?
No, I'm fine.
Thank goodness. Just to be safe,
I'll call the police...
Ayaka, were those men by any chance
old acquaintances of yours?
I'm sorry, Mother.
The truth is, they've been
following me around these last few days,
threatening to leak stories
from my time at the orphanage
to the media, whether the
stories are true or not.
But with what just happened,
I will properly report it to the police
tomorrow and have them caught.
Can I trust you on this?
Of course, Mother!
Incidentally, where were you
and what have been doing up so late?
I was practicing the willow
in the rehearsal room.
Are you able to do it now?
No, not yet...
But I will work hard,
so that I do not disgrace myself
as the successor of the
great actress, Midori Kurenai!
Yes, well, it's late, so go to sleep now.
I will. Good night.
We'd better report
this incident to the Miss.
What do you think she'll do?
Beats me.
"Kurenai Theater Studio"
The next production of "Lady Detective"
is about a young girl,
who shows up at a mystery author's place,
claiming to be a fan
and proceeds to play out a
game of death. It's a two-person play.
"Lady Detective"
and proceeds to play out a
game of death. It's a two-person play.
"Lady Detective"
It's also the play that launched
our studio head's career.
"Lady Detective"
The young girl, whom our
studio head played back then,
"Lady Detective"
hasn't been cast yet,
but there's no doubt Ayaka
will be chosen for that role.
But there's no doubt Ayaka
Ayaka must be a very good actress.
Of course!
After all, she was adopted for her
promising talent as an actress.
I hear the studio head plans to
make this performance her last
and retire to let Ayaka take over.
Is everyone for Ayaka
becoming the new studio head?
What an odd thing to ask.
Of course, we're for it.
Ayaka is serious about her work
and she doesn't give herself airs.
The studio head wants everyone to
assemble in the rehearsal room.
Oh, okay.
Is everybody here?
I will now announce who will play
opposite me in our next production.
At long last, this day has come.
Everything I've endured up
until now has been worth it.
Come in.
This is Kaworuko Kurushima.
I'm sure you all know her
from the TV dramas she's been in.
She will be playing opposite me.
I'm Kurushima. I look forward
to working with you!
What?!
Why?
It's not Ayaka?
I never expected a guest
performer from the outside.
Wh-What's going on here?
I'm honored, Ms. Kurenai.
I never imagined I would
get to play a part
-That woman...
-in "Lady Detective".
It's like a dream come true!
I expect much of you.
Do your best.
I will.
You bitch!
Mother, what is the meaning of this?!
Are you saying I am not good enough?!
Yes, you still have a long way to go.
I do not understand! How am I lacking?!
Please explain it to me!
Listen to me.
If you think your expression and
your voice are all there is to acting,
you are greatly mistaken.
Unless you are focused down to
the very tips of your fingernails,
it cannot be called acting.
Uh, what are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
I am referring to last night's incident.
Wh-What do you mean?
You are so hopeless.
I told you to drop this pitiful act.
Ms. Kurenai...
So there you have it.
My mind is occupied with
the production right now.
You're distracting me, so please leave.
If it galls you, go and polish your craft.
She saw through me?
No, it can't be.
My performance was perfect.
I get it!
I bet those bastards ratted me out!
What a ham.
What's with that piss-poor performance?!
You think you can take my place
with that level of skill?
You've got some nerve!
You should give up the part!
That's it. I can just
force her to give it up.
What? We never ratted you out!
Well, we'll just say that you didn't.
Anyway, about the money...
Yeah, yeah, that's what I'm calling about.
Hey, I'll pay you double,
so would you do me a favor?
Miss Kurushima, what's the matter?!
Who did this?! Who would
do such a terrible thing?!
It's okay, Ayaka!
If you did this for my sake,
please don't do anything
like this ever again!
I'm not bothered by this at all.
I mean it.
Thank you for what you said earlier.
To be honest, I was happy
to accept the role,
but I felt bad about taking it from you.
No, it's okay. Don't worry about it.
Then turn it down from the get go!
What do you make of that?
I hope she's not up to something.
Yes!
Well? Are you having fun?
Y-Yes. Um, I'm sorry,
but it's getting late, so I...
A little longer won't hurt, right?
We've just gotten to be friends.
But...
Yo, cutie.
May I help you?
Is she the one?
Yup.
Woohoo! Super foxy.
Well, I'll leave the rest to you.
Okay.
A-Ayaka, wait...
Okay, you're coming with us.
P-Please let me go!
Sorry, we're not letting you go.
Please, I beg of you!
I have an important rehearsal tomorrow!
Drink this and we'll let you go.
What is that?
A medicine that'll make your voice pretty.
You're lying.
Okay, hold her.
Now, drink it down in one go.
Hey, did you hear? Did you hear?
Miss Kaworuko's lost her voice!
I wonder what happened.
Maybe it's the pressure.
Who knows?
I wonder what could have happened.
She was so enthusiastic.
If you're going to blame someone,
blame this woman, Kaworuko.
Wh-What?
Assemble all the troupe members
in the rehearsal room!
I have an important
announcement to make!
Yes, Ma'am.
I guess that means I'm the lead now.
Wait just a minute.
Do you not want to know
what the announcement is?
What?
The next production will be canceled
and the troupe will also be disbanded.
Additionally, I will be dissolving
the arrangement to adopt you.
It's your doing, isn't it?
Wh-What is?
I've told you to drop the pitiful act!
Don't take me for a fool!
You cannot deceive my eyes!
This is a misunderstanding!
If this is about the other night,
it really was nothing!
I was reborn when you took me in!
I am so glad that I met you!
Thanks to you, I learned
the joys of performing
and found hope to live by!
Words cannot express
how thankful I am to you!
Oh, Mother!
This is disgraceful! Get away from me!
At any rate, the decision
has already been made!
I've also informed my attorney!
This is goodbye.
What the hell, you damn hag?!
It saddens me that you
would call me a damn hag.
Don't say such sad things.
I've done everything for your sake.
My instruction may have been harsh,
but what you did is not
something that can be overlooked.
But if you are willing to
acknowledge your mistake
and make amends for what you did...
If you still wish to continue
acting at that point,
I'll talk to a theater troupe
I know on your behalf.
It's okay.
You can still start over.
With your talents, I'm sure you
can become a wonderful actress.
Cut the crap!
Pardon me?
Shut your damn mouth!
I've had enough of your pompous ass!
What's that?
Like hell I'm gonna play house
with you for that!
If I can't get your fame
and fortune, there's no point!
Don't you get it?!
I am sorry...
I am truly sorry that it
had to come to this.
Like sorry's gonna cut it, you dumbass!
Just you watch!
Since it's come to this,
I've found my resolve!
"Ayaka Kurenai"
I'll end up suffering the same fate,
but if she dies before
she dissolves the adoption,
at the very least,
her estate will go to me.
Go to Hell!
What?
Wh-Why?
Don't you get it?
When did you get in here?!
Hey, what is this?! Why?!
Someone untied the thread first.
Huh?
That person accessed
Hell Link last night
and untied the red thread just earlier.
What did you say?
Your grievance has been heard.
It's too late now.
Give it up.
Why?! I was first!
What's going on?!
Answer me!
Hey, hold it!
What is this?
I'm on stage?
Feel like acknowledging
your own guilt yet?
Like hell!
If you don't acknowledge it,
you'll be going to Hell.
You don't mind that?
W-Well...
I don't want to go to Hell!
Yes, I acknowledge it. So...
Psyche!
What?
Whose voice was that?!
Me!
Hey, hey, your performance is all wrong!
You can't just pay lip service,
you have to speak from
the bottom of your heart.
Yes, I truly feel bad about Kaworuko...
Serves her right!
What the hell are you?!
Ow!
My! What is this play?
This is far too tawdry...
No! It's not my fault!
Wh-What? What is going on here?
That hurts!
Wait... Stop!
That hurts! That hurts!
Stop!
Stop! I've had enough of this acting!
We want to hear the words of
your true self, not your character.
B-Believe me, this is my true self.
No, no, that's not right.
Come now.
Damn it! If you want to
hear it that badly, I'll tell you!
I don't really give a damn about acting!
It's just a stepping stone to me!
For me to rise up in the world!
That's right. I've worked hard
to learn the craft of acting,
so I'm going to deceive people
for all they're worth!
At times, I'll be the great actress
that everybody admires!
At other times, I'll be
the elegant lady of the house!
At yet other times, I'll be
the scandalous temptress!
And at yet other times...
So, which is your true self?
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Where am I?
It was a convincing performance.
The best you've ever been.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Oh, sorry, coming through.
Hey, sorry, get that for me?
Sure!
"Kaworuko Kurushima"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Chie Tanuma.
You hate him?
I mean, because of him, Yuko is...
And she loved him!
She really loved him, and yet...
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
Next time, "Silent Friendship".
"Hell Girl
Silent Friendship"
Next time, "Silent Friendship".
"Hell Girl
Silent Friendship"