It is said that life's
encounters are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
"Please, help me."
That one again, eh?
Day in and day out. Talk about persistent.
But you decided not to
take that request, right?
Are we being ignored again today?
I swear...
J-Just a little longer...
That's enough for today.
What?
Oh, hello? It's me!
I'm starving! How about
we go grab a bite to eat?
Yeah, I'm at the office right now. See you!
Man, if only I could make
the acquaintance of Hell Girl,
this company could easily double in size.
Oh, but if that happened,
I guess you'd be out of a job.
I'll see you bright and early tomorrow.
What? I have final exams tomorrow.
There's a board meeting.
Misato, who do you think you even
owe the fact that you're in school?
"Dead Line Incorporated
Dead Line Incorporated Reception
Dead Line Incorporated
Asano Planning, Inc."
Good night.
Good night, I'll be going now.
"Fujimi Housing"
"The Woman in the Tall Tower"
"Dead Line Incorporated"
Yes, the online shop Dead Line
is a company our president,
Riho Kaifu, started
with a couple friends
when she was a student.
Ms. Riho is the only one
left of the original founders,
but with her rich knowledge of
computers and business acumen,
she's grown the company
to this size in just 4 years!
She must be an incredible woman.
All the employees look up to her.
Can you believe it?! In just 4 years!
Hey! When you put it like that,
you make it sound as if I used
some unscrupulous methods.
I'm sorry. That was hardly what I meant.
Is this our new part-timer?
What?
I'm Onda. Nice to meet you.
I'm the president, Riho Kaifu.
I look forward to working
with you, Ms. Onda.
Likewise!
Yes, so regarding the
M&A of Midori Communications...
Mr. Midorikawa, the largest shareholder,
is vehemently against it
and that puts us in a
rather tough situation.
Please be persistent and
continue to negotiate with him.
But it seems incredibly unlikely
that he will change his mind...
If we do not give up,
a providential wind might blow our way.
After all, that has been true in the past.
I understand.
Next, on the matter of increasing
the number of host computers...
Please take a look at the data before you.
-Along with the expansion
of the fiber optics network,
-Oh, Ms. Riho...
-each home...
With regards to that,
you are a pro among pros.
We will leave it entirely in your hands.
I'm honored.
Those directors are all idiots.
I didn't need you to come in.
A girl that looks like
she's in high school?
Yes. I saw her earlier
in front of the bathroom.
Oh, that's probably Misato.
Misato Urano. She's supposed to be
a distant relative of Ms. Riho's.
You'll see her around the office
from time to time.
Misato Urano, huh?
I think she's in her first
or second year in high school.
Her parents have passed away,
so Ms. Riho's looking after her.
She's treated like a part-timer here.
Sort of a real world education.
I had no idea.
But for all that she's
related to our president,
she's absolutely no good with computers.
So, she's a part-timer, but about
all she does is clean, make tea,
and act as a kind of companion
when the president is working late alone.
I see.
And then there's
Ms. Riho's old boyfriend...
Hey! You're talking too much!
Next up is news of a death.
The former president of
Midori Communications, Raizo Midorikawa,
still the largest shareholder, has died...
Of the Midori Communications shares
that I, Raizo Midorikawa, own,
I grant 75% of those shares to
President Riho Kaifu of Dead Line.
Maybe "grant" is going too far...
Oh, well.
Okay, pop that on to
that old geezer's PC for me.
Make it so it was written
maybe 10 days ago.
I'll alter the file's
property and registry.
So, which directory should I put it in?
I'll leave that stuff up to you.
Properties this, servers that.
It's all gibberish to me.
I can't understand how people
even manage to work with PCs!
Oh, it's time.
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
Make it more extreme today.
Something they'll believe
we'd want revenge for.
So it was uploaded by someone else...
It's just like the Miss suspected.
Ignoring us again?!
Maybe Hell Girl doesn't
really exist, after all!
Misato, go through that homepage
and find out who's behind it!
Should be a piece of cake for you.
Especially compared to
stealing data on new products
or messing with account balances.
But...
Do you want to go back to
being the shoplifting girl?
That's not it.
I tried that the other day at your request,
but instead, they came through
our firewall and almost got in.
That's not my problem!
Shoplifting girl, huh?
Troubling.
Yeah.
"Loop"
Wow! This shop is a
subsidiary of Dead Line?!
Huh? You know about our parent company?
My ex-girlfriend shopped with them a lot.
But I heard that company
only employs women.
That even their part-timers
are all women...
Now, they do.
There was a time when
they had men like me, too.
But the focus of the company
shifted towards women,
so the men wound up
reassigned to outside subsidiaries.
When you get down to it,
we were demoted, really.
There's no chance we'll be
reinstated at the main office.
Oh, that's right! I can never
go back to the main office!
Yeah, that's what being demoted means!
-I-I can never go back!
-S-Sir, get a hold of yourself!
"Minato Ward Office"
"Partial Copy of Family Register
Full Copy of Family Register
Certificate of Residence
Basic Resident Registers"
"Police Department"
"Yakitori Furusato
An Establishment with Taste
Yakitori Ramen Furusato"
Shoplifting?
It happens, right? Even in your store?
Sure, every once in a while.
That reminds me, I got an
odd memo about a year ago.
Memo?
Yeah, it said that if
we caught a shoplifter,
we were to contact the president
before reporting it to the police.
Huh.
And then it turned out
a girl I caught in my store
was related to the president.
Related to the president?!
Oh, no, no. Forget what I said.
Never mind all that.
What?! After you told me all that?!
Ms. Riho's told us not to talk about it.
But...
Maybe I will tell you.
-What?!
-About all sorts of things!
At the office, this girl is thought
to be useless with a computer, but...
Nope. According to the shop owner,
she's quite the computer geek.
She builds her own machines
and is supposedly capable
of hacker-type work, too.
Conversely...
The president is no good with computers.
Oh, you knew.
Watching their dealings in her office,
it was easy to figure out.
Furthermore, that girl
and Ms. Riho are not related.
Oh, they're not?
I checked into it during the day.
Incidentally, the ex-boyfriend
she started the company with
was apparently very
knowledgeable about computers.
Though, they seem to have
broken up before the company got big.
I get it now.
That's when she suddenly needed
someone good with computers.
And she thought of how she could
use a shoplifter to her advantage!
Make them help her in exchange for
not handing them over to the police.
And she's the one that fell into that trap.
Well, that's the sort of illegal methods
she's used to grow her company.
Really?
Hello?
Hey, Misato, I just got a call
from some weird man.
He's demanding I pay 100 million
if I don't want the company secrets leaked.
Is it a hacker?
Finding that out is your job!
You listen to me.
Make sure you find out who he is
before I get to the office tomorrow!
Getting in to work at this hour, eh?
Oh, my head hurts. Must be a hang over.
This is the issue you asked me
to handle yesterday.
Why don't you go to school for once?
Okay.
Also...
Let's take a break from
the Hell Girl thing for a while.
Staying up late night after night
like this isn't good for my skin.
Okay.
Hello? It's me!
"Metropolitan Police Department"
The man whose body was found
was Toru Kobayashi, age 33.
He was in the Metropolitan area...
The target is Toru Kobayashi, age 33.
I'll leave the method up to you.
Just take care of it quickly.
At last, with this...
At last, what?
At last, with this, you can
get the police to arrest me?
If I'm questioned about further crimes,
you think they might turn up evidence
that I murdered your father, too?
Like father, like daughter, I guess.
The way you're both good with computers
and the ultimate fate you'll both share!
Your father was the same.
In exchange for not pursuing
sexual assault charges,
he ended up helping me.
Not that he was guilty of those charges.
"Copying
Remaining Time 10 Sec
Cancel"
But his guilty conscience
got to be too much for him
and when he tried to
report me to the police...
...he disappeared from this world.
It must have been tough
for you to find my company.
After all, the fact he worked here
was strictly confidential.
Urano...
No, Misato Tamura!
How...
I can't use computers,
but there's a handy profession
called "investigator".
When I was having trouble
after I'd gotten rid of Tamura,
you showed up at the perfect time.
It got me a little suspicious.
So I hired an investigator
and had him look into it.
"-Cade PC Pavilion"
So I hired an investigator
and had him look into it.
"-Cade PC Pavilion"
You got caught shoplifting
on purpose, right?
So you could infiltrate this company.
You also allowed that hacker to get in,
so you could get dirt on me.
But too bad! I've turned
the tables on you!
Your actions haven't been secret at all!
S-Someone!
It's no use. This guy took care
of the security guard just earlier.
Don't you think anything of human life?!
Come on, after you kill one person,
it doesn't matter how many you kill.
That's how I've grown this company.
You're definitely going to Hell!
We're talking decades until that happens.
Life is ultimately just a game.
Whoever enjoys herself the most
before the game's over wins.
Don't let her get away!
Darn it!
It's because of contingencies like this
that I wanted to use Hell Girl!
Men are so useless
when you need them most!
Midnight!
That's right! Hell Link!
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
Please, kill Riho Kaifu for me!
"Kaifu
Send"
Please, kill Riho Kaifu for me!
Please!
"Send"
You summoned me, remember?
Wh-Who are you?!
I am Ai Enma.
Hell Girl?!
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie this red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
Right away?!
Not decades from now?!
Yes.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
After you die, your soul will go to Hell.
This world is Hell!
As long as that woman is alive!
Your grievance has been heard.
Did you take care of her?!
At least answer me!
This is!
"Dead Line Incorporated"
Oh, right. I...
Kenji, are these the hard disks...
I-It's not what you think, Riho!
I can explain!
H-He's dead!
Riho, what have you done?!
Like hell...I'm going to...
let you people...mess up my life!
I've found my resolve, thanks to you!
No matter what methods I have to use,
I'll win the game of life!
Even if I have to sacrifice
every person out there!
You'll be the first.
You'll be the first to be sacrificed.
You're next.
What are you doing in a place
like this, Ms. Riho?
"Dead Line Incorporated"
I-In a place like this?
The gateway to Hell.
"Dead Line Incorporated"
What?!
I told you it's your turn, didn't I?
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Why?!
Why do I have to be killed
over and over again?!
Not over and over.
What?
For eternity.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Hey, did you hear?
The thief they caught last night is
saying he killed the security guard!
But the security guard guy
is alive and well.
That's just it! Maybe he
was dreaming or something.
But talk about disappointing!
To think Ms. Riho was absolutely
no good with computers!
It was apparently Misato that was
doing all the president's work.
And I hear,
starting today, she's going to be
living in Ms. Riho's condo, but...
Who are you talking to?
Huh?
Uh, who was I talking to?
That's what I want to know!
Good work.
How did you like the
life of an "office lady"?
Sitting in front of a desk
all day just isn't my thing.
Lost in the darkness...
Wow!
When I die, I'm going
to Hell without fail.
We're talking decades until that happens.
Life is ultimately just a game.
Whoever enjoys herself the most
before the game's over wins.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm going to enjoy this game
to my heart's content.
"Misato Tamura"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental.
Your name?
Haruka Yasuda.
You hate her?
Just because of what she saw that day
through the window, Mother is...
I feel so sorry for her.
I can't stand to see her like this!
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
Next time, "Early Afternoon Window".
"Hell Girl
Early Afternoon Window"
Next time, "Early Afternoon Window".
"Hell Girl
Early Afternoon Window"