It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
Ai...
You have committed a forbidden act.
You have opened the door to your
heart that you swore to keep shut.
You can no longer be entrusted
with this task.
You will return with me to Hell.
And...
...you will be punished for your sins.
I can't yet.
I cannot return to Hell.
That will not be permitted.
Now, you are going back.
No...
It's not over yet.
Ai, I will not permit you to go!
The Miss! She was all right!
Where is she going?
Retribution...
-Retribution?
The Miss is still ruled
by a powerful hatred.
Miss...
Looks like we're being called on.
H-Hey!
Wanyuudou!
So you will go, after all.
Do you mean to go through
this again, Ai?
"The Ephemeral"
Why didn't Sentaro try to save Ai?
That's because...
You understand why, don't you, Hajime?
Because you said so.
Tell me. I want to hear it.
Hell Girl...
You want to hear, don't you?
What?
I'll tell you about your father.
Where's Hajime?!
Give Hajime back!
M-Mother?
I won't let you have Tsugumi.
What?
A woman like you...
I don't even want to see your face!
I want to start over.
How can I trust someone
who's already betrayed me once?!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, forgive me.
You must be joking!
You didn't just betray me!
You betrayed Tsugumi, too!
Go to that man!
Don't ever show your face
around us again!
Mother...
Get out of here!
Hajime...
M-Mother...
No...
No.
It's...
...not my fault...
What a bad man your father is.
It was his fault, and yet he
refused to acknowledge it.
It's...
...not my fault...
If your father had forgiven her,
your mother would not have had to die.
He could have saved her...
You must have been lonely
without your mother.
It must have been hard.
I will banish your father
to Hell for you.
Now, take it.
N... No!
I don't want it!
"Amano"
All that remains is for you to decide.
400 years?
Yeah, it's been about that long since
the Miss took up this task.
She had to do it, as her punishment.
Punishment...
A punishment she was
sentenced to in Hell, huh?
The Miss has done her best...
Long months and years, over the eras,
she's watched the result of the
grievances brought about by man.
She couldn't run away from it,
even if she wanted to.
Not as long as grievances existed.
Over the course of a mind-boggling
length of time,
the Miss has worked
to wash away her sins...
Forgetting her own grievance,
locking her emotions away.
But you two took her back to square one
in the blink of an eye.
That your ancestor was the object
of the Miss's vengeance...
You guys must've been shocked, too.
Talk about the worst karmic bond.
But why are you telling me this?
Weren't you ordered to watch me?
To be honest,
we don't know what to do anymore.
Yeah, we're powerless...
You there...
Hey, you there...
She's never spoken
to anyone but the Miss...
It looks like she means you.
What?
I'll let you out of here.
But in exchange...
Exchange?
There's something
I want you to do for me.
Mother...
You can just banish him.
You can just banish
the one you hate to Hell.
You've hated him all along, haven't you?
That was all a lie!
A world of lies that you created!
It's not the truth!
Even without knowing what happened then,
in your heart, you've hated
your father all this time.
You're wrong! I don't think that!
You think that it was your father's
fault that your mother died.
I don't think that!
It's...
...not my fault...
I don't... think that...
Why?
Why do you say such terrible things?
Wait! Give Hajime back!
Wait, Hell Girl!
Think well upon it, Tsugumi.
Nooo!
It's...
...not my fault...
Mother...
...in your heart, you've hated
your father all this time.
No...
Wh-What is it now?
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
Tsugumi...
Mother...
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance
will immediately be banished to Hell.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Here, it's your favorite snack, Tsugumi.
Stop this...
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander for
eternity in pain and agony.
Please, stop this...
Help me, Hajime...
It's...
...not my fault...
Tsugumi, it hurts... It hurts.
Stop this!
Your beloved father robbed you
of your mother.
It must be hard, Tsugumi.
It must be painful.
Your heart torn in two...
I'll help you.
You can escape this misery.
Pull the thread. Free your heart.
Don't suffer anymore.
I want to help you.
Tsugumi!
What did you try to make Tsugumi do?
Answer me, Ai Enma!
Miss.
Please stop this already, Miss!
Doing this won't...
Silence.
Let's get out of here, Tsugumi!
Wh-What's wrong, Tsugumi?
Poor Mother...
What?
Poor her...
Tsugumi...
That's right.
If only this man had forgiven her,
your mother would not have had to die.
Your mother would have
been with you, Tsugumi,
and you wouldn't have had to be lonely.
Stop this!
This has nothing to do with you!
Do you really think so?
Th-This can't be...
Your poor mother.
All because of that man...
You must pass judgment on him.
No...
No.
It's...
It's me that should've died.
I trusted her...
I couldn't forgive her!
I was so angry, I couldn't help myself!
Tsugumi, I'm sorry! It's my fault!
It's all my fault that your mother died!
Forgive me!
It's too late to apologize now.
What has already happened
cannot be undone.
I know. I know. I was an idiot.
Regret is meaningless.
What has been lost will
never be restored.
Untie the thread. I will avenge you.
Ayumi...
I loved you. I adored your smile.
That's why I worked so hard.
But b-because of that,
I left you feeling lonely...
In your desire for affection,
you made a mistake...
And I couldn't forgive you for that.
Not only that, but I thought
you deserved to die for it...
I never thought that would
really come to pass...
I just couldn't accept it...
l-I've always caused nothing but trouble
for the people I care about.
Always hurt them...
I'm to blame.
It must have been hard
for you, too, Tsugumi.
It must have been so lonely.
Now, untie the thread!
Tsugumi, do it.
You dummy, what are you saying?
You dummy!
I never once thought it was hard!
I was happy being with you, Hajime!
Because I love you, I was happy!
Tsugumi...
Why would you say things like that?
Weren't you happy, Hajime?
When you laughed with me,
was that all a lie?!
Having our meals, watching TV,
going out shopping...
There were times when I was lonely
because Mother wasn't around,
but Hajime... Father,
because I had you, I was all right.
It wasn't hard.
Was it hard for you to be with me?
Were you not happy?
Tsugumi...
Tell me...
Yeah, I was happy.
Just being with you, I was...
...able to feel blessed.
Really?
Really.
Okay. I'm so glad.
You're just Ai.
I don't need this.
You loved him, didn't you?
Loved Sentaro?
He loved you all along, too.
That's why he always regretted it.
So he built that temple...
Where...
Shichidouji, where we started.
Miss!
Ai...
Miss...
We're going.
Come.
Yes, Miss.
Why did she burn the temple?
Ai Enma was...
Nah, it's nothing.
Thank you, Tsugumi.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Don't leave me alone ever again, okay?
Yeah, I promise.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
All that remains is for you to decide.
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
You know what they say about
all that ends well.
Once the wound closes, that's it.
But before you know it,
you're suffering again in a similar
way from a fresh wound.
Ultimately, there is no such
thing as the end.
Humans are such utterly
pitiful creatures.
Eh, Miss?
The fresh wounds will be even more...
"It will continue..."
"Hell Girl"
The fresh wounds will be even more...
"It will continue..."
"Hell Girl"