It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
Does it bother you that much?
Sure, it bothers me.
There's no guarantee that Hell
Girl will notify you each time...
...and I want to stop her,
no matter what.
Tsugumi thinks what
Hell Girl does is fine, though.
The people that get sent to
Hell are all bad people, anyway.
Tsugumi...
I'm done.
Hey, Tsugu-
Sheesh!
Tsugumi?!
Tsugumi!
Tsugumi!!
You okay, Tsugumi?
Yuko was with Hell Girl...
Yuko?
Mr. Murai's...
My senior's?!
"Kind Neighbor"
Come to think of it,
they didn't come by this year,
did they?
They came last year, remember?
"We Wish You the Best in this Hot Weather
...a tough time, but we are happy
to hear that you are all doing well."
They came last year, remember?
"We Wish You the Best in this Hot Weather
...a tough time, but we are happy
to hear that you are all doing well."
They brought vegetables that
they grew on their farm.
Oh...
Father!
Oh, you've been drinking
so much again!
I'm sorry that he always does this.
Nah, I don't really mind...
I'm not gonna drink!
I won't drink anymore!
"Oden Shop"
I understand,
so let's go home, Father.
"Oden Shop"
Hajime, what kind of flower is that?
Red spider lilies, aren't they?
Red spider lilies...
Let's hurry.
Damn guy showed up, as expected.
Mr. Murai!
I wonder if they're not home.
Mr. Murai?
Yuko?
Is no one here?
Miss Yuko!
Tsugumi...
Mr. Murai...
Do you want some more?
No, thank you.
How are you doing?
Feeling a little better?
Yes...
What in the world happened?
I was totally under the impression
that the farm was going well.
Won't you tell us?
Yuko...
It was two years ago...
Right after we'd moved here.
There we go...
Whoa!
That was close.
Father!
Working hard there, I see!
The man's name was Ryosuke Sekine.
He lived on the other
side of the farm.
I apologize for my earlier behavior.
Maybe it's because I used
to work for a publishing company,
but I have this habit of
being suspicious of strangers.
And it doesn't seem like
we're very welcome here, so...
Thank you for the food.
It's delicious!
Here you go.
Oh, no, not me.
I've had a lot of bad experiences,
so I don't drink anymore.
Is that right? That's too bad.
But quitting a company job!
That's quite a daring move.
I inherited this vast place
from my uncle, after all.
It would be a shame
to just let it sit here.
And ever since I lost my wife,
I've had to leave my little girl
here alone so much.
I thought I could be around
for her a little more out here.
We're going to grow vegetables.
We're complete amateurs,
so I'm sure it won't be easy,
but we decided we'd work
hard at it together. Right?
Yup.
In that case, I might be able
to offer you some advice.
Since I used to do it long ago, too.
Really?!
I don't know how much
help I'll be...
Isn't that great, Yuko?
He says he'll lend us a hand.
Yeah!
After that, he began to
come to our place every day.
How to work the field.
How to pick seeds.
Even how to water
and fertilize the plants.
He was very generous
in teaching us.
In town, we'd be treated
as outsiders.
For Father, that man was the
only person he had to talk to.
Thanks to that man,
even in what was supposed to
be a difficult first year,
we were able to grow
really delicious vegetables.
I still remember it now.
Father looked really
happy that day.
That night, the man convinced
my unwilling father...
...and forced him
to expand the farm.
And then...
We had abnormal weather
conditions this year...
...and there were lots of pests.
Mr. Sekine...
We should've used pesticide.
We don't have room for that
kind of thing in our budget yet.
Necessity knows no law, right?
I imagine it's expensive...
Pesticide...
It's still not too late.
I'll let you have some
of the stuff I used to use.
R-Really?!
Please don't be shy.
Let's do our best!
Th-Thank you very much!
Father believed what
the man told him...
...and used the pesticide
every day,
but the vegetables kept dying
one after another.
It was around then that
Father started drinking again.
I still say it'd be better if
we consulted other people, too!
At this rate,
they're all really going to die!
It'll be okay. As long as
we do as Mr. Sekine says...
Father!
It'll be okay. No worries.
It'll be okay.
In the end, Father didn't
go consult anyone else...
...and kept on waiting for the
pesticide to start taking effect.
I wonder if he got lost
and wandered in here.
Oh, no! You can't lick that stuff!
What...
...does this mean?
Father?!
He told us it was a pesticide
that would kill the insects,
but he'd been giving us a solution
of just juice mixed with water.
Not knowing that, Father completely
believed it was real pesticide...
Why did that man
do something like that?
I heard about it
and found out later...
...that he used to be in a dispute with
Father's late uncle over this land.
It was revenge?
Why did Father have to die?
Moving in to a new house,
starting a new line of work...
We only wanted to live normally!
And that's why you accessed the site?
What?
The Hell Link site...
You were given a straw doll, right?
That you can get revenge
if you pull the thread?
I understand how you
feel really well,
but you shouldn't seek revenge!
Hajime!
Tsugumi, you be quiet!
Listen to me, Yuko.
If you pull that thread,
a person is going to be banished to Hell.
You may be able to get
your revenge that way,
but you'll have banished
someone to Hell.
That fact will never be erased.
You'll have to live with that
burden for the rest of your life.
You can see what a terrible
thing that would be, can't you?
I knew your father well.
He was always talking about you.
All he thought of was your happiness.
That's why I know that your
father wouldn't want revenge.
To say nothing of having you
live the rest of your life...
...with this guilt on your
shoulders for his sake.
This is sort of getting messed up...
Hajime!
I'll hold on to this.
Think this through carefully!
Hey, man, that's foul play,
isn't it?!
We'll just have to get it back.
Father...
Do I smell?
A little.
That wasn't fair.
Taking it away from
her was underhanded!
Yes, it might have
been underhanded.
But please understand.
I don't want Yuko
to seek out revenge.
I don't understand!
Yuko's father was practically
killed by that man!
See, Tsugumi,
there's a lot that happens in life.
And some of it's going to
be unbelievably unjust...
But you have to overcome
those things.
That's what it means to live.
So, it's okay even
if you get killed?
I never said that!
Yes, it's what you're saying!
Why are you taking sides
with a bastard like that?!
He deserves to get sent to Hell!
Yuko's father never
did anything bad...
A bastard like that,
the sooner he dies the better!
You're so pigheaded, Hajime!
If you got killed,
Tsugumi would get revenge, too!
Tsugumi!
Miss.
Wanyuudou...
I didn't expect Tsugumi
to say something like that...
I wonder if it's my fault,
after all.
Rain?
Tsugumi!
Father...
Hell Girl!
What should I do?
I don't know. Please tell me!
What should I do?!
That is for you to decide.
I'm just not going to forgive him!
Not him!
Yuko!
Have you seen Tsugumi?
What?
I can't find her anywhere.
You can't go that way!
It's dangerous at night!
Tsugumi!
Oh! This is...
It's Tsugumi's.
Tsugumi!
Hajime...
You idiot!
Do you have any idea
how worried I was?!
And in this rain...
It's not like I asked you
to worry about me.
Tsugumi!
You idiot...
You made me so worried...
I really was worried, you know...
Hajime...
You're not going to take revenge?
You're really okay with that?
Yeah.
I see. I'm glad.
You've gotta find happiness enough
for both you and your father.
Thank you.
Father, I'll do my best.
Not once, but twice...
So we never got our turn
in the spotlight.
We really have to do
something about that man.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
But I'm thinking of staying
here for a while.
Since I have a lot of memories
with my father here, too.
What do you want?!
He'd borrowed money with
this place as collateral?
I have his note right here, too.
It seems he had a lot of expenses
related to expanding the farm.
I told him I didn't need
anything of the sort,
but he insisted on it,
saying it wouldn't feel right otherwise.
That's a damn underhanded thing to do!
How far do you have to take
it before you're satisfied?!
Mr. Murai trusted you to the very end!
And yet, you...You call yourself human?!
You piece of scum!
Stop it!
It doesn't matter now.
Please move out as quickly as you can.
This place is a little more
cleaned up now,
so it should sell for a nice price.
Yuko...
Now, shall we go?
She should've pulled it, after all.
Then Yuko could've stayed
in that house...
It's your fault, you know, Hajime.
There's nothing for you
to worry about.
You'll make friends in no time.
Now, go on in.
That is for you to decide.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
There's a memory that
I can't forget.
There's a feeling that
I can't push away.
Tsugumi, I can't tell
you everything yet.
But please understand.
Revenge is wrong.
Hajime...
I don't think getting revenge
is a bad thing.
"Hell Girl
Rain of Remorse"
Next time, "Rain of Remorse".
"Hell Girl
Rain of Remorse"