It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
You're lying!
It's not a lie!
Here, take a look at this picture.
Holy crap, you're right!
Sho! I love you, Sho!
He's not going to hear you.
I was listening to him
talking to the store clerk
and it sounded like
he's a regular customer!
What?! Then let's all
go together next time!
Even if we have to skip class!
What about you, Shiori?
Huh? Of course!
And it seems like other celebrities
go there pretty often, too.
So it's famous among
certain groups of fans.
Why do you look at me like that?
If you want friends,
you could go find someone else.
Hey, hey, have you decided
who you want in your school trip group?
What's wrong with us sticking together?
We can just stick together.
Right.
I won't forgive you.
I'll never forgive you.
How's school? Are you working hard?
Of course, she's working hard.
After all, she was able to
transfer in to her dream school.
Right, Minami?
Y-Yeah.
That reminds me, Shiori hasn't
come by to hang out lately.
I wonder what's the matter.
She says she's busy.
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
Shiori Akasaka
"Send"
You seem to get more
and more of them every day.
I guess so.
Don't they have anyone they
can go talk to or something?
Like friends...
I guess not.
"Friends"
Who are you?
You summoned me, remember?
I am Ai Enma.
You're Hell Girl, aren't you?! You came!
Thank you!
Take it.
O-Okay.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
All right.
You should think this through carefully.
I have thought about it.
I thought about it a lot and
I decided this was the only way!
Once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
Though, that's only after you die.
But...
My life right now is Hell anyway!
If I'm going to do this, I'll do it
in front of her eyes instead of here.
What kind of look will she have
on her face when she's sent to Hell?
It'll be a sight to see.
"Private Kazanami Campus
High School, Middle School,
Elementary School, Kindergarten"
"Private Kazanami Campus
High School, Middle School,
Elementary School, Kindergarten"
Morning!
The hairstylist there is so cool!
I'm thinking about going there
on a regular basis.
What's that smirk on her face?
It gives me the creeps.
Shiori, I guess it'll be goodbye
when school lets out today.
A lot has happened up until now, but...
Hey, hey, what's the
transfer student like?
Here she comes!
"Middle School
Transfer Exam
Hall"
Hi!
Are you enrolling in
the middle school here?
What?
I'm Shiori Akasaka and
I'm in the elementary division.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, um, I'm...
I guess we'll be in the
same grade starting in April.
I'm Minami Shibuya.
See? Isn't this band great?
Yeah, but I've never heard of this band.
Not here. But over there,
they're incredibly popular!
And their lyrics are really great, too!
It's English. I can't understand it.
I'll translate it for you sometime.
I thought we were great friends,
until that happened...
"Faculty Room"
Please excuse me.
I'm sorry for being late, Shiori.
You're a lifesaver!
The other subjects are fine,
but English has me worried...
What is it?
I'm sorry, Minami. I can't
walk home with you today.
I-I see.
Your English is what they
call "Queen's English", right?
Yup.
Your house is big, right?
I can't wait to see it!
It's not that big a deal.
"Contacting Center
OK"
"There are no new e-mails.
"Enter Text Shiori
Why won't you respond (T_T)
Text OK Features"
Girls' PE will be assembling in the gym!
PE is such a drag.
And the teacher's so stuffy.
She's looking at me again.
Do you want to make me suffer that much?
Just like that time.
That's stalking!
"E-mails Received
Next Sunday
English Homework"
That's stalking!
"E-mails Received
Next Sunday
English Homework"
It is?
"Ebisu's class is so...
Today's Class"
It is?
"Ebisu's class is so...
Today's Class"
It is!
"Just Earlier
What are you doing now?"
It is!
"Just Earlier
What are you doing now?"
She e-mails you every 30 minutes, right?
"That reminds me...
About Tomorrow"
She e-mails you every 30 minutes, right?
"You know...
Next Time
Tomorrow at Lunch"
She e-mails you every 30 minutes, right?
"You know...
Next Time
Tomorrow at Lunch"
Without a doubt!
"You know...
Next Time
Tomorrow at Lunch"
She's definitely a stalker!
What? What do you think I should do?
Go talk to the teacher.
Oh, right.
I'll do that.
I see.
All right, I'll talk to Shibuya
and tell her to stop.
I'd appreciate that, Mr. Ebisu.
"Faculty Room"
Please excuse me.
Then, how about next Sunday...
Hey, Shiori...
I want to talk to you about something.
Sorry, I don't.
What are you doing?
Shiori, you've got the wrong idea.
I'm not really...
Let go!
Shiori!
Are you okay, Shiori?
Yeah, but...
Oh, man! Wax stains
don't come out, you know!
Shiori, I really...
What are you trying to do to Akasaka?
Sheesh! This is the
problem with stalkers.
I'll take care of you!
I'm not a stalker!
Shiori, I want you to believe that,
even if no one else does!
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't make me suffer any more
than you already have!
-Here we go!
-Pass! Pass!
If everyone wants to ignore me,
then that's fine.
-Rebound!
-Over here! Rebound, rebound, rebound!
I'm used to it now.
Shiori, you will pay
for doing that to me.
Just quit it already!
Hey, nice shot!
Don't look at me like that...
-Shiori!
-What?!
Are you okay?!
Y-Yeah...
-Why don't you go to the nurse's office?
-Okay.
"Nurse's Office"
Thank you very much.
Come to think of it,
I wonder what that thing was.
What the?
What is this?
Does she plan to curse me
to death with this?!
Is my sprained finger
because of a curse, too?
This is so stupid!
If that's how you want to play this,
then I can play, too!
It's not here! It's not here!
It's not here!
If we don't hurry,
the co-op's going to get busy.
Right.
Where did it go?
Accepted.
Um, by the way...
Would you care for more coffee?
Oh, no, thank you.
Um...
Could I get you to sign this receipt?
And a note stating that you
won't publicize this incident...
Huh?
Oh, well, as insurance, just in case.
Well, I don't mind.
Though, I doubt you'll
have much use for it.
Please do.
What's wrong?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Oh, please make sure to pick up the tab.
Looks like I've lost her.
Stalker! Stalker! Stalker!
Minami, you're the one
who's going to be cursed!
Good grief.
Talk about bad luck for Wanyuudou.
No kidding.
She might've come to the shrine
(This is a traditional
way of to curse someone to death.)
To lay a curse in the hour of the Ox,
(This is a traditional
way of to curse someone to death.)
But she used a normal nail
instead of a spike.
(This is a traditional
way of to curse someone to death.)
I guess kids these days don't
even know the proper protocol.
I feel sorry for you,
so I'll pull it out for you.
Much appreciated.
Wait.
What?
What is it, Miss?
Aren't we going to retrieve him?
No, let's leave things
the way they are for a while.
What?
But that girl Minami...
What'll she do now that
she's lost her black straw doll?
Minami's got a cold?
Yes, she said she's not
going to school today.
Maybe this is a message from God.
Maybe this is a divine message
telling me to stop seeking revenge.
Is this the effect of the curse?
If it is, then that straw doll's amazing!
But she couldn't possibly be dead, right?
No, there's no reason
for me to let it bother me.
After all, she's the one who started it.
"July 12
School Trip
Day 1"
"July 12
School Trip
Day 1"
So that's the schedule.
"July 12
School Trip
Day 1"
Everyone split up into groups of three.
Oh, Shiori, what are
you doing over here?
We're full already.
What? But we said we'd be together...
The other day...
What? Didn't we tell you?
That we'd be teaming up with Ueno?
-Right?!
What?!
"E-mails Received
I want to see you...
Shiori"
"E-mails Received
I want to see you...
Shiori"
"I want to see you..."
Wh-What's going on?
"I'm really sorry about everything
from before... So, be my friend again.
Shiori"
"I'm really sorry about everything
from before... So, be my friend again.
Shiori"
"I'm really sorry
"I'm really sorry about everything
from before... So, be my friend again.
Shiori"
about everything from before...
So, be my friend again."
Shiori!
I'm sorry, too, Shiori!
I must have been crazy!
Thinking of trying to send you to Hell!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Shiori...
They're all mean.
Just when I needed them,
they left me out in the cold.
I was being tricked...
I was being tricked.
I see...
Minami...
You're my only real friend, Minami.
Forgive me for the way I've been.
Be my friend again.
Okay.
Really? You're really sure it's okay?!
I'm sure.
Oh, this is...
Why do you have this?
I'm sorry, Minami.
This is...
It's okay.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Minami!
Shiori...
My, my, are they making up?
That was an unexpected conclusion,
wasn't it, Miss?
Don't you want to
see this through to the end?
I wonder if she hates happy endings.
Let's use this.
For what?
To curse everyone in the class.
What? Oh, but this isn't
an ordinary straw doll.
What do you mean?
Rather than nailing it,
you pull this red thread.
Then your target goes to Hell...
Oh, no, um...
Oh, then...
Wait!
Why?
The person who pulls it...
well, has to be me.
Then, here.
What?
Do it!
But...
I said, do it!
Do it!
I'm asking you to do it, so do it!
I've found her! It's that girl!
Come on, do it!
Th-The thing is...
With this, the one who does it
goes to Hell after she dies, too...
What?
So, I can't...
So?
So what?
So... So...
I... I can't...
Say, we're friends, right?
Or am I wrong?
Y-Yeah...
We're real friends, right?
Yeah...
If you're a real friend,
you'll do it for me, right?
Or aren't you my real friend?
I-I'm your friend...
Then...
Then!
Tell me, Shiori, are we really friends?
Your grievance has been heard.
Wha?!
Minami! Minami!
Minami, where are you?!
What is this place?!
No!
I-It's not... It's not my fault...
It is your fault.
No...
This is the world of hatred
that you wished for.
It is?
Maybe it is.
Maybe that's true.
But it was Shiori's fault.
Just because she's my friend
doesn't mean she had the right.
Consider my feelings, too...
You...
Where did that girl,
who was with you, go?
Probably Hell.
What?
But it's okay.
Because I'll be going there someday, too.
Be my friend over there, too, Shiori.
"Minami Shibuya"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
ltsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Masaya Kataoka.
You were used?
The truth, my ass!
Freedom of the press, my ass!
My family lost everything
because of those things!
It's unforgivable!
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Broken Threads"
Next time, "Broken Threads".
"Hell Girl
Broken Threads"