It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are helpless
to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
All right, let's do this!
Hanagasa!
Those are scouts for the pros, right?
Yeah.
They're not the same people
who were here the other day.
That's what you'd expect
with the right arm in high school
that every pro team is watching.
But still...
I sure envy him.
Hanagasa!
"Tarnished Mound"
M-Muroi!
Y-You okay?
Y-Yeah...
You guys went to the
same middle school, right?
Uh, yes...
Then you know where Muroi lives, right?
Walk him home.
B-But...
Please, Iwashita.
O-Okay.
I'm sure you know already,
but you were messing around
and he fell from the embankment, got it?
What's that supposed to mean?!
I know.
Hey!
Please, Iwashita. Please...
Well, I'm counting on you.
I'm sorry, Iwashita.
I don't mind, but shouldn't
we tell a teacher the truth?
And what'll that get us?
If this became publicly known,
we'd be barred from
the tournament just for that.
I'm sure everyone else feels the same,
but I want to be in the tournament, too.
And if we're gonna do it,
I'd want to go to Nationals.
I hate to admit it, but to do that,
I guess we need him.
Exactly.
Well, I just have to grin and bear it,
and everything'll be fine.
But why did he hit you?
I dunno.
He's probably stressed out
from all the scrutiny.
What a disappointment.
"The right arm in high school
that every pro team is watching," my ass.
Now, now...
"Muroi"
-Owowow...
-My goodness...
Honestly, what happened?
Shoving him off an embankment?
We were messing around
and I just ended up pushing him...
You took it too far.
Really, be careful, okay?
I'm really sorry about this.
That was the last time I saw Muroi.
Muroi was absent from school
the next day and the day after that.
And the morning after that...
I have a sad announcement to make.
Kouichi Muroi of Year 1,
Class C has passed away.
I heard it was a ruptured internal organ!
What did he do?
Maybe someone punched him.
Let us have a minute of silence
in memory of Muroi.
What's this about?
Don't give me that "what's this about" line!
Muroi's dead!
So it seems.
Wha?!
It's your fault!
My fault?
You have some proof to back that up?
P-Proof?
There's nothing...
Of course, you don't.
Shouldn't you be worrying
about yourself instead?
Wha...I-Is this for real?
Hell Link?
Yeah, if you access the site at midnight...
...Hell Girl will come to
avenge your grievance!
That's scary! Stop it!
"Baseball"
"School Staff"
Iwashita!
Coach...
These are detectives.
They say they want to ask you
about Muroi's cause of death.
I-I...uh...
We were told you shoved him off
an embankment, but is that true?
The thing is, according
to the coroner's examination,
he could only sustain those injuries
if he were hit with a bat or something.
No...
Is that true, Iwashita?!
Oh, man!
If that's true, we can kiss
the tournament goodbye.
Y-You're wrong...I...
Murderer!
It's your fault!
It's your fault that Shinichi...
Do you know how much Shinichi suffered?
He was saying, "It hurts! It hurts!"
Right up until he died!
Writhing in his bed...
And yet, he...
He kept saying it wasn't your fault,
it wasn't your fault...
Why?
That's...
Give him back! Give Shinichi back!
Sister, calm down.
-Give him back!
-That's...That's...
...because he...
Muroi, I promise you.
If I make it to the pros,
I'll play extra hard in your memory.
Impressive.
Yeah. Admirable.
Hanagasa...
You bastard!
Dad?!
Listen to me!
Everyone's got the wrong idea about me...
You idiot!
I-I really do not know what I should say...
I know it was unforgivable,
but please...please...
Go home! Just go home!
We'll go home.
We'll go home for today,
but we will return at a later date
to offer our apology.
We are truly sorry!
An apology won't come cheap.
Tens of millions...
No, hundreds of millions...
N-No way...
What...should I do?
In any case...Please, believe me!
It wasn't me!
Anyway, let's go somewhere else and talk.
Hold it, Iwashita!
"Muroi"
"Matching Sites (1 out of
Hell Link
Your grievance shall be"
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
That rumor was true...
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
"Mamoru Hanagasa"
"Send"
Do you not want to go?
It's okay, Grandma.
It can't be helped, after all.
You have no choice, but to do it.
What's with that site?
I haven't been able to get to it since...
H-How long have you been there?
You summoned me, remember?
I am Ai Emma.
Hell Girl?!
So it was true...
Take it.
O-Okay.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
O-Okay.
However,
Once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay the price
for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
you, too, will go to Hell.
Well, that's only after you die, though.
But no...
Even then...
Huh?
Wh-Where'd she go?
Was it a dream?
All that remains is for you to decide.
Okay, okay, okay!
They can't be in the tournament,
so why's the baseball team practicing?
But the official notice
hasn't come yet, right?
But talk about a bad break.
I've always thought this, but isn't
collective responsibility messed up?
I'm so sorry for you, Hanagasa.
I was looking forward to watching you
in the tournament.
You, there. Don't stand so far away.
Come over here.
What? That girl...
Huh? What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Okay, I'm here. Come on out.
Hanagasa...
Please, won't you take responsibility
for what you did?
It's too much for me to bear.
And? You thought I'd go, "Okay, I'll do it"?
If you won't say it...
If you don't, I have some ideas of my own...
Like tell them the truth?
But you already tried that last night.
Not that anyone seemed
to believe you, though.
Don't you think anything
of the fact that Muroi died?!
I do feel sorry for him.
But I never thought he'd wind up dead.
Talk about being too soft.
I guess he was never suited
for baseball to begin with.
That isn't funny!
Hold on. I don't care if you hit me,
but that'll be like
acknowledging your own guilt.
Also, don't think you'll
get away scot-free if you injure me.
If you hurt my dominant arm or something,
it'll be a huge deal.
Between that and reparations for Muroi,
your family would go bankrupt.
Wh-What am I supposed to do?
What happens to you isn't my problem.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm actually grateful to you and Muroi.
Thanks to you guys, I don't have
to participate in the tournament.
The team might've wanted to go
for the sake of a memorable youth,
but wearing out my shoulder
for something like that...
The scouts said it'd be better
if didn't have to play, too.
B-Bastard! Don't tell me it was on purpose?
And what are you going to do
if it was on purpose?
Are we done here?
Muroi...
Suffered...in pain...
He did?
Of course, he did!
Well, I didn't see him.
Are we done already?
We're done, right? Later.
But you'd better turn yourself in
to the police soon.
Or it'll make a bad impression
during your trial.
Your grievance has been heard.
Ai, I'll leave your under-kimono here.
Thank you, Grandma.
For our part, we plan to designate you
as our number one draft.
We intend to contract you
for at least a hundred million.
Thank you very much.
See you.
All right!
Hanagasa! Hanagasa!
Hanagasa! Hanagasa! Hanagasa!
Murderer! Murderer! Murderer! Murderer!
"Mamoru Hanagasa's Grave"
Wh-What's going on?!
What is this?!
Time out!
One more strike out
and you'll have a perfect game.
Hey, what is this?
Don't worry about it.
Is this a human...
Anyway, just one more strike out.
What's wrong? Don't you know
what a strike out is?
If that's the case, it means "to kill".
Muroi's out! Iwashita's out!
Hanagasa's out!
What kind of joke is this?
Up at bat is Iwashita.
Iwashita...
I get it. So this is your doing.
Give it up already!
Okay, that's the game.
What're you doing?!
It wasn't my fault.
I don't want to hear your excuses.
If you lose...
Enough with the practical jokes!
This is no practical joke.
Baseball is a serious
game of life and death.
Now, continue the game.
Damn it!
Like hell I'm letting you score!
Die!
Wha...
Safe!
My dominant arm!
Feel like acknowledging your guilt yet?
What did I do?!
You killed one and
framed another for it, remember?
Don't you feel bad about
what you did to those two?
What happens to those guys
isn't my problem!
Just because you've got
some skill at baseball,
you think you're special
and you can get away with anything...
Talk about conceited.
Haven't you people read the papers?
My talent isn't just "some skill".
They say someone with my gift
only comes along once in a decade!
If I were to become
unable to play baseball,
what a loss it'd be for pro baseball
in Japan...no, the world.
Don't you get that?
You guys understand, right?
The same goes for Iwashita and Muroi, too.
You should be happy to die for my sake.
So he says, Miss.
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Wh-What now?!
Answer me!
I joined the team because
I wanted to play baseball, you know.
Sure, unlike you, it might
be impossible for me to go pro,
but I wanted to keep playing,
even if it was just amateur baseball.
But I can't play baseball anymore, can I?
If you want to play that badly,
go play on your own!
Really? Then let's play together, Hanagasa.
Play by yourself! Leave me out of it!
Oh? Don't you know? You can't
play baseball by yourself.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
-Morning!
They say "Youth A",
but it's totally obvious, you know?
If it's a baseball ace
that even the pros were watching...
Well, his face was all over
the newspapers and TV,
and that's why the witness was able to say
the guy hitting the junior players
with a bat was Hanagasa.
But I wonder where he disappeared to.
I've asked your aunt,
so if you run into any problems,
don't hesitate to call.
Okay.
"Muroi"
If you could come back home
once in a while...
When things settle down...
Though, I think that'll be a while.
"Daisuke Iwashita"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction
and any similarities between
the names of characters or organizations
in this story and actual names
are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Junko Kanno.
You were deceived?
I trusted that doctor.
Animals can't talk.
And knowing that,
he treated them like that.
It's unforgivable.
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Silent Cries"
Next time, "Silent Cries".
"Hell Girl
Silent Cries"