It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
"Little lost, little lost kitty cat"
"Where is your home?"
"Hell Link"
Hurry! Hurry up!
"Internet"
"No sponsored sites.
Matching Sites (1 out of 1)
Hell Link
Your grievance shall be avenged."
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
H-Help me!
Help me, please!
"The Man Stalking Me
Send"
Ai. Ai.
You have a message, Ai.
Okay. I'll be right there, Grandma.
I'll be right there.
"The Possessed Girl"
"May 250:35
Private"
This is the Takamuras.
"May 250:35
Private"
We are not here right now.
"May 250:35
Private"
Please leave a message.
"May 250:35
Private"
"Little lost, little lost kitty cat"
"Where is your home?"
Bastard! That's enough already!
It's okay, Ryoko!
Hey! You show up again and I'll kill you!
I can't take this anymore!
It's okay, Ryoko!
Mom and Dad will protect you!
Mom!
Ryoko...
"Your message was received.
Hell Girl"
Hell...Girl...
"Traffic Safety Campaign
Going On Now
Tarukawa Police"
How long do you plan
to leave this man at large?!
Mr. Takamura, please calm down.
That man has been stalking
my daughter for a whole year now!
Why haven't you arrested him?!
We have increased the patrols
around your home.
We just need a little more...
How much proof do you think
I've handed over to you people?!
And yet, you don't even know his name?!
What the hell is that about?!
So, as I said...
Hey, sorry for being late.
Mr. Kisaragi, what's going on here?
He showed up again yesterday!
Yeah, I'm sorry.
We're doing the best we can...
Akimoto, sorry, but could you
go buy me some coffee?
What?
I just got off the night shift
and I can barely keep my eyes open.
I understand!
We've pretty much narrowed down
who the suspect is.
What?
I'm sorry it's taken so long.
But in all honesty, the situation
calls for acting with prudence.
Meaning?
That detective?!
With a member of the police force
involved in the crime,
it makes things quite difficult.
In particular, that Akimoto's
the son of an influential family,
so if we handle this clumsily,
it'll all get covered up.
So it was a detective...
We will arrest him!
But given this situation,
we must move carefully.
Please have patience for just
a while longer until we have solid proof.
But Mr. Kisaragi, my daughter
is at a breaking point!
-Any more and...
-Mr. Takamura!
I understand.
Please act like you know
none of this when Akimoto gets back.
Avoid behaving oddly at all costs.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Sorry for the wait!
Here you are, Captain.
Your usual black was okay, right?
Yeah. Thank you, Akimoto.
I put it on your tab.
You owe me three cups' worth now.
Oh, sorry about that.
Hurry up and come save me!
"You have mail."
"I love you,
Ryoko"
Ryoko?!
What's wrong, Ryoko?!
-Ryoko!
-Nooo!
I'll pick you after school.
Okay. Thanks, Dad.
Don't worry. I'm with you.
I'm sorry.
Silly! There's nothing
for you to apologize for.
Right.
Takamura?
You're Ryoko Takamura of Year 2,
Class A, right?
Yes...
Would you mind coming with me?
What?
"Science Room"
Um...
Here, go on in.
Come on.
Oh, wait!
You're here.
You summoned me, remember?
What?
I am Ai Emma.
Hell Girl?!
Do you finally understand now?
You came!
Because you summoned me.
Thank goodness!
At last, it'll be over.
Has this past year been that hard?
It began with love letters.
I found them in the mailbox every day.
And then they turned into weird gifts.
Weird?
That's fantastic.
He was trying to get your attention.
It's pretty sick, though.
And then?
I started getting phone calls
and e-mails, too.
I changed my e-mail address
many times, but it was no use.
Quite the resourceful guy.
After that, he would follow me
practically every day.
And finally, I don't know how he got in,
but he let himself into my room
"Today, I found this lovely dress in town.
I just know you'll look good in it."
But he let himself into my room
"Today, I found this lovely dress in town.
I just know you'll look good in it."
While we were out and...
"Today, I found this lovely dress in town.
I just know you'll look good in it."
It was no use, no matter
how many times we changed the locks.
I can't take it anymore!
Even worse, I can't stand to watch
what it's doing to my mom and dad!
Wanyuudou.
Yes, Miss.
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie the red thread around his neck.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance
will immediately be banished to Hell.
To Hell?!
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay the price
for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
you, too, will go to Hell.
We're talking about after you die, though.
You'll never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
No, stop it!
No! Nooo!
What?
All that remains is for you to decide.
That bastard!
Hell...
You'll never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
Why you!
Wha?!
H-He's dead?!
Sorry for being late, Dad!
Welcome back.
Detective Kisaragi?!
We figured out who your stalker is.
Really?!
Yeah, we're going to
go arrest him right now.
"He asks her where her home is,
but she doesn't know"
"He asks her what her name is,
"Meow, meow, meow-meow,
meow, meow, meow-meow"
"All she does is cry,
the little kitty cat"
"The policeman dog doesn't
know what to do and goes..."
"Woof, woof, woof-woof,
woof, woof, woof-woof"
Stop it!
Don't yell. Please don't
scowl at me like that, Ryoko.
You've got no right to
talk to me like you know me!
What are you saying?
This is you and me.
We've even exchanged gifts.
You're the one who just
kept sending them to me!
Finding those flowers was tough, you know.
If you hadn't been talking to
your friends and said you wanted them,
I wouldn't have had to go to such trouble.
What?
And that doll, and those insects,
and that lovely dress...
Oh, yes, and that dead hamster
I sent you on your birthday.
What are you talking about?
Love is about devoting yourself, isn't it?
I really came to understand
that with this relationship.
So why?
I love you so much!
What are you unhappy with?!
No! Why?! Why are you doing this?!
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't
have had to suffer like this!
What did you say?
What's there to suffer?!
What part of my love is making you suffer?!
Just stop it!
Ryoko, what part of it
is making you suffer?!
...you, too, will go to Hell.
I'm going to ask you one last time, Ryoko.
What part of me is making you suffer?!
Well?! What is it?!
-Answer me, Ryoko!
-Nooo!
...to Hell.
Ryoko!
Your grievance has been heard.
Hey, what are you doing in there?!
Hey, hold it!
It's gone! The doll's gone?!
Are you all right, Ryoko?
The covenant has been established.
Look down at your chest.
It's the seal of the covenant.
The seal...of the covenant?
Ai, I'll leave your under-kimono here.
Thank you, Grandma.
Dad...
I won't forgive you. You betrayed me.
I'll make you regret it!
Welcome.
Damn! Lights-out time, huh?
Wha?!
Is something the matter?
Oh, you can't do this with the water.
You shouldn't leave it running.
"Youji Takamura"
Wh-Wh-What's going on?!
I'm so sorry.
-Dad!
-Dear!
No! Dear!
So he's dead.
Serves him right.
I'll send you right after
your father, Ryoko.
It's what you get for betraying me.
Bastard!
How dare you make my daughter
suffer like that?!
Why you! Take that! And that!
Well? Has it gotten
through to you a little?
She means, do you feel like
repenting for what you did?
Captain Kisaragi.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Oh-ho, is that so?
It's Ryoko's fault!
It's her fault for betraying me!
It's all her fault!
Hear that, Miss?
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Wh-Wh-Where am I?
W-Wait! Where are we going?!
Wh-Where in the world are we?!
Where are we, I wonder? Eh, Mister?
Wh-What are you doing?! Let me go!
No can do.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
"Little lost, little lost kitty cat"
"Where is your home?"
See you later!
Later! Bye!
Wanna drop by somewhere?
Yeah, let's.
Okay, as punishment,
the unsociable Ryoko
must go explore the
haunted apartment building alone!
What?! No way! I'm not going!
Then, you can take us out to eat.
I don't like that, either!
-Picky, picky!
-Hah-hah!
Well, I'll see you tomorrow!
Okay, see you tomorrow!
-Bye-bye!
-You owe us!
Oh, please!
You're late!
Sorry about that.
To make up for it, we'll go eat
wherever you want to today, Ryoko.
Hey, that's a great idea, Dear.
Hell...
"Ryoko Takamura"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction
and any similarities between the names
of characters or organizations
in this story and actual names
are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Daisuke Iwashita.
You were used?
He was my senior and a shining beacon.
I thought he was a great person, but...
I never imagined he would secretly
do something like that so callously.
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Tarnished Mound"
Next time, "Tarnished Mound".
"Hell Girl
Tarnished Mound"