It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
This is incredible!
The heavy train is slowly
floating up into the night sky!
Esper Watanabe is lifting the train
with the power of his hands,
just as he said he would!
It floats! It floats!
What a farce!
Who said that?!
Unbelievable! The subject
of a lot of recent talk!
Who?!
The good-looking psychic medium!
His name is Gilles de L'Enfer!
And he has burst onto the show!
I've come to expose your lie!
Gilles!
Wh-What's going on?
I wasn't told about this!
"Please crush him!"
Y-You can't mean that!
That's Esper Watanabe for you!
He courageously takes
on Gilles's challenge!
What?!
Wh-What the heck is this?!
Stop!
Stop this! Come on!
If you want me to stop,
acknowledge your lie.
Cut it out!
If you won't acknowledge it,
you'll go to Hell!
Please stop this!
"Hell Girl vs. Hell Boy"
What are we going to do if
the Miss finds out about this?
It'll be fine if she doesn't, right?
That's true, but...
If she finds out, you tell her
we repeatedly tried to stop you.
All right, all right.
This is the place.
What's that?
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
What's that?
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
Quit it!
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
Mr. Esper Watanabe, what's wrong?!
He is currently in a different world.
It's over the top,
even for a staged show.
You don't believe it?
Of course, not.
Oh, really.
Even though you believe in Hell Girl?
-It's a lie! It's a complete lie...
-It's coming from the TV.
-But still...
...that I have psychic powers!
-I don't think sending people to Hell...
...is the only solution there is.
-It's true! It's true that it's a lie!
-I have no psychic powers whatsoever!
-So you have to stop doing
this kind of thing.
-I have no psychic powers whatsoever!
-It's true! Please believe me!
-What was that all of a sudden?
-I really don't have any powers!
-Who knows?
-Looks like something's up.
-It's all a lie!
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
-It's all a lie!
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
Forgive me! Forgive me!
I have no psychic powers!
-It was all tricks! Forgive me!
-Well? Do you sense any
response from her?
-It was all tricks! Forgive me!
-Nope. Can we really
communicate with her?
-It's true! It's a lie!
-Nope. Can we really
communicate with her?
-Please believe me!
-I see.
-It's hot!
-Since you can see things
that Hell Girl sees,
-It's hot!
I was thinking she'd be able
to see things that you see, but...
What do they mean by communicate?
So that's what's been going on.
-Do you think she's seeing
the TV show we're watching, too?
-Stop it! Please stop it!
-I don't know.
That's enough. Let's get out of here.
I agree.
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
Just what did you do to Esper Watanabe?
"Psychic Medium Gilles de L'Enfer
Challenges Esper Watanabe!!"
I showed him a glimpse...of Hell.
What a load of crap.
No kidding. Damn bogus psychic medium.
Ms. Abe, what are we going to do with
the show starting next week?
Isn't it obvious?
We'll have that kid
take over as the star.
Well, I look forward to working
with you starting next week.
Likewise.
Oh, good work!
Shuddup!
I bet he resents you for this.
Since we've already started,
let's have him resent me more.
What?
Do you know about Hell Girl?
I've heard about it.
She smells like the real thing,
the same as me.
It could be that she
is not of this world.
I-I see, but then...
Yes. Gilles de L'Enfer
versus Hell Girl...
Wouldn't you like
to see that, Ms. Abe?
I do! I'd definitely
want to see that!
But where should I go
to get that appointment?
If it's an appointment,
let's ask Mr. Watanabe to get it.
Oh, that's true!
That's a great idea!
I'll go discuss this with
the organizer right away!
Hell Girl, don't get cocky,
just because you're
the talk of the net.
No idea.
Then, you were communicating
to her without knowing it?
Oh!
Which means, things get communicated
from you to her,
but stuff doesn't get communicated
from her to you, huh?
Thank goodness! That guy earlier...
Anyway, we can trust
you on that, right?
It made a sound!
I'm ruined!
I should never have accepted
a challenge like that!
So why am I polishing my boots?!
I'm done for!
Aw, man, I would've liked to be
a little more popular before I died.
Yes?
Oh, Mr. Watanabe?
Good work today! It's Abe.
What?!
Thank you for always calling on me!
This is Esper Watanabe! Come to me
for all your psychic power needs!
Thanks to you, the response
to today's broadcast was enormous!
We're talking about
doing a continuation.
So how about it?
Want a revenge match?
Against Gilles!
What?!
I'll do it! I'll do it!
I'll definitely do it!
No, please let me do it!
Okay, glad to hear it.
Then I'll see you
at the studio at 9pm tomorrow.
You can count on me!
This is my chance!
Just you watch, Gilles!
This time, I'll stab you in the back!
No, I'll skewer you in the back!
Goodbye!
This kind of set should be good, right?
Yes. Incidentally,
when is this being aired?
With it being so late,
we can't do a live broadcast,
but we've booked the special
programming slot for tomorrow.
And what about him?
He's coming in at 9pm.
He was awfully fired up that
he'd get revenge for yesterday.
When he finds out that was a lie,
his hatred will grow even more.
Only when we've pushed him
to that point
will he even have a chance
at contacting Hell Girl.
Right. I've told the staff members
to pull out all the stops.
Thank you for that.
By the way, I wonder
how long it takes...
...for Hell Girl to come after
you've contacted her.
Who knows?
Does she take the train?
Or maybe she'll come by car?
Good evening.
Who might you be?
So, what do you want?
Yes, well, there are some things
I'd like to ask you about.
If it's an interview,
could you please go through
our station's PR department?
Is it true that you've been to Hell?
It's true.
When was that?
When I was a child.
As I said, please go through
the PR department for an interview!
Then, do you know of Hell Girl?
What are you talking about?
We aren't doing anything...
There's a message I'd like
to pass along to Hell Girl.
I told you, we don't know anything!
What message?
What?!
"Stop this now."
"It will make no one happy."
"Revenge is meaningless,"
is my message.
Revenge is meaningless, you say?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
Do you suppose it's hypocritical?
No, I'm sure it's as you say.
But though you might
know that intellectually,
deep in your heart, you cannot
resist the urge to crush your opponent.
That is the way with people.
That may be true, but...
Then what about you?
What?
Well?
"Shibata Family Grave"
What did you do?!
That was your wife, wasn't it?
For what it's worth,
I'll convey your message.
Though, of course,
I doubt there will be a response.
Is he the real thing?
It's almost midnight! How long
are you going to make me wait?!
Well, I think it might take a while.
The filming for Gilles is taking
longer than expected.
Why is it just Gilles?!
There's no revenge if I'm not there!
-Well, that's true, but...
-It's going just as planned.
Oh, okay.
You're the only one thinking
you'll get revenge...
...and Gilles wants to fight someone
more powerful is what he's saying.
What?!
Just what is the meaning of this?!
-Now should be a good time...
-Well, so like,
-that's just what Gilles is saying.
-Yes, shall we get him a snack?
-That's just what Gilles is saying.
Mr. Watanabe, you must be hungry.
-Stop it! Stop it!
-Here you are!
-A little snack from Gilles for you!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
You're going to give me burns!
Damn that Gilles de L'Enfer!
Just how much does he have to mock
me before he's satisfied?!
I'll sue him later for sure!
A computer?
Hell Link?
It's hard to say if
it's the Miss's fault...
...or if it's the fault
of that guy's daughter...
Keep your voice down.
Anyway, I don't think...
...the possibilities are
necessarily limited to either or.
What do you mean?
Maybe there's some kind of
connection between the two of them.
We have a request.
Come with me.
Wh-Who are you?
You summoned me, remember?
I am Ai Enma.
Ai...
You're really pretty.
Take it.
What?
Okay...
What am I supposed to do with this?
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will enter
into a covenant with me.
This will, huh?
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
Then let me get right to it!
However, once you have
your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
What?
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
What?!
That's only after you die, though.
Are you scared?
Y-Yeah...
Of course, he's scared!
What the-?! What the-?!
Gag!
What the heck is this?!
I wasn't told about this!
Welcome! I am happy to make your
acquaintance, Ai Enma!
Whoa! You!
And you are?
I am Gilles de L'Enfer!
It means "Gilles of Hell!"
I am honored that the real Hell Girl
has come to join me here.
Gilles, how dare you use me like this?!
Good work.
Hot! Hot, hot! Hot, hot!
Daikon radish is a great garnish
for a ham like you!
Now, allow me to explain
the plan for today.
Right now, I am the most
talked about person on TV...
...and you are the most talked
about person on the net,
and the idea is to have a
life-and-death Hell showdown...
...and bring it to people's living rooms!
That's the show!
So we fell right into their trap.
There's no way you'll
win against the Miss.
How promising.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
Hold on a second, Gilles!
Just who are you talking to?!
We can't have a show like this!
What are you talking about?!
They're right here!
Huh? What?
Gag!
What the-?!
Hey, what's going on over there?!
What is this?
How am I going to explain a show that
makes no sense to the higher-ups?
You're a great help.
Now, you two go as well!
Damn it!
It's no use.
You guys won't be able to get loose.
Finally, it's just the two of us.
Oh, yes, I have a message for you
from a reporter named Shibata.
He says revenge isn't good.
He was giving himself
an awfully righteous air.
Considering how
pretentious he was,
he should be writing
about Hell instead,
where those who have committed evil
deeds reside after being condemned.
But well, I suppose it would
be impossible for him.
Unlike me, he wouldn't be able
to come back from Hell.
That's right.
I was born with psychic powers.
When my parents realized that,
they killed me out of fear.
But I came back from Hell.
And then...
The first thing I did
after I came back...
...was to send my own
parents to Hell.
Wh-What's this?!
Being young, I had more power
than I could manage...
...and I was causing chaos around me,
so maybe there was no helping it.
If I had been a little older,
perhaps I could have understood
what my parents did.
But I still would have done it.
The perfect murder with absolutely
no evidence left behind.
The massacre of my entire family.
I don't intend to justify my revenge.
But even so, my powers have brought
me nothing but suffering.
You can understand me, can't you?
A-Ai...
The only time I send others to Hell...
...is when I can't control my own
feelings because of my hatred.
You understand that, don't you?
You do, don't you?
Say something.
Say it!
Watch out, Ai!
Miss!
Can't you do something, Wanyuudou?!
This fight would be ours,
if only the thread were untied.
You apparently send villains to Hell
for the sake of others,
but ultimately, that's hypocrisy!
You have all of that power,
so why don't you try
to use it for yourself?!
Your clothes are in tatters.
I couldn't bring myself
to send you to Hell like this.
I'll change you into
a new set of clothes.
It looks good on you.
It looks very good on you.
Now, it's time to say goodbye.
So long!
Ai!
You all can hold a memorial
in her honor!
Ai...
Ai?!
What?!
You're all right?
Why did you let him
do whatever he wanted?
I was thinking.
This can't be possible!
Now, Miss, get back at him
for all you're worth!
The thread hasn't been untied.
But at this rate,
you must feel frustrated, too!
What I feel doesn't matter.
Let's go home.
You mean to go home after
the beating you got?!
Then I'll untie it!
I-I-I'll untie it!
If you untie it,
you'll be going to Hell, too.
If I don't untie the thread now,
you'll do me in someday!
There's no way you'll forgive
me for asking for revenge!
I'll forgive you. Really.
You're lying!
Hell is far more terrifying
than you can imagine.
You could never endure it.
Don't mock me!
Behold the pride of a hammy actor!
Your grievance has been heard.
Stop!
Stop this!
Father...Mother...
Teacher...
Make them stop their revenge!
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
You mean "again," right?
Hell again, huh?
I'll concede victory to you this time.
But no matter how many times
I'm sent to Hell,
I will come back to life
and settle this match!
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Oh, man...
Looks like I managed to survive somehow.
Ai, you have a request.
All right.
"Hiroshi Watanabe"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Yuko Murai.
You hate him?
My father trusted him.
He really relied on him
for emotional support...
And yet, from the start, that man...
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
Next time, "Kind Neighbor."
"Hell Girl
Kind Neighbor"
Next time, "Kind Neighbor."
"Hell Girl
Kind Neighbor"