It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
So? Have you made any friends?
Yup! I've made lots!
Mother, I'll help you
make the pot stickers.
Oh? Can you do it?
Sure, I can!
"Okame Express"
Mother!
Oh, right.
"Early Afternoon Window"
Mother, what's wrong?
You're all spaced out.
Oh, it's nothing.
Come on, we better hurry
or your father will be home.
Coming!
"Okame Express"
These are from Mrs. Todaka.
She said not to talk.
That if you talk,
it'll be terrible for you.
You really love cherries, don't you, Ai?
Why did you throw them away?
Hey, Mother?
Never you mind!
Just finish what you're doing!
Oh, Mrs. Yasuda, morning.
Good morning.
Did you enjoy those cherries?
Yes, thank you.
So?
What?
Goodness! I'm only asking how they were!
They were quite delicious, thank you.
Really. I imagine it was the
perfect refresher for pot stickers.
How did you know that?
Your residence smelled
a little last night, so...
You have to be careful when
you use garlic, Mrs. Yasuda.
This is a far cry from your provincial
standalone homes on spacious lots.
In a sense, we are in a
communal living arrangement here.
Now, now, you two,
why don't you leave it at that?
Mrs. Yasuda is just
out of the country, after all.
Mrs. Yasuda, I believe...
...your daughter transferred into
the same class as my girl, right?
See you later, Mom!
Be careful on your way now!
I will!
I hope we can become good friends as well.
Mrs. Yasuda, you should be careful.
It's all over if you incur
Mrs. Todaka's displeasure now.
Neither you nor your husband
will find it livable here.
After all, she's the lady behind
the autocratic branch manager.
Doesn't something stink here?
Totally!
It stinks of pot stickers!
Pot stickers? Isn't that kind of bad?
That's super bad!
I wonder if I did something
to Yuria Todaka...
Why?
She made fun of me,
saying I stank of pot stickers.
Hey, open the door!
Oh, it's Father.
Damn it!
What are you so worked up about?
Hell if I know!
I received a summons from the
branch manager out of the blue
and the next thing I knew, he was
making outrageous accusations.
What did I ever do?!
You'd better not have done
something to incur his wife's wrath.
What's that supposed to mean?
She's the one in the wrong anyway.
Whoa, whoa, you mean you
really did do something?!
Give me a break, okay?
Hold on! I didn't do anything!
I only saw her having an af...
Please don't stir up any trouble!
Of all the people, I need to
get along with that branch manager!
What? Introduce a friend to me?
Yes, he's an incredibly marvelous boy.
Marvelous?
You understand, don't you?
-You should enjoy yourself, too.
-What?
At any rate, I'm going to
send him over straight away.
I'll make you sorry if you
pretend not to be home.
Bye.
Ma'am?! You're home, right?!
Open the door, Ma'am!
I came all this way
because you asked me to!
Yo! Let me in!
Come on!
-Please stop! The neighbors will hear you!
-Hey, hurry up and open the door!
Hey, do you hear me?!
-No... Go away...
-Hey! Open up!
Go away, please...
Say, I don't think you should be
taking your time getting home.
It looks like there's
trouble at your place.
Some young guy apparently
barged in and caused some trouble.
What?
I hear your mother's been
having one affair after another.
It's gotta suck. Having a parent
that's having an affair.
Stop that, you two.
Ow!
I feel so sorry for the daughter.
Mother?!
Mother, hang on!
Why?! Why did it come to this?!
It's all over.
Once she has it in for you here, it's over.
Why me?
It's Mrs. Todaka who's in the wrong...
Mrs. Todaka?!
What in the world happened?!
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
"Your grievance shall be avenged."
Happy birthday, Yuria.
Wow! Thank you, Dad!
My, isn't that nice?
What about for me?
Your birthday is still a ways off.
Don't age on me so fast.
My, how rude!
Them...
Because of them...
Don't be scared.
You summoned me, after all.
Then, you're...
Ai Enma.
Hell Girl...
I want to know what happened
between Mrs. Todaka and my mother.
What will you do once you know?
Once I know, I'll get back at them.
Or else, my mother...
I don't want to see my mother suffering.
I cannot save your mother.
All I can do is simply avenge her.
Avenge... her...
Yes.
Take it.
What?
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
You will enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
Do you still want retribution?
Yes.
All right. I'll show you.
This is...
Yes, the place where it all began.
And...
Look, here you come.
Us?!
This is that day...
Sure, I can!
I got some great shots.
If you don't want these
to be spread around,
you'd better not go telling
unnecessary stories.
If you ever do talk... Let's see...
How about we have your daughter
play a starring role next time?
What? For real?!
Stop it...
Please just stop it!
It seems your mother was unlucky
and saw something she needn't see.
Don't just say she was unlucky,
like it's that simple!
It's Yuria's mom who's in the wrong!
So why does my mother have
to be the one being tormented?!
I can't accept that!
Yes...
But that is what I am here for.
Mother's home!
What have you done?!
You've destroyed my position!
And the rumor's going
around the company, too!
That you're entertaining young men!
That's not true! That's all Mrs. Todaka...
Shut up! Don't say any more than that!
Why won't you believe me?
No, you won't even listen
to what I have to say!
Always, always... All you
care about is your work!
How dare you!
I swear! Who do you think
you owe this lifestyle to?!
My family is in a shambles.
It's her...
Yes...
It's because of that woman...
Your grievance has been heard.
Yes? Who is it?
Delivery for you, Ma'am.
Oh, my.
D-Dear...
What is the meaning of this?!
Y-You're wrong! This isn't what you think!
Th-This man forced his way in
and I had no choice...
Don't lie to me!
You invited that man in, didn't you?!
Please believe me! I'm the victim here!
Why you!
Th-This man really tried to force me!
Namiko!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?!
You're shameless!
Wh-What are you all doing here?!
Mother, why did you do this?
It's not true! It's not like that!
I'm going to be bullied at school now!
You're wrong!
So it was Mrs. Todaka
who was having the affairs.
You're like a bitch in heat!
What a laughingstock she'll be now.
It's not true!
Look, she's got a great body for her age.
What in the world is this?
What the hell is the deal with you people?!
All of you, just go away!
Who the hell are you, brat?!
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Welcome to the end that the
vortex of your lust has brought you to.
As unfortunate as it is,
this place is well suited to you.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Whether what I did that day
was truly the right thing or not,
I do not know.
G-Good morning.
Oh, morning.
The whole thing with your mother
must have been difficult.
To think she would run away
with another man!
It's no way for the wife
of the branch manager to behave.
None of that now.
The child is not to blame.
Mother has begun to smile again.
That alone is enough for me.
I think I am probably happy right now.
It just might be that I'll be
happy for the rest of my life.
But someday, I know...
Yes, when my life comes to an end...
...I will face the consequences
of what I did then, on that day.
Every time I see this seal on my chest...
...I am reminded of that.
"Haruka Yasuda"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
ltsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Ayaka Kurenai.
Why do you hate her so?
She doesn't love me.
Not only that, but my future...
She's trying to crush
my prospects as an actress!
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
"Hell Girl
Cracked Mask"
Next time, "Cracked Mask".
"Hell Girl
Cracked Mask"