It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
"The little lark, who forgot his way home"
"Is amidst a vast field of wheat"
"He called out seeking his mother"
"But there is only the rustle
of wheat in the wind"
Tsugumi!
Who are you?
I am Ai Enma.
You summoned me, remember?
Hell... Girl?
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance
will immediately be banished to Hell.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
All that remains is for you to decide.
You saw something again, didn't you?
Yeah.
Who is it this time?
I don't know.
But I saw a poster.
For a circus.
A circus poster...
"A Night Among Traveling Entertainers"
"Happy Circus"
Come on over!
It's the fun Happy Circus!
Tightrope walking and beast masters!
We're here again this year!
The Happy Circus!
It's the Happy Circus that
comes just once a year!
Wow! It's a real circus!
I had no idea they still had these.
Come on, little lady.
I hope you have fun!
Hajime, hurry up!
Right.
Hey, kid, you come on over, too.
It'll be lots of fun!
It's him again.
Sheesh, how does he
get wind of these things?
Who is it?
Who accessed Hell Link?
What?
That's amazing!
You want to do a story on us?
Yes, I was so surprised, to be honest.
I had no idea a circus
like this was still around.
It's just so, I don't know, nostalgic.
Then, you came all this way
from Tokyo just to see us?
I just happened to find you
guys online and got curious.
You just happened to find us, huh?
Drop dead! I wish you'd
just drop dead already!
Never mind them.
They go through the
same thing every night.
It's like a ritual
for that married couple.
And enter the lover.
Up until last year,
that was his role, though.
Bull's-eye!
That's the world's greatest
knife thrower for you!
But don't hit me, okay?
Well, shall we start looking
around from over there?
What are you doing out here,
little girl?
I'm waiting for my father.
Your father? You must mean the reporter.
But why is he covering
a circus like this?
Don't know.
I see.
Aren't you able to
do something, ma'am?
M-Ma'am?!
I mean, you belong to the circus, right?
O-Of course, I can.
Show me! Show me!
The girl?
Yes. You know, the one that escaped
from the box she was skewered in.
Oh!
Could I meet with her for a bit?
I want to talk to her.
Talk?
It's nothing major,
but her performance was
quite impressive, so...
I won't be able to let you.
She's the troupe leader's favorite.
But, I guess you did come
all this way from Tokyo...
Come with me.
She's in there?
Wait here a minute.
So you're here to do a story on us?
You sure are an odd one.
Doing a story on a lousy circus like this!
The name itself is a mockery to begin with!
Happy Circus, my ass!
You think so, too, don't you?
You again!
Come on, get over here.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Don't touch me, Mokku!
All right, all right.
-If you want someone to talk to,
I'll keep you company.
-Hello.
-If you want someone to talk to,
I'll keep you company.
-Come on in.
-If you want someone to talk to,
I'll keep you company.
She's got quite the taste.
Come with me.
I'll help you.
So don't think of doing something
stupid like trying to get revenge.
Revenge?
You accessed Hell Link, right?
Anyway, come with me.
Stop this!
What?!
You're scared, right?
Don't worry. I'll take you someplace
where he can't get to you.
-So come with me!
-No!
Let go! Let go!
You idiot! Don't yell!
I'm trying to help you!
No! No!
This isn't good, mister.
The deal was that you
were only going to talk.
Mokku!
Okay, I think it's time you left.
Hajime!
Look! Look at this box!
We're going.
So long.
Let me out!
Hone Onna?!
-Mokku, let me out!
-What the heck are you doing?
So, it wasn't that girl?
I was sure it had to be her, too...
Anyway, let's eat.
We'll go back again later.
You messed up again!
That was because someone had
tampered with the heel...
Tsugumi?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Tsugumi!
Get a hold of yourself, Tsugumi!
That girl is being bullied!
What?
Please, save her!
That girl?
She's got scars all over her body.
She's being beaten all the time!
All the time?
But she had no such scars...
Don't tell me...
Twins?
That was the trick
behind escaping the box.
It was the other one that
hated the troupe leader.
What kind of place was the girl in?
A place like a cage...
All right, got it!
I'm coming, too!
"The little lark, who forgot his way home"
"Is amidst a vast field of wheat"
This is awful...
"He called out seeking his mother"
That's...
You untied it?
"He called out seeking his mother"
"But there is only the rustle
of wheat in the wind"
Look after her!
"But there is only the rustle
of wheat in the wind"
How does it look?
Why the hell are you here?!
I'll explain later!
Hurry up and get away from here!
Or you'll be sent to Hell!
Hell?
Never mind! Just run!
What are you doing?!
Let go! Let go of me!
"Forgetting his way home and lost"
"The lark is alone in the wheat"
Working hard, I see. Good, good!
Here's a reward for you.
Here, say, "Ah!"
Ah!
"Though no mountain fox cries out"
"After sunset is the forlorn moonlight"
I said, let go of me!
-Hurry!
-What is your problem?!
Hurry up and run!
You're not making any sense!
It can't be!
Wait!
So it was her...
Where am I?
What is this?
The circus troupe of Hell!
Looks like the star is
finally taking the stage.
We expect a lot from you.
What?
Now, ride around.
Ride around?
Come on now. If you don't hurry,
you'll be caught by those arms.
There's no way I can do this!
So you can't even do
something like that?
Then I guess there's no helping it.
S-Stop this!
Please, stop this!
Stay away!
Nooo!
I wonder how long you'll
be able to hang in there.
Please, help me!
I-I don't want to die!
Then repent to your older sister.
Poor girl.
She suffered terribly because of you.
Then, could it be that you people are...
Demeaning your older sister,
so that you would be the favorite...
What a dirty thing to do.
Repent to your older sister!
Why do I have to apologize to her?!
Because of her, I'm always
just half a person!
I want to stand on stage alone, too!
What's wrong with that?!
I haven't done anything wrong!
One of me is more than enough!
I wish she would just disappear!
So she says, Miss.
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
What is this?
Where are we going?
Stop!
I'm telling you to stop!
No! I don't want to!
I don't want to go!
-Stop! Come on, I said, stop!
-I consign this grievance to Hell...
Nooo!
I guess they're all leaving.
Yeah...
Where's Mokku?
Have you seen Mokku?
Troupe leader.
Ah, that looks good on you, Yumi.
It fits you perfectly.
She's smiling.
All right! Time to leave!
"Yumi"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
"Save me"?
That's what the girl said?
Yeah.
She's at a sanatorium shrouded in fog.
Do not go.
Turn back.
Hell Girl...
I'm going.
I won't let you banish anyone to Hell.
Do not go.
You must not go.
Hajime, I hear a music box.
"Hell Girl
Glass Scenery"
Next time, "Glass Scenery".
"Hell Girl
Glass Scenery"