It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
Tsugumi, you sure this is the place?
Yeah.
It was this hospital.
"The Light of the Hospital Ward"
A nurse that's young
and beautiful to boot, huh?
But she's the sort of person that's
going to get sent to Hell, okay?
You know,
it's not like I'm trying to prevent
her from being banished to Hell...
...because she's young
and beautiful.
Hajime, let's not do this!
It's just not good to get in
the way of the kind of person
who's backed into a corner and has
no choice but to go to Hell Girl!
You're still saying things like that?
Because...
I'm not going to condone revenge.
Not ever.
Honestly!
What's wrong, Tsugumi?
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Is it her?
Yeah.
Kanako Sakuragi, 23 years old.
Graduated from Joto Prefectural
Nursing School.
Her address is...
Good grief...
There's no way there are
any bad rumors about her!
Kanako's good to her parents
and she's a hard worker.
She went to nursing school
instead of college...
...because of her family's finances.
Um, what about a boyfriend or...
My! You've set your sights
on a nice girl!
What?
Uh, well...
But she says it'd get
in the way of her work...
...and she wouldn't have time
for him anyway,
so she says she doesn't want one.
That's too bad.
Seriously. You don't find
nice girls like her these days.
There's no way there's
a problem with her parents.
She's the way she is
because of her parents.
Then, could she have done
something to cause resentment?
No, no! There is
no way she could have!
This is utterly ridiculous.
Oh, speak of the devil...
Hello.
Ah, going to work now?
I have the night shift today.
But more importantly, Grandpa,
are you eating properly?
Quit worrying about everyone else
and worry about yourself!
I'm fine!
Well, if anything happens,
you come right to the hospital, okay?
Bye.
Well? Nice girl, isn't she?
There's nothing.
No matter who I ask, there's nothing.
Maybe the problem's inside
the hospital, after all.
I know!
Mr. Hajime Shibata...
You're staying at the hospital
for some tests?
Yes.
Do you have any symptoms
that are bothering you?
The area around the stomach
feels a little heavy...
That's certainly cause for concern.
But you'll be fine.
It's true what they say
about worry causing illness,
so rather than brooding about it,
please go into this with
a positive outlook, okay?
A-All right.
That's the spirit!
Well, then, if you have any
questions, feel free to ask me.
Kana, my stomach's
not feeling good, either!
All right, I will give you
a shot later, Mr. Yamada.
What?!
A looker, isn't she?
Wha... sure...
With an awesome personality.
I wish I could be hospitalized for life.
The old man that used
to be in that bed over there...
...said the same thing
before he died yesterday.
But being as cute as she is,
I wonder if she isn't resented
by her coworkers sometimes.
Not likely.
Nope, nope.
I don't know about that...
We're telling you,
there's just no way!
Miss Sakuragi again?
Again?
One in two male patients ask
about Miss Sakuragi, you know.
Like, "Does she have a boyfriend?"
Or, "What kind of guy does she like?"
-It's always about stuff like that.
Are you one of those, too?
Well... oh, man!
So, then,
is she maybe not very popular
among her coworkers like you girls?
Not at all!
She's good at what
she does and she's nice.
Nice, so nice. She's not
two-faced about it, either.
It's a tough job, but it's been
a real help having her around.
Really?
Really, really.
You must really like her!
Well... really, right?
There really is nothing.
Who is it?
Who the heck would want her gone?
You can't tell with people
just by looking at them, right?
There's no knowing what she
might be doing in secret.
She really doesn't have
that kind of vibe.
You're just not a good
judge of character.
What?
My, that looks delicious.
Oh...
Is she yours?
My unworthy daughter.
My! How could you say such a thing?
Hello.
Tsugumi!
Oh, no, it's all right.
Please don't worry about it.
Oh, Miss Sakuragi, if you'd like,
please have this.
Oh, please don't mind me.
Not at all. It's the least
I can do to apologize.
Really, the regulations
don't allow me to.
Tsugumi?
It's no surprise that
the reporter's at a complete loss.
Well, for once, I doubt he'll
be able to interfere this time.
But it's the Miss
that you have to feel sorry for.
Yeah...
But that's her fate...
Is it really all right
for it to be this way?
Are you uncertain, Ai?
Darkness...
You know, that was immature of you.
But I'm a kid.
Well, yeah, but...
I want to see the person in charge!
Talking to you guys
is getting me nowhere,
so I'm demanding to see
the person in charge!
"Nurse's Station"
so I'm demanding to see
the person in charge!
"Nurse's Station"
But as I said, this matter
has already been explained...
"Nurse's Station"
That was nonsense!
Mr. Higuchi, there is not a single lie
or falsehood in our explanation.
Just like we have told you many times,
your wife passed away because
there was nothing more we could do for her.
You're lying!
I know!
I talked to numerous lawyers
to try to sue this hospital!
But they barely even listened to me
before every last one turned me down!
Hey!
You guys got to them, didn't you?!
We would never do such a thing!
You listen good!
Because of the mistake you made,
Yoshiko...
Because of you...
Oh, Mr. Shibata...
Oh, well, I heard some yelling, so...
Oh, Mr. Higuchi.
Higuchi...
He lost his wife,
but he believes it was because...
...of a mistake Miss Sakuragi made
and he refuses to question his belief.
Really, talk about repaying
kindness with resentment.
I'm not forgiving you!
No matter what anyone says,
I'm never forgiving you as long as I live!
I swear, I'll send you to Hell!
That's a promise!
Yoshiko... Yoshiko...
Yoshiko...
Who are you?
I'm a freelance reporter.
"Shibata"
Would you mind telling
me about your wife's death?
There's nothing.
No matter who I ask, there's nothing.
...talk about repaying kindness
with resentment.
Tsugumi?
Tsugumi, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Tsugumi?
Tsugumi... Tsugumi...
Tsugumi...
Tsugumi?!
Tsugumi!
What's wrong?!
Tsugumi?! Tsugumi?!
Mr. Higuchi,
I investigated everything
I could regarding Yoshiko's death.
I see, and did you
find any conclusive proof?
Yes, I did.
That your assertion is nonsense.
I see.
Then, leave!
So you turn a deaf ear when the talk turns
to things you don't want to hear.
What?!
No matter how I investigated every angle,
I could find no fault with what
the hospital and Nurse Sakuragi did.
Mr. Higuchi,
this is all just in your head.
I get it, you were asked to come here,
too, weren't you?!
That hospital sure does
some underhanded things!
How much did you get?!
Or did you come to blackmail me?!
Mr. Higuchi, I do feel bad for you
that your wife passed away.
I lost my wife, too.
I understand well what it feels
to be a widower.
But trying to hurt someone
that has done no wrong...
...in an attempt to cover up
your grief is wrong.
Am I wrong?
Do you have any children?
One daughter.
I have none.
My wife was my entire life.
I never wanted much,
if we could just peacefully
grow old together,
I thought that was enough.
I doubt you could
understand that, though.
So, then, who am I supposed
to turn this feeling on?!
Mr. Higuchi...
It's that woman...
It's that woman's fault.
That woman...
Mr. Higuchi, was it you?
Were you the one who accessed
the Hell Link site?
The one who asked Hell Girl
to avenge you against Nurse Sakuragi...
Aren't you the one?!
What are you talking about?
Please do not start playing dumb now.
Access? Is that to do with
the so-called internet thing?
Sorry, but I can't make heads
or tails of that stuff.
It can't be...
Are you awake?
You seem to be doing
a lot better now...
If you're still hurting,
I'll have a pediatrician
take a look at you, though.
I'm fine.
I see. I'm glad.
Hey...
Here...
Thank you.
Yesterday...
When you were being yelled
at by that man...
I saw it.
I see.
Were you scared?
A little.
That man is a lonely person.
He suddenly lost his wife,
whom he'd been married to for a long time.
He must be unable to cope
with that pain...
So, he's not really a scary person.
Stuff like that happens
a lot at the hospital.
But if taking his anger out on me...
...serves to alleviate
his pain even a little,
I think maybe that's part
of my job, too.
Or something like that.
But you're getting sent to Hell...
What're you doing, Tsugumi?
She got sent...
What?
She got sent to Hell...
Tsugumi...
Tsugumi!
Where am I?
Why am I on a boat?
Who are you?
I am Ai Enma.
I am sending you to Hell.
Hell?!
No way!
Why?
Why am I...
What for?!
Who would do such a thing?!
It's him?!
It was him.
I don't know him.
I don't know him!
I've never even met him!
Who is he?!
Why would he do such a thing?!
No... I don't want this...
Please, help me!
Help me!
Please!
This job sure left a bad aftertaste...
But it's something that's happened
lots of times over the centuries.
Grudges come in as many shapes
as people do...
The Miss is to be commended
for carrying out her duty.
But my ears can hear it...
The Miss's heart cracking
under the strain...
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Nooo!
Why?
Why?!
Who knows who the hell this guy is
or what the hell he was thinking...
And to fall victim to a guy like that...
...is wrong.
It's absolutely wrong!
Do you still think that getting revenge
is the righteous thing to do?
Would you still defend Hell Girl?!
I don't know... I don't know...
Tsugumi...
I don't know!
Tsugumi!
Why...
Why?
There!
It's cold!
Y-You're... Hell Girl!
I... I...
I wanted you to...
You know?
What?
You know Sentaro?
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
The thread that linked
the Miss to the Shibata family...
It was an abominable bond
that reached across 400 years.
The scattered cherry blossoms
begin to impart their memories.
History erased.
In the mountains, covered in deep snow,
a deep-seated hatred pushes open
the door to the Miss's heart.
And then, the Miss...
Next time, "Home in the Twilight"
"Hell Girl
Home in the Twilight"
Next time, "Home in the Twilight"
"Hell Girl
Home in the Twilight"