It is said that life's
encounters are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
Did he really disappear?
Please, I just want to talk to her.
"Tanuma"
As I told you, my daughter
says she does not want to see you!
If you would just convince her to see me...
If you don't stop this already,
I am calling the police!
Yes? Shibata here.
Just how long are you
going to make me wait?!
What?
The photos! What happened to the photos?!
Photos?
Shibata, you!
Ah, right, I'll definitely
get it to you within the week.
Crap, I'd totally forgotten about it.
Hiromi made these?
Yes!
And this is our shop's main offering.
Sis is very confident about this creation.
Please give it a try.
What do you think?
This texture is... soybean milk skin...
It's delicious.
Really?!
That's Hiromi for you. This flavor
would be difficult to create.
Her talent will be missed.
In all honesty, I wish she would've
kept up her great work here instead.
Wow! Thank you very much!
But it's been my dream and hers
to open up our own shop, so...
As well as your father's.
Yes.
Oh, if you'd like,
please give this one a try, too.
Oh, but I think the cheese
and tofu one here is also quite good.
"Sweet Trap"
"Jul. 2 (Sat)
We will await your visit
with a collection of original creations."
It's all ready, I see!
Welcome back.
Wow! So this is the kind of kitchen
that Father had envisioned.
Thank you, Yuka.
What?
We were able to open
our own shop this quickly
thanks to you working
part-time jobs every day
and saving up for this with me.
Come on, it was a given that I did that.
After all, we decided this together.
I know, but...
I wish Father could've
made his cakes here, too.
Father...
But the crucial part is still ahead of us!
We have to rake it in and pay back
all the debt we've still got left!
Right.
And this is where I've got
great news to tell you!
Great news?
What? You went to Mr. Morisaki's place?
Yup!
When I took your cakes over,
he said he'd get this shop
on "The Corner Patisserie"!
What?!
That show is popular,
so it'll be good advertisement!
So, the shoot will be
next week on Saturday.
H-Hold on, Yuka, that's the day...
He suggested that we take
this chance to do it on opening day.
Mr. Morisaki is such a really nice person!
Oh, and he suggested we should
present the "Heritage" on that day.
He was full of praise for you, Sis!
"Amano"
The people in the neighborhood are
also extremely inconvenienced by it.
The Ward Office realizes
something must be done about it,
but the fact is, no good resolution
has presented itself at this point.
-These aren't very good photos...
-This was the Raging Bomber,
Kimi, reporting.
-Man, I'm gonna get chewed out
by the chief editor again.
-Next up is
-Man, I'm gonna get chewed out
by the chief editor again.
-"The Corner Patisserie" segment.
Wow!
They look delicious!
Today, we're starting with Mr. Morisaki.
We'll have him introduce
the new creation at Chez Morisaki.
This is it.
What is this cake called?
Its name is "Ivresse" and it
contains a secret ingredient...
("lvresse" = "intoxication" in French)
D-Do you think we'll do okay?
It'll be fine! Just leave it to me!
Okay, we have one minute until we go live.
And now, let's call in Ms. Itou as usual.
Ms. Itou!
Here I am! I'm Itou,
the reporter with a sweet tooth.
We are here with a patisserie
called Le reve, which is opening today.
This is the owner and patissier,
Miss Hiromi Kasuga.
And her younger sister, Miss Yuka.
Now, let's get right to
introducing your cakes.
Right. This is our house specialty,
the "Heritage".
Th-This cake is something Sis...
I mean, o-our patissier had
been thinking of for a long time.
-This cake is the same as
the one they just showed.
-Soybean milk skin
-Ouch, this is harsh.
-Has been finely mixed
into the dough and...
That's the same as Mr. Morisaki's creation.
What's going on?! Get me
the people on location!
It looks like a Western-style cake,
but when you taste it,
-it'll have a really nostalgic flavor...
-We're cutting to commercial!
They cut to commercial.
That's gotta suck.
Oh! My deadline, my deadline.
It's the same as Mr. Morisaki's cake?!
Just what does that mean?!
So, like I said, it's partly our fault
for not doing our research,
but I never expected for two
of the same thing to show up!
I don't really care if you guys
copy him, but of all things...
We did not copy him!
Yuka!
But Sis...
This is messed up!
We're the ones who really...
I am sorry about this.
Sis?!
Sis!
Excuse me?
Please forgive me.
Um, out of 2000 yen?
-Please wait a moment.
-Hey, hey, have you heard of Hell Link?
Oh, yeah, if you access
the site at midnight,
it's supposed to avenge
your grievance, right?
Yeah, that's the one!
I stayed at my job too long.
I have to get back fast to help out!
Oh...
This is the shop, right?
The one that stole one of
Chez Morisaki's cake ideas?
I hear she used to be
one of his apprentices.
It'll probably go
out of business soon enough.
Well, I suppose so.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Is something the matter?
Not really.
Any customers?
Just two so far today.
Sis, I still think I should go see him.
This is just too terrible!
You can't do that.
Sis!
It's no use going now.
So don't go.
But at this rate!
"Search Results 4 Matches
1. Hell Link
2. Second Avenue, Hell
Huh?
Maybe it really is just a rumor.
Come to think of it...
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
This is it!
"Shinya Morisaki"
"Send"
Ai.
You have a message.
Okay.
I'm coming.
"Your message was received.
Hell Girl"
Hell... Girl?
Who's there?!
You summoned me, remember?
I am Ai Enma.
Then, you're Hell Girl?
Wait!
She's here.
So you were deceived.
My late father, my sis,
and I dreamed of having our own shop.
It was our family dream!
And that dream was shattered.
Please, avenge us.
Do you hate that man?
Enough to want to kill him?
W-Well...
Wanyuudou.
Yes, Miss.
Take it.
What is that?
If you really want retribution,
untie this red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
However...
What?
...once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
Though, that's only after you die.
What?
N-No!
All that remains is for you to decide.
H-Huh?
The loan is being terminated?!
I tried to negotiate
with the higher ups, but...
If you had at least been
paying off the interest...
I promise I will pay back
the amount that I am late by!
So is there any way you
could wait a little longer?
Unfortunately, that's not
really within my power.
If you could just talk to them somehow...
"JGS Bank"
Yeah.
Okay, I understand. Good work.
Was that satisfactory,
Mr. Morisaki?
More than enough.
I appreciate you taking the
trouble to do this, Branch Manager.
"Space For Rent
Midoriyama Corporation, Inc."
Yuka, let's get going.
Yuka...
I'm sorry, Sis!
If I hadn't gone to that guy,
this wouldn't have happened!
It's not your fault, Yuka.
Why do we have to be put through all this?!
We haven't done anything wrong!
Sis!
I need to tell you something.
What?
Sis?
"A Patisserie Evening
Guest Shinya Morisaki
Sponsor Medaka TV, Inc."
I heard about your shop.
You have my condolences.
You put us out of business!
And you did that just
because Sis rejected you!
You kept pursuing her even though
you knew she wasn't interested,
and you did that just
because she turned you down?!
You're despicable!
No wonder she rejected you!
Say what you will. You're not
getting your shop back now.
Besides, I'm grateful to you.
What?
After all, you gave me the perfect
opportunity to exact my revenge.
But I never expected
things would go so well.
I haven't been in such
a good mood in ages.
You'll just have to work hard
to pay off your debts.
If you want, I could introduce
you to a nice establishment.
After all, you two are
both quite the beauties.
Well, good luck.
Unforgivable...
You are not getting away with this!
Your grievance has been heard.
Ai, I'll leave your under-kimono here.
Thank you, Grandma.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
please enjoy Chez Morisaki's new cake!
It looks delicious!
Just what you'd expect
of Mr. Morisaki's work!
What's with this cake?!
This tastes so bad,
it's not even palatable!
Do you take us for fools?!
Trying to feed us this crap!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Stop! Stop this!
Shinya Morisaki?
Yeah, from the TV show
we saw the other day.
The girl was there, too.
What?! That girl with the same cake?!
Oh...
Wait! It's not me!
I'm not the one who made that cake!
Then it was true that you stole this cake?
And all to get back at a woman
who rejected you?
This is a real scoop.
So how about it, Mr. Morisaki?
He ran away!
Wh-What was that?!
What the hell is going on?!
Hiromi...
Mr. Morisaki, the truth is,
I cared for you as well.
H-Hiromi...
Please, eat me.
What?
Please, eat me!
I don't care where we go, just get going!
I understand.
What the hell is happening?
Am I dreaming or something?
Sir, you like sweet things, right?
What?
H-Help!
Has it gotten through to you a little?
Those two worked so hard
to set up their own shop.
What a horrible thing to do.
Repent for what you did.
Repent?! Why must I repent?!
I was serious!
I loved her!
That's why I gave her special attention!
She's the one who betrayed me!
I've done nothing wrong!
So he says, Miss.
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Wh-Where am I?! Where are we going?!
Answer me!
I'm never letting you have
one of my cakes again.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Where's Mr. Morisaki?!
The thing is, he's nowhere to be found!
There's no way he's not around!
Hurry up and go find him!
Looks like I was too late.
Thank you very much!
I appreciate you coming.
I'm sorry for being late!
Here's your lunch.
Thank you.
Well, I have to go to work now.
Be careful.
I will!
Welcome!
Sis, I haven't given up yet.
We're going to open up
our own shop again, no matter what!
"Yuka Kasuga"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Minami Shibuya.
Are you really sure?
She's your friend, isn't she?
She was my friend.
I thought she was my one
and only true friend,
but after what she did...
I can't forgive her.
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Friends"
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Friends"
Next time, "Friends".
"Hell Girl
Friends"