It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are these ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
"May 13th (Fri)
Shiraha Community Chest
Target: 100,000 yen"
"May 13th (Fri)
Shiraha Community Chest
Target: 100,000 yen"
With the 20,000 yen from Mr. Kato,
the total amount of our donation
has reached 100,000 yen.
The donation money will be placed
in the care of Mayumi Hashimoto,
our class representative.
I will look after it with
the utmost responsibility.
It's not here. It's not here. It's not here!
Why?!
I made sure to put it in my bag...
What'll I do?
What's wrong, Hashimoto?
K-Kuroda...
"Hell Girl"
"From Beyond the Twilight"
"Certificate of Commendation"
It looks pretty impressive.
You think so? It was 100,000 yen.
What are you saying? It was a donation.
Aw...
-They could at least give everyone
in the class a little gift or something.
-Mayumi.
Aren't you glad you were able
to safely deliver the donation?
You do know...
...who you owe it to, right?
Y-Yes...
So? Where's the money? Did you bring it?
Oh, yes.
That should be the last
of what I borrowed, right?
What are you talking about?
That was interest.
Everything you've paid so far is interest.
But that's...
You have a problem with that?
What would've happened
if I hadn't lent you the money?
If you don't like it,
why don't you tell everyone?
Tell them, "I lost the money
I was entrusted with."
I'm kind of feeling thirsty.
Go buy us something to drink.
What? Oh, okay...
Make it quick!
Hey, have you heard of Hell Link?
The one where you submit an entry
on its homepage at midnight
and it'll avenge you
for whatever grievance you've got?
Yeah, that's the one!
The friend of a friend
at cram school actually used it!
I've heard it's chancy.
If you use it,
you supposedly end up dead, too.
I've heard that some kids
have suddenly vanished.
No way!
What's this?
What?
Why isn't it carbonated?
Because...you always
say you hate sodas...
I was in the mood for a soda today.
Can't you even figure that out?
You're so useless.
I'm sorry...
"Nokizuka Private Girls' Middle School"
4x - 2x = 2x.
Which means 2x = 120.
Divide it by 2 and x = 60.
Now, you know what x equals,
so by substituting this
into the original equation,
"After school
The usual spot"
so by substituting this
into the original equation,
"After school
The usual spot"
you can also figure out what y equals.
You can also figure out what y equals.
There's been money going missing
from time to time lately.
The amounts are small, but...
I wonder if we're being robbed.
Lately, they say there are burglars
that repeatedly target the same homes.
It's a little creepy...
And it's just us two girls
when your father comes home late.
Maybe we really should
contact the police...
Mayumi?
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
Hell Link...
This is it...
"Send"
"Aya Kuroda"
If you use it, you supposedly
end up dead, too.
"Aya Kuroda"
No way! Not Hashimoto!
Someone supposedly saw her
at night in the downtown area.
"June 7th (Tues)"
Someone supposedly saw her
at night in the downtown area.
"June 7th (Tues)"
Hey, aren't you feeling thirsty?
Yeah, I am. Let's go
hit the vending machines.
And here I thought she was so serious...
I guess looks can be deceiving.
Quit it. She can hear you.
But I mean...
Hashimoto.
Kato Teach wants to see you
in the faculty room.
I heard a strange rumor going around.
That you've been going
out on the town at night, but...
Of course, I'm sure it's
completely unfounded gossip.
I know better than anyone
that you're not like that.
Welcome home.
What happened to your face?
Mayumi...
Why won't you tell me anything?
You've been acting strange lately.
I hate to think it, but could
the money that's been disappearing...
I trust you!
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Aya Kuroda
Send"
"Send"
"Hell Link"
"Your message was received.
Hell Girl"
"Nokizuka Private Girls' Middle School"
Mayumi?
What happened to your eye?
Oh, hey...
Tonight. 8 o'clock. Don't forget.
Nothing's happened after that.
In the end, Hell Link was just a rumor...
Hit on a guy? You mean, me?
We're looking for a guy
who might take us out to eat.
It's okay if he ends up being middle-aged.
But...
It's your own fault that
you didn't bring any money.
What're you just standing there for?
He looks good. He'll probably go for it.
B-But...
Come on!
Uh, um...
What?
Um...I...Well...
Are you trying to pick me up?
You're cute. How old are you?
Okay, okay. Sure. Are you alone?
Where do you want to go?
What do you feel like eating?
N-No!
Oh, h-hey...
I can't take it anymore...
Why do I have to...
What are you doing, running away?
Why...
If you forget to bring money again,
I'll make sure this photo of you
and him gets around.
Where am I?
You're...
...Hell Girl...
I am Ai Emma.
Ai...
You summoned me.
Avenge me...
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance
will immediately be banished to Hell.
To Hell...
However...
Once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay the price
for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and your soul will wander
for eternity in pain and agony.
All that remains is for you to decide.
Mayumi!
Did you hear me, Mayumi?
That little...
Curses come home to roost.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell...
go to Hell...go to Hell...
to Hell...to Hell...
Hashimoto.
Can I see you for a minute?
"Faculty Room"
Just now, this was sent
to the school by e-mail.
Th-This isn't what it looks like!
This was...
Don't make excuses!
It's clearly you in the photo.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?!
You're only in middle school
and here you are...
I believed in you. This is disappointing.
Mr. Kato!
At any rate, I'll be calling
in your parents tomorrow.
With this, it'll become harder
to get a recommendation next year,
when you're applying to high schools...
Your grievance has been heard.
"From: Mayumi Hashimoto
Sub: Re: At 10 o'clock
> At school
Okay"
What the hell is she doing?!
She's such a slowpoke!
Mayumi?
Mayumi!
Where are you?
Wha...
Wh-What are you all doing?
Hey!
What is this?
What's going on here?
Mayumi, you'd better not be...
Hold it right there!
Hold on! What did you do?!
Damn it! What's going on?
Mayumi!
It's no use hiding!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
There!
Got it!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Oh, I don't like those much.
What? They're delicious!
You think so?
Am I...half asleep or something?
Hey, could you get the ball?
Oh, sure...
You're so useless.
We'd better punish her.
Nooo!
This doesn't make any sense.
Mayumi?!
You...
Mr. Kato...
Something weird is
going on here at school.
Yeah, I know.
This way.
Um, Mr. Kato, where are we going?
Don't worry. Your friends are waiting, too.
What?
A-Aya!
Help!
Aya! Aya!
Th-This is...
So it was you.
You stole it.
Wh-What? This is a pack of lies!
Do you have some kind of proof?!
Was someone watching?!
Sure was.
Well? Have you learned
your lesson a little?
Wh-Who...are you?
You're with Mayumi, aren't you?
How dare you pull this awful stunt?!
Awful stunt indeed.
So you still won't
acknowledge your own guilt.
You shouldn't be so obstinate, little lady.
You've got to be kidding me!
All I did was make fun of her!
It was just a game!
I haven't done anything wrong!
So she says, Miss.
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Wh-Where am I?
H-Hey, where are we?!
Where are you taking me...
I consign this grievance to Hell...
"Nokizuka Private Girls' Middle School"
Mayumi.
Mr. Kato wants to see you.
Says he wants to discuss
the preparations for the sports fest.
Okay, got it.
What?
You've really cheered up lately.
You had eyes like this for a while there.
Sorry for making you worry.
Just keep up that spirit
and do your best to run the sports fest.
I will. Thanks! Later.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell.
"Mayumi Hashimoto"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction
and any similarities between
the names of characters or organizations
in this story and actual names
are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Ryoko Takamura.
You're being pursued?
I'm being watched.
He's always watching me.
It's so hard...
I can't bear it anymore!
Your wish?
Banish him to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
The Possessed Girl"
Next time, "The Possessed Girl".
"Hell Girl
The Possessed Girl"