It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
"Simono"
You're late!
Are you trying to starve me to death?!
"Simono"
I'm sorry! I'll make your
breakfast right away!
This tastes bad. Make it over again.
But I'll be late to school, so...
Don't you care what happens to them?!
Yukky! Pinky!
I could kill them at any time!
"Bound Girl"
I see that girl around a lot lately.
I wonder if she moved
into the neighborhood.
It's nothing like that!
I heard she lives in the
big condo next to the park.
She apparently goes to
Ms. Simono's place for tutoring
and the girl cooks for her
in return. Every day!
What?!
Is Ms. Simono even capable of tutoring?!
She hates children, doesn't she?
But she used to be a
school teacher, you know.
Though, she quit immediately when
she inherited her parents' fortune.
I wonder if her parents are aware of this.
"Curry"
They apparently came
to meet her once, but...
"Curry"
You know! Ms. Simono is nothing,
if not pleasant to outsiders.
They probably fell right for it.
They both work and come home late,
so they probably think their
daughter's being looked after.
Yukky...Pinky...
Yukky...
Yukky!
Yukky!!
-Your teacher from school came by earlier.
-Open your eyes, Yukky!
-Yukky!
-I ignored him, of course.
You talked, didn't you?
I haven't said anything!
It's true! I really haven't
told anyone anything!
I told you what would happen
if you talked, didn't I?!
I really haven't said anythi...
I told you I could kill them
at any time, didn't I?!
I'm sorry, Yukky...
For not being able to make
you a proper grave...
Is my tea ready yet?
Coming!
One!
Two!
Three!
-I-I'll be right there!
-Four!
Oh, my glasses! My glasses!
But you wear contact lenses!
Oh, there it is.
-These comedians are funny!
-Right on you.
Why the heck?!
Why you!
And now, for an SM!
That's CM!
Um...
Huh? What?!
Oh, uh, um, it's already time...
What?
Oh, is it that late already?
Y-Yes.
You make sure you study
when you get home!
I'm supposed to be your tutor,
after all!
-Pinky...
-I'm the one who'll come under
suspicion if your grades get worse!
Do you understand?!
Oh, y-yes!
Pinky...
I'm home.
Yukky...
If only I hadn't let you go that time...
I'm sorry, Yukky!
I'm sorry!
I didn't think she'd really kill him...
At this rate, someday, Pinky will also...
Someone! I don't care who!
Send her to Hell...
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
I found it...
"Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send"
Yukky...
"Meiko Simono
Send"
I'll get revenge for you.
"Meiko Simono
Send"
"Send"
Miki, are you awake?
Mom!
Where's your dad?
He said he's going to be gone overnight.
Oh, that's right.
I still haven't found Yukky and Pinky.
You haven't?
Why don't you give up already?
I'm going to look
for them a little more.
Hajime, breakfast is ready,
so make sure you eat it, okay?!
Sure!
See you later!
I am Ai Enma.
Hell Girl?
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
-untie that red thread.
-Tsugumi!
-Untie that red thread.
-Hey, Tsugumi!
Hey!
You saw something again,
didn't you, Tsugumi?!
She was giving someone the straw doll!
Then it's happening again somewhere!
Tsugumi, did you see anything
that hinted at where it was?
Any distinctive buildings or store names?
Someone's about to be sent to Hell again!
So...
Do we absolutely have to stop it?
What?
Well?
Of course!
"Shibata Town"
What a truly easy to identify location.
So it's this house.
"Simono"
Simono...
Is that the mother?
"Yamada Shop"
Ms. Simono?
She lives alone there.
What?
She doesn't have any kids.
She inherited a sizable
fortune from her parents.
She doesn't even work
and stays cooped up at home.
Who knows what she does?
I think she used to date various men
when she was younger,
but I never heard that she got married.
I wonder if I got the wrong house.
Maybe he's talking about that girl.
The one that's supposed to be regularly
visiting Ms. Simono's lately.
Oh, her!
She used to walk her dogs a lot.
She comes from the condo by the park.
So that's the girl.
What's wrong, Pinky?
You seem down.
Is it because Yukky's gone?
You better not be thinking
about running away with it!
Whose fault do you think
this leg injury is?!
I'll never permit you to run away!
I can kill it at any time.
So can I!
I can do it at any time, too!
It's been 3 days since then.
No activity whatsoever.
I wonder what that girl's thinking.
Wanyuudou must be bored out of his mind.
That's not true.
She talks to me on a daily basis.
I could also do it...at any time!
Here. These are the results of
the investigation you requested.
That was quick. You're a great help.
Let's see...Miki Kamikawa.
First year in middle school.
No one around her has died
under suspicious circumstances
or gone missing recently, huh?
Has she given up on revenge? Or...
There were dogs, though.
What?
Dogs?
Her dogs went missing.
Ever since she moved here,
walking her dogs in the morning
and in the evening was her daily routine.
She doesn't stand out in school
and she doesn't have
any close friends, either.
Her parents both work
and are often not at home.
Her two dogs were the only
ones she could open up to.
But two weeks ago,
the dogs went missing during their walk,
and that was the last time they were seen.
It was right around then that she
became a regular visitor here.
The two are related...
That's probably how I should look at this...
"Simono"
I told you, didn't I?!
That I'd kill your dog if
you snitched to anyone!
What?
A suspicious man has
been hanging around lately.
You snitched, didn't you?!
I don't know about that!
I don't know anyone like that!
It's your fault for not keeping
your end of the promise!
I'm going to kill it now!
Wait! Wait!
By untying the thread, you will
enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance will
immediately be banished to Hell.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
Curses come home to roost.
When you die, your soul will go to Hell.
What are these guys?!
What?
You've become a mom!
P-Pinky...
Wh-Why?!
I told you, didn't I?!
That I'd kill this dog!
Pinky! Pinky!
Hurry up and make breakfast!
-I'm hungry!
-Ow, that hurts!
-Please stop! Please stop!
-You better not be thinking
of starving me to death
and stealing my fortune!
Why?
Why did it end up this way?!
That day, I just...
I thought a change of scenery
would be good for once
and I took a different path
for our walk! That was all!
Yukky! Pinky!
Yukky!
Wait!
Yukky! Pinky!
Ow! Owowowowow!
Let go, you! Let go! It hurts!
Yukky! Yukky!
Are these your dogs?!
Not only did they make
a mess of my garden,
but they even bit my leg!
Unforgivable!
I'm going to hold you
responsible for this!
You said dogs that have
bitten people are put down,
so I did everything you told me to,
but before I knew it, Yukky and Pinky
were being treated like hostages!
When I asked my teacher,
he said it wasn't true!
They do get put down sometimes!
Like dogs that have become sick!
If this was how it was going to be,
I should've talked to my mom first!
Mom says she hates dogs, too,
but if I'd talked to her,
she probably would've helped...
I won't let you talk to anyone!
What?!
If you do that, these guys
will be dying one by one next!
What?!
You hear me?! Do you understand?!
You know, you say that,
but it's all that thing.
So it's all that thing!
He's got an axe, after all.
No, no, he ain't got one.
Why didn't I do it then?
If I had, Pinky would be...
We're not doing that!
Oh, well.
"Shibata Town"
Here! A change of clothes!
Oh, thanks.
Hajime, you stink!
You haven't had a bath in days, have you?!
What? D-Do I smell that bad?
Well, I couldn't let that
girl out of my sight, so...
But considering how she looked,
maybe we're out of the woods.
-Did she come?
-What?
Hell Girl.
No.
Is what Hell Girl's doing bad?
Any action that results
in the taking of a life
is unforgivable, no matter
what reasons there might be.
But there are people in this world
who do even worse things
and think nothing of it, right?
That's true, but...
Who's going to punish
those people for us?
That's a different story.
Is it really?
Tsugumi.
"Simono"
Who is it?
Oh, I'm from the police box
in front of the station.
Police?!
I knew it! You saw it that time,
didn't you?!
What?! What are you talking about?!
I don't know anything about this!
I'll kill them!
Don't!
-Kamikawa! Hey, Kamikawa!
-Hey, what's happening?! Open up!
What's going on?!
We heard one of my students
screaming inside!
This way!
Requesting backup!
The location is Shibata Town, 8-cho...
I have to hurry, or those puppies will...
Who are you people?!
You guys are after my fortune, too,
aren't you?!
-What?!
-Like hell I'm letting you have it!
That woman killed my dogs,
Yukky and Pinky!
I won't let anyone have it!
Stop this! You are hindering an officer!
Let go!
Like hell I'll hand it over!
Not even to my own child!
Hey!
Damn it! Let go! Let me go!
It seems she believed that the girl
had seen her child's skeleton.
That was why...
She didn't want to hand over her fortune,
even to her own child, huh?
What a terrible story.
That's a doll you got
from Hell Girl, right?
It's not something you need anymore.
Right?
What about them?!
What? Them?
Nooo!
They'd just been born!
I hadn't even given them names yet!
If only I'd sent her to Hell sooner!
-I could've done it at any time!
-Stop!
Don't do it!
Your grievance has been heard.
I finally got my hands on that
fortune by killing my parents.
Like hell I'm going to
share it with some kid!
That's why you killed them?
That's right!
I'll kill any bastard that
gets in my way! Even dogs!
You might be an
experienced killer, but...
-I bet this is your
first time being killed.
-What?
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
"Hell"
I don't have time to be going to Hell!
If I don't get back in a hurry,
my fortune will be...
Do you have any idea how you look now?
Wh-What do you mean?!
Huh?
-Nooo!
-I consign this grievance to Hell...
If only I'd untied the thread earlier,
Pinky wouldn't have had to die, either!
And the puppies wouldn't
have had to die, either!
I could have...
I could have done it at any time.
"Miki Kamikawa"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Inori Ujiie.
You are not happy?
I have no kin, and yet,
she welcomed me into her family.
I was so happy.
I wanted to repay her kindness, but...
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Bride Doll"
Next time, "Bride Doll".
"Hell Girl
Bride Doll"