It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
You look splendid, Inori.
Just like a doll.
Why?
Why?!
"Bride Doll"
Why...
"Master Japanese Doll Maker
Kyougetsu Ujiie"
...didn't I notice it then?
That strange glint in Mother's eyes...
Mother...
What are you doing at this hour?
I thought to feed the koi...
Leave such matters to the servants.
You need not undertake
any household chores.
Come.
I apologize.
It is getting rather chilly.
Take your bath first,
so you do not catch a cold.
Thank you very much.
M-Mother...
You have gained weight.
What? No!
No, you have gained weight.
I will not allow it.
You must never gain weight!
Come here!
Mother!
I'm sorry! Forgive me, Mother!
It seems the wind is picking up.
What an unpleasant wind.
Lukewarm and cold...
People cry on nights like this.
"Kyougetsu Ujiie"
Yukio...
What's the matter, Inori?
I...
Are you feeling better now?
Forgive me...
I'm so scared...
I'm sorry for that.
It's not that Mother hates you.
I think she wants the Ujiie
bride to stay beautiful.
That's just how she is.
There's that important
exhibition coming up,
so she must be on edge.
Ugly!
How ugly!
I suppose mother is a great
doll maker of Japan.
You've married into
a difficult family.
Oh, no. But I have you.
Now, I have another early start
tomorrow, so let's turn in.
I've been rather tired lately.
Um, if you would just tell me when
you want a massage, I could do it.
I learned how to at the Kyougetsu Home,
so I'm very good at it.
Forget about the orphanage.
You don't have to do
such things anymore.
You're our precious bride now.
But I would like to be
allowed to do something, too.
Otherwise, even though I've
married into the family,
it's like I'm a guest here.
Then, let's have you
make breakfast tomorrow.
All right.
Yukio, breakfast is ready...
Inori, I believe
I told you this before.
That you need not undertake
any household chores.
I apologize.
Come, Inori, join us before
the food gets cold.
Oh, no.
A separate meal has been
prepared for Inori.
She's gained weight, just a little.
Come, have a seat.
Do you not hear me telling you
to have a seat?
F-Forgive me...
Straighten your spine properly.
That is how you should be.
The servants will take care
of your every need.
You will sit quietly.
Beautiful and graceful.
Like a doll.
Are you all right, Inori?
Yukio, help me! Please help me!
Just what is the matter, Inori?
I'm scared! I am scared out of my mind!
Of that look in Mother's eyes!
The mistress has ordered that
you are to cool your head.
That you are to empty your mind.
Empty my mind...
What do you think, Ms. Ujiie?
Shall we try dressing it?
No, not yet.
The eyes are not dead yet.
This cannot be called a dead doll.
A shroud could not possibly suit it!
What I desire is a doll filled
with sorrow and despair.
Ai, you got a message,
just like you expected.
Please forgive me. Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I want to go back.
I want to see everybody!
Bye-bye!
Tsugumi!
Are you...Again?!
I can see! There's a girl crying.
I think she's about high school age.
She's pretty, like a doll.
Who's there?!
Hell Girl...
Doll...
No!
You look splendid, Inori.
Just like a doll.
You will sit quietly.
Like a doll.
No!
What are you afraid of?
I figured it out,
that she'd been watching
me for a long time.
Ever since I was a child...
You are quite adorable.
Come to my home when you've grown up.
Everyone was happy for me.
That an orphan like me was able to
marry into such a wonderful house.
So you hate this house, this woman.
I am not a doll.
I want to be a person!
I see.
If you really want retribution,
untie this red thread.
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay
the price for it as well.
I know.
The Sister always said so, too.
Hey, are we still going
to stick around?
Someone is about to bring
misfortune on herself.
We can't just ignore that.
But it's what she
wants herself, right?
It's an adult's duty
to provide guidance even then.
I'm not an adult,
so I don't understand it.
Hajime, that's her!
I'm sure of it.
What'll I do? I've come
outside without permission...
But you came outside,
because you wanted to run away...
Am I wrong?
Come on, let's hurry.
Won't it be bad to stay here?
"Kyougetsu Home"
Are you okay?
Have you stopped crying?
What?
Why...
How did you know that
I had been crying?
I don't know.
I don't know, but I've got this
ability to know things like that.
It looks like I sense it when someone
gets in contact with Hell Girl.
Do you want to send someone to Hell,
no matter what?
But in the end, if you curse someone,
you'll go to Hell, too.
I do not mind that I will
be bound for Hell.
But I can't let everyone at
the Kyougetsu Home suffer.
Kyougetsu Home...
You mean this place?
My home.
I grew up here.
When I was here, I couldn't
wait to get out into the world,
but now, I miss this place.
And the one who was supporting
this home of ours...
...was Ms. Kyougetsu Ujiie.
Or rather, it was Mother.
Everyone is very grateful.
They wish me the best in my marriage.
But you're having to endure something.
What happened?
"Emergency Exit"
Nothing. I am permitted nothing.
I'm told to just behave like a doll.
What do you mean, like a doll?
At any rate, this doesn't seem like
a problem for you to solve alone.
I'd suggest that you have an honest
talk with the people at the Home.
I can't do that.
Why not?!
If you talk to them properly,
I'm sure they'll understand!
That's why I can't.
Everyone's sure to tell me...
If there is ever anything
you absolutely cannot bear,
come back at any time.
Do you understand?
The people here are all truly
kind and they care about me.
That's why I can't tell them!
If I don't suffer in silence,
this place will be shut down!
And that's why you called Hell Girl...
Emergency exits...
"Emergency Exit"
...are for anyone to use
in an emergency, right?
"Emergency Exit"
I think so...
To me, Hell Girl is my emergency exit!
Isn't there anything we could do?
You followed us,
because you wanted help, right?
That girl won't untie the thread.
She cares about the people
here above all else.
But is it okay for things
to be this way?
Sacrificing herself...
I feel sorry for her!
She'll probably keep suffering
from now on, too.
Ms. Ujiie, Inori is...
I see. You may leave for today.
Yes, Ma'am.
Where did you go out to?
I apologize. I went for a little walk.
Is that so? For a walk?
Forgive me.
It cannot be helped.
You have such mobile legs.
Unlike a doll.
What?!
If only those legs wouldn't move!
Like a doll.
You are supposed to be my doll!
Behave as I wish you to behave!
A doll has no need of a soul!
Those eyes...How wonderful they are.
Young and beautiful.
You are the very picture of a dead doll.
Man, oh, man. Women are scary.
You just figured that out now?
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, Sister.
I can't pray anymore.
I can't do any more penitence, either.
Will you untie it?
It's her fault!
She treats me like a doll
instead of a person!
I can feel pain and anger, too!
I won't be her doll!
Inori, who are you talking to?
Yelling like that...
Yukio...
I'm so worried about you...
I do resent that woman.
-I will live my life with Yukio.
-Inori, are you all right?! Inori?!
Your grievance has been heard.
You sure have grown old.
There's no stopping the oncoming years,
Ms. Ujiie.
Wh-What?!
You envy dolls, don't you?
Dolls that remain eternally
beautiful and never age.
Impossible!
Aw, man, you're going
to come to a bad end.
Becoming obsessed with dolls
is up to you,
but people aren't dolls.
Compared to dolls,
humans are nothing!
Nothing but superficial,
ugly, depraved beings!
Dolls are my all!
And bringing them to life
or killing them...
...is up to me.
I am truly a god!
Good grief.
Time for the Miss's turn.
O pitiful shadow lost
in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing
harm to others...
A damned soul,
wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
You're beautiful.
Just like a doll.
I would like to make
a doll like you.
I imagine a shroud would
suit it quiet well.
I will let you make them for
eternity in the world beyond.
But your model will
be yourself dying.
Oh, how beautiful you are.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Yukio...
From now on,
I will devote myself to you to make
up for Mother's absence as well.
Body and soul...
Soul?
I don't need something like that.
All you have to do is watch me quietly.
Like a doll.
So in the end, she's a pitiful doll.
A living Hell.
"Inori Ujiie"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Jill Due Lonfer.
The man who found
his way back from Hell.
You want to meet me?
Yeah, I do.
I can't imagine that you're
more powerful than I am,
but well, I have a bunch of
questions I want to ask you, too.
I don't.
Next time, "Hell Girl vs. Hell Boy".
"Hell Girl
Hell Girl vs. Hell Boy"
Next time, "Hell Girl vs. Hell Boy".
"Hell Girl
Hell Girl vs. Hell Boy"