It is said that life's
encounters are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
Save me.
"Glass Scenery"
I hate fog.
It makes me afraid of what's
ahead of us on the road.
If I could see ahead,
I could be strong even if
something bad was coming.
Kids shouldn't think
such complicated things.
I'm not a kid!
You're a kid, any way you look at it.
I'm your guardian, Hajime.
Oh, is that so?
Be careful, okay? Don't speed.
Yes, Ma'am, Miss Guardian.
A music box?
Where's it coming from?
It can't be from outside...
Is the radio on?
Watch out!
You okay?
Do not go.
What?
Turn back.
Do not go.
Is it Ai Enma?!
A sanatorium?
"Reception"
Excuse me?! Hello?!
Oh, excuse me!
Hajime!
There's...no one here.
Wanna go back?
I'm okay.
You're sure?
Yeah, that music box was
playing in the scene I saw.
Tell me stuff like that sooner.
Sorry.
Anything else?
She said, "Save me."
What?
A girl's voice said, "Save me."
It looks like there really
isn't anybody here.
Yeah.
Let's make one round and then go home.
Okay.
Well?
Is this the same as the scene you saw?
It's a little different.
Different?
The view outside is the same,
but I feel like it's different somehow.
I see.
Something must have set it off.
All right, let's go home.
Okay.
Uh...Who are you?
Hello.
I see. So your name is Nina?
Yes.
I'm Tsugumi.
Tsugumi...
Yup, and this is my father.
Father...
That's nice.
Because Nina doesn't have a father.
This place is quiet.
Yes.
Where are the other patients?
Nina's the only one here right now.
I didn't know.
What about the doctors and nurses?
I haven't seen any around yet.
They're here.
So they were around.
I'm going to go say hello.
Oh...
Say, why did you come here?
What?
You had some business here, right?
Oh, um...
My father's a friend
of the director here.
We happened to be in the area,
so we decided to drop by for a visit.
That's strange...
I was sure she came this way...
Excuse me...
Nina, your eyes are a pretty color.
Thank you.
Your hair is beautiful, too.
You can touch it.
Go ahead.
O-Okay.
Wow, it's silky smooth!
So warm...
Her hand is so cold...
Were you able to say hello?
Yeah, I guess.
The director might be out today.
He goes out a lot on the weekends.
What?
The director?
Ow!
What?!
I'll tell you later.
Say, you're staying
the night tonight, right?
What?
There are a lot of open rooms,
so it'll be fine.
Nina will make arrangements for you.
Oh, but...
Sorry, but we have
a hotel reservation in town.
You won't make it.
You won't be able to
go back in this fog.
Is that the girl?
The one that accessed Hell Link...
Probably.
I did a cursory check earlier,
but there weren't any
computers here in the facility.
Furthermore, the sanatorium itself is strange.
Against whom does that girl...
No, against what does
that girl have a grievance?
Not to mention, that girl...
Stop!
I'm sorry.
We'll stop thinking about this.
I want to go home, Hajime.
Yeah, let's go home.
Just as soon as this fog lets up.
With things getting to this point,
it can't be a coincidence.
Yeah.
That journalist named
Shibata or something
is definitely acting on info
he's obtained ahead of time.
That source would have to be...
The Miss...
What for?
Who knows?
It might be that the Miss is
doing it unconsciously, too.
I don't understand the Miss lately.
To be honest with you.
You have a point.
Take this case for instance.
Yeah.
I never thought she'd act
on a request like that.
An access from a soul...
Hell Girl...
You took so long.
I was getting tired of waiting.
I cannot accept your request.
What?
What do you mean, you can't?
You're supposed to avenge me, right?
That's your job, isn't it?
I cannot avenge your grievance.
Oh, wait!
Wait, Hell Girl!
Nina!
Liar.
Ni...na?
Hey, you just called out to Hell Girl?
But it doesn't matter.
I don't care anymore.
Because, now, Nina has...
Aren't you kind of hungry?
Shall we go have dinner?
Wh-What?
Let's go.
Come on, let's eat.
What's wrong?
Hurry up!
Then, shall I make some tea?
Wow, thank you!
Your father is so nice.
Wh-What? Uh, yeah...
He's not anything like Nina's father.
Because Nina's father
left Nina and disappeared.
I didn't know...
What about your mother?
What? My mother?
I wonder if I had one.
I don't know about a mother.
Nina, could I ask you something?
What?
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to,
but you accessed Hell Link, didn't you?
Hell Link? Yeah, I did.
You have a grievance against someone?
Yeah.
I see. Against whom?
My father.
He left me all by myself
and I was lonely.
I hated him for a long time,
because I blamed him for it.
But I'm okay now.
What?
I'm not lonely anymore.
I have you, Tsugumi,
and I have a new father, too.
What?
You'll stay with me forever, won't you?
You won't leave Nina all alone, right?
What are you saying, Nina?
Nina, we just, well...
dropped by to visit the director.
There's no director here.
What?
There's no one else here, except Nina.
From now on, let's live happily
together here, just the three of us.
We're a family now, after all.
Nina...
Okay, Tsugumi?
Hajime!
Tsugumi, what's wrong?
Stay away from me!
Nina, you...
You're the same.
You're the same as Father.
Tsugumi!
I won't forgive you.
We're running straight out to the car!
Hajime...
I know we're under orders
from the Miss, but...
I never expected to be helping him.
He is someone who is unrelated
to this particular job.
What's going on here?
Tsugumi...
Tsugumi!
Hajime!
Hajime?
It's your fault, Tsugumi.
Now, come with Nina.
You're...
Hi, there.
Tsugumi!
Tsugumi! Hey!
Thank goodness...
Start!
Start, you piece of junk!
Damn it!
Nooo!
Stop!
Stop this.
Hell...Girl...
Tsugumi...
Hell...Girl?
You didn't avenge Nina!
I have no use for you anymore!
Don't get in my way!
Stop this. You must not involve them.
It's their fault!
They're trying to leave
Nina all alone again!
Just like Nina's father!
Leaving Nina by herself again!
You are not Nina.
Wh-What are you saying?
I am Nina!
Remember.
Your mistress died.
Nina...
Tsugumi! Tsugumi!
Hey!
What does this mean?
I don't know.
This is the place...
What?
The scene I saw...
A doll...
I'm right here!
I'll be waiting!
I'll be good and I'll be waiting, so...
So...
Come get me, Father!
I don't want to be alone!
It's so lonely!
Save me...
She took on Nina's feelings...
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Miki Kamikawa.
You cannot escape?
That woman says I have to come every day.
That woman lives to hate people.
At this rate, those little ones will be...
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Bound Girl"
Next time, "Bound Girl".
"Hell Girl
Bound Girl"