It is said that life's
encounters are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
A butterfly, hanging upside down,
that will head towards the light sometime
The reflection in the mirror
as we cut our hair
Footsteps echoing
in the hallway during class
The sound of rain follows us ceaselessly
Purely what we feel is blinding
and can take the shape of a sweet flower
Or the shape of a poisonous fruit
Rain again today
I want to link that day to now, sky-to-sky
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a trace
of each of our emotions somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard one emotion?
In this craziness, uncertainty
Will we be able to leave a
trace of each of our selves somewhere?
In this craziness, you gave me life
To what bounds can we
safeguard each of our selves?
What do you think, Tsugumi?
Is this the view you saw?
Looks like it.
I see.
Sightseeing? Probably not, right?
Oh, are you from the island?
The guidebook said that island is a
place noted in connection with Heike.
Well, that's true,
but it's not much of a place.
All we get are visitors coming to fish.
Maybe a diver once in a while.
It's pretty quiet, sadly.
Well, that's the sort of island it is.
I wonder what they've come for.
Strangers with empty hands...
I see.
"Island Woman"
"Minato Inn"
Mina!
Where are you going, Mina?
"Welcome to Sarutsuki Island"
Yesterday, the day before yesterday...
Who could she be waiting for?
I wonder if it's a sweetheart.
Who knows?
It's that man again!
What's he doing way out here?
Yuji!
Yuji...
Mina! You came to pick me up?
But I didn't tell you I was getting
out of the hospital today...
I need to talk to you.
Hajime, that's her!
All right. Come on.
So her name's Mina, huh?
Aww, I wanted to see the romance!
It's no fair, the Miss gets all the fun!
Wouldn't know.
And it's such a small island, too.
Well, we'll just move on.
I've never seen her.
I'm busy right now.
I don't know.
You'll have to ask someone else.
Hajime, are you really
a professional reporter?
Well, it can be like this at the start.
He's pretty tenacious.
Oh, if it's Mina Minato...
I'm sorry, I have to
take care of something.
Have you hit a slump lately?
Where did you learn a word like that?
"Diner"
Wow, a special feature on the island!
Then you'll be mentioning our
place in the magazine, too?
Yes, well...
Then have a taste of all
of our specialty items!
Our specialty monkey parfait,
special monkey ice cream,
and monkey dumplings with ice cream!
I don't want them.
So, Mina is the daughter at the inn
at the edge of the harbor?
Don't you go talking about
unnecessary things now.
Yeah...
Speaking of which, she isn't
the daughter to be precise.
I think she's the niece of Fujie,
the proprietress.
What about her real mother?
As I recall, her name's
Satsuki and she passed away.
When?
This isn't good. What're we going to do?
Leave it to me.
I think that was about 15 years ago.
She threw herself into the ocean.
Mind you, her body never washed up, but...
Why did she kill herself?
She left the island at one point,
and Mina was born between her
and a man she met over there, but...
Fujie...
In the end, the man left her
and she came back to the island.
I wish I'd never left the island.
It was just like you said, Fujie.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Sister.
We'll be together again from now on.
But I guess it must have been
a shock to her, after all.
In the end, about two years later,
she left Mina and...
And then?
P-Please leave!
What was up with that?
I'm telling you, you're in a slump.
You keep saying it's a slump,
but come on!
It's a tiny island,
so the rumor will spread
and I doubt anyone else
will talk to him now.
Serves him right.
When you're in a slump,
you should quietly...
No way! I'm not giving up yet!
"Minato Inn"
Sister, I don't want Mina to suffer
the heartache that you did.
I'm doing various things with that
in mind, but she won't understand.
What do you think I should do, Sister?
Sister...
It was the same with me.
I had a hard time winning
the trust of the islanders.
Impressive.
So, Mr. Principal, are things not
going well between Mina and her aunt?
Things used to be good before.
Anyone would have thought they
were a real mother and daughter.
But then...
During middle school and high school,
Minato used to commute by boat,
but she was forced to
drop out of high school.
Why?
There's no need for an academic degree
to take over the inn...
Was that what she wanted?
No!
I felt very bad for her, so I went
to talk her aunt out of it,
but I wasn't able to manage that.
Minato was indebted to her
for her upbringing,
so she reluctantly went along with it.
Poor girl.
I learned about this later, but...
Yes?
It seems a boy from her high school
had called by phone to ask her out.
The aunt apparently
found that unforgivable.
That's terrible.
Incidentally, do you know
a young man named Yuji?
Oh, you must mean Numata.
He works for the prefecture's
Department of Fisheries.
He's studying the island's
fishing resources and such.
Is he seeing Mina?
Yes.
Does Fujie know about that?
Well, I suppose it's what people
call a woman's intuition...
Why can't I see Yuji?!
Because he's not from this island?!
It's too late if you wait
until you get hurt!
That's just an idea that
you've got stuck in your head!
No. Sister also...
Your mother also thinks the same!
Everyone that leaves this
island is met with misfortune!
I don't want you to suffer that!
That's why!
That's why!!
Mina, do you realize
what you're saying?
This injury from 3 days ago was...
It was probably a poacher.
You're wrong.
My aunt did it.
Just what basis do you
have for saying that?
I saw her!
That day, I heard groaning
from the bathing area,
so I went to find out
what was going on.
At the time, it didn't
make any sense to me.
But I remembered that you said
you'd been slashed with a knife...
Mina, what are you doing?!
It was you, wasn't it?!
You attacked Yuji!
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
It is for your own good.
That's ridiculous...
So...
What is this?
"Audiovisual Room"
"Conserve Electricity"
"Fujie Minato"
"Send"
Hajime, this is the place!
This is where that girl
was standing last night!
Get away from there, Tsugumi!
What?
Hell Link?
This is the only choice we have left.
If you had only come earlier,
we could have prepared some
delicious seafood for you.
Um, so where is Mina tonight?
She went out during the day
and she has yet to return...
But I'm amazed you tracked her down
over a grade school composition.
I've been a judge for a long time,
but Mina's work was exceptional!
Oh, my. Really?
Yes!
Mina still has the certificate
from that hanging in her room.
I'm sure she'll be happy to see you.
Well, then, please make
yourselves at home.
I guess checking her out ahead of
time was the right thing to do.
Right?
But from the looks of it, she didn't
seem like such a bad person.
Maybe she's done some extreme
things because she cares about Mina,
but it might be possible to work
it out with some persuasion.
I want to meet with her
as soon as possible...
Where'd she go?
Tsugumi!
Tsugumi! Tsugumi!
What's wrong, Tsugumi?!
What will you do?
What?
Will you untie it?
Will you not untie it?
Don't tell me it's...Hell Girl...
But something like this is...
It's bad luck!
Don't!
But...
If we don't do anything, there's no
knowing what she might do to us!
Next time, it could be
worse than just an injury!
Still...
Whether you throw it off the cliff
or you untie the thread...
...is up to you.
The rocky cliffs?!
What could be going on?
Let's follow him.
All right.
Let's untie it.
Okay, I'm untying it.
Okay.
Hey, you two!
Y-Yes?!
Wh-What is it?
You're Mina and Yuji, right?
W-We haven't done anything yet!
Where's the straw doll?!
What did you do with
the black straw doll?!
What are you talking about?
You haven't untied
the thread yet, right?!
Please, think this over one more time!
You can still turn back!
If you make a hasty
decision to untie it,
there'll be no taking it back!
What?
Oh, goodness!
It looks like we're too late.
I don't think we can
get involved this time.
If you untie that thread,
you'll end up weighed down with a
burden that's far too heavy for you!
Are you fine with that?
You two want to find happiness, right?
Yeah.
I'm telling you right now.
No matter what there might be,
you'll never find happiness by
bringing grief to someone else!
So don't be rash!
Uh, um...
I was married once before
and I'm saying this,
so you know I'm right!
Believe me!
Thank you very much.
You two understand, then?
For being so concerned about
a couple of strangers like us.
Right?
That's true.
Truly, thank you very much.
Nah, I'm just happy you understand.
But what'll we do, Yuji?
My aunt isn't the sort of
person you can reason with...
Oh, I know! Why don't
we just go and elope?!
Elope?!
Elope, huh?
Hey, now, that's not good!
Yeah! I hadn't thought of that!
Yeah!
Now, calm down!
Do you two even have any prospect
of making a living after you elope?!
But your aunt...
I'm sure she'll understand someday!
When she does, all three of us can...
That's true.
Come on, listen to what I'm saying!
Thank you very much!
H-Hey!
Good grief. I guess that
wasn't really like me.
"Don't be rash!
You only have one precious life!"
Owowow...
Damn it!
I saw this show last week.
Hajime sure is taking a long time.
Oh?
It's Mina.
Mina...
Mina doesn't listen
to me at all anymore...
What should I do, Sister?
I'm sorry, Fujie...
...for foisting off Mina on you.
Mother?!
Mother, you're alive?
If only I weren't in this
wretched condition...
Don't. We agreed we wouldn't talk
about that, remember, Sister?
You're right.
I'll try talking to Mina myself.
Mina...
Wh-What is that?
What are you saying?
It's your mother.
-As you can see,
I've been unable to move...
-What?
-As you can see,
I've been unable to move...
Wh-Where is her voice coming from?
It was Sister's...
It was your mother's fault.
Fujie, stop this! Please don't do this!
Why are you doing this terrible thing?!
That's what I want to know!
After the terrible experience
you went through,
why are you trying to
leave the island again?!
I hate this island!
Don't say that, Sister.
This is the island where
we were born and raised.
But I'm still leaving! Don't stop me!
Why won't you understand, Sister?!
I won't let you go!
Be with me forever, Sister!
Nooo!
Y-You're terrible...
Mina, you mustn't blame your aunt.
She's doing everything with
our best interests at heart.
I'm so glad to hear that, Sister.
From now on, the three of us
will be happy together.
S-Stop this, Auntie!
Please, don't do this!
Be good now.
Mina...
The three of us are going to get along...
...and live on this island, Mina.
Mina!
Please stop this!
The hell are you doing?!
Please calm down!
Shuddup!
Yuji!
Anyone who gets in the way...
...of our happiness...
Nooo!
Your grievance has been heard.
Why...
I love you, Sister.
We'll be together forever. Forever...
How sad.
If you close yourself off,
you leave yourself with no escape...
I consign this grievance to Hell...
There was no helping it.
You think so?
We could've stopped it,
if that hadn't happened.
You know...
If you only look up a little,
there's this vast sky overhead.
Yeah...
"Mina Minato"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Always a dead end
There is no escape
I place my sorrow upon a bird in the sky
And I'll let it fly
This place is ephemeral
An eternity that binds me
Coming or going
All that passes by are dreams
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Yumi.
Why? Because you are not loved?
I was bad at being loved.
I know that,
but I don't want to be
treated like this anymore!
Your wish?
Banish that person to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
A Night Among Traveling Entertainers"
Next time, "A Night Among
Traveling Entertainers".