It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
Has everyone connected
the dots in their textbook?
A space surrounded by three
straight lines like this is a triangle.
And a space surrounded
by four straight lines is...
Shibata!
Oh, y-yes, ma'am.
I'm home.
How did it go, Ai?
The same as always.
They all have that sad look in their eyes.
Ai, you're troubled again, aren't you?
"Beyond the Dead End"
"Cherry Blossoms Setting Sun
Cherry Blossom Tree
Uniform Gloomy Looking
Like an inn Girl
Is this really from Hell Girl?
Old Man Fat Middle-Aged Man
Suicide in Park Hanging"
Is this really from Hell Girl?
Probably.
I think it's about the person
who's being sent to Hell next.
Why does she tell you these things?
I don't know.
Suicide...
Where in the park did
this guy hang himself?
Monkey bars.
Monkey bars?
It's where you, like...
Oh! Monkey bars.
Right, monkey bars. Monkey bars, huh?
Let's see... Oh, here it is.
"Weekly Buncho
Issue 36 320 Yen"
"Dark Rumors About
Mayor Kusunoki and the Mob"
"Matsunobe Town Employee
Mysteriously Commits Suicide".
Oh! This man!
"Mysterious Suicide
Haruki Kirino (44)"
I'm sure of it!
"Mayor Kusunoki Under Suspicion
Mayor Kusunoki Avoiding"
And this guy's the mayor of that town, huh?
"Mayor Kusunoki Under Suspicion
Mayor Kusunoki Avoiding"
Oh, I saw this man, too.
He totally looks like someone
who's doing something bad.
What about the family of Kirino,
the suicide victim?
He's got one daughter
about to start high school.
His wife passed away over 10 years ago
and it seems his daughter
takes care of all the domestic work.
"Uniform
Gloomy Looking Girl"
and it seems his daughter
takes care of all the domestic work.
The mayor is popular and
has some local recognition,
but he has his share of bad rumors
going around about him and his son,
who serves as his assistant.
"Himawari Home"
I'm still... I'm still willing
to forgive you right now.
Turn yourself in!
If you tell the truth, I'll let you live!
Give it up already!
We've been tolerating this because
of the way your father died!
Be more aware of your position!
Move it!
Father...
What do you mean?!
That's not what we agreed on!
Hold on a minute!
What are you doing?!
Give me those!
Father, those photos...
Forget you saw them. Got it?
I'm going out.
Father, where are you going at this hour?!
"Matsunobe Town Police Department"
Please identify the body.
It's my father!
Results of the court ordered autopsy
suggest he committed suicide.
What about the envelope?!
What?
It was about this big.
He should've had it with him!
-Was there one?
-No, there was nothing.
"Funeral Service for the Late Haruki Kirino
Reception"
I am very sorry for your loss.
Please leave. There is no reason
for you to attend the ceremony.
Why can I not attend the ceremony?
Why don't you think about what
you've done and ask yourself that?!
This is impossibly rude!
Yoshiyuki!
There seems to be some
kind of misunderstanding.
Don't play dumb!
I am not playing dumb.
I saw them! I saw the photos!
I will have the police investigate
if it is a misunderstanding or not.
Please leave for today!
-You...
-This is just rude!
The mayor is saddened by the
death of one of his staff members!
He's taken precious time out of his
busy schedule serving the public
to make it to this memorial service!
And telling him to leave,
no matter what your reason, is just...
Leave!
We're going back.
"Matsunobe Town Police Department"
I'm sure of what I saw!
It's easy for you to say what you saw...
We can't investigate without proof.
Those people got rid of it!
Enough is enough.
Of all the people, there is no way
Mayor Kusunoki is guilty of this.
If you want money, don't you think
there are better ways to go about it?
"Leave town!
Is it money that you're after?!
Don't blame suicide on other people!"
"Apologize to the mayor!
Like father like daughter!"
Coming!
Pardon me, Miss Kirino.
Who is it?
Oh, hello. I'm a magazine reporter.
I've spoken to members of the press
at length about this already.
No one took me seriously.
Some even wrote the
complete opposite of what I said.
It's tough when it's a scandal
on the level of the mayor.
But someone's dead!
Everyone reported that fact.
He was killed!
There's no proof, which makes
your assertion unconvincing.
You must know that yourself.
"Himawari Home"
I talked to various local people
before coming to see you.
Almost no one spoke badly of Kusunoki.
They said he's compassionate and
working hard on the issue of welfare.
That he's even donated a
large sum to this nursing home.
But I saw it.
Photos of Kusunoki and his son, Yoshiyuki,
meeting with people with ties to the mob.
My father died the night he
went out late with those photos,
and those photos and the
negatives have disappeared.
He wasn't the sort
of person to commit suicide!
It's just strange, no matter
how I think about it!
That is the entire story.
No matter what others may say,
I can only believe in what
I saw and what I've seen.
You okay?
I'm fine. I'm used to this by now.
More importantly, please write about it.
That there are suspicions
concerning Kusunoki!
If I can find corroboration.
Please!
There are rules in this world.
Rules that protect murderers?!
There's no need to follow rules like that!
You've met Hell Girl?
You've met her?
How?
Why don't you forget about revenge?
What is this about?
I just want you to not do it.
This is none of your business!
Won't you give me some time?
I'll look into it.
I don't know if what
I find will satisfy you,
but I'll try to come to my own conclusions.
Make your decision after you've seen them!
What is it you're after?!
Don't you think revenge is meaningless?
I have a point blank question for you.
Isn't the cause of Mr. Kirino's death,
in fact, not suicide?
I am not sure why you
would ask such a thing...
That is what Mr. Kirino's daughter claims.
You cannot believe such
unsubstantiated nonsense.
But the idea that it is nonsense
is also unsubstantiated.
What are you driving at?
I only want to know the truth.
Regardless of what that truth might be,
I want to find an answer
that I can be satisfied with.
I believe we have
nothing more to discuss, then.
Let me see the mayor.
I want to talk to him.
Please leave.
You're here, aren't you?!
You can hear me, can't you, Mr. Kusunoki?!
You have some nerve talking like that!
You're just a freelance reporter!
That's why I can make it
as a freelance reporter!
Yoshiyuki.
I lost my parents when I was young
and I was raised by my grandmother.
But I lost her before I was able
to repay much of her kindness.
So when I see the elderly,
I just feel terribly rueful.
Though, I'm elderly myself now.
You're late today!
Sorry about that. I've just
been so busy with work.
Ms. Tanimoto, is your hip all right now?
How could it be all right?
I'm as good as finished!
The way you sound, I'd say you'll
be fine for a long time to come!
When the last director passed away,
the deeds to the land
and all the buildings here
went to some people with mob ties.
They were planning to
build a luxury condo here.
But if that happened, the elderly here
would have nowhere to go.
So I asked that they cancel those plans
and decided to make some
special concessions to the mob.
That was all there was to it.
Kirino found out about it
and tried to shake us down.
We couldn't possibly give in
to such a despicable threat.
So naturally, we refused.
He was probably in debt or something.
When he realized he couldn't
get money out of this,
he took his own life.
I do feel responsible.
Dad!
He said he wanted the money to send
his daughter to a university in Tokyo.
A man like that would
never commit suicide!
Do you realize what it is
that you are saying?
I did not have a hand in this.
But there is no doubt that
someone took action on my behalf.
It is up to you whether
you write about this or not.
But if I fall, this place
will be shut down.
What will happen if
this place is shut down?
What will become of
the elderly living here?
That's all I got today.
In the end, I didn't find out the truth
about your father's death.
I'll go see Kusunoki again tomorrow.
But...
Some things in this world can't be
split neatly into good and evil.
I think this case might be one of those.
So, forget about getting revenge.
You're sure to regret it.
I don't know what you're thinking,
even going so far as to hire
that has-been newshound,
but can we just end this with that?
Why are you doing this?
The mayor is losing heart.
I want you to stop
troubling him any further.
It's unbelievable how selfish
your thought process is!
Selfish?! You're the selfish one here!
What do you think will happen
if you bring my old man down?!
It'll bring trouble to a lot of people!
But you're the only one to
grieve the death of your old man!
You're trying to destroy this town
based solely on your emotions!
Get a clue already!
It's hardly unreasonable that
the townspeople are angry with you.
Hey, wait!
I won't write it.
I will keep this incident to myself.
In exchange, I have a request.
What might that be?
Please bow your head
to Mr. Kirino's daughter.
Please get down on your knees
and apologize to her.
You'll be going to college soon, right?
Then you'll get a job, get married...
It'll happen in no time at all.
I'd better work hard.
Don't say things like that.
I won't be able to do right by you
without the proper finances.
Now, I better get to work.
I promised her that I would
draw my own conclusions.
All I could come up with
was to ask this of you.
What are you doing?!
I only have you, now.
You're all I've got.
You mustn't listen to what this man says!
He's bound to come asking
for money later anyway!
I can't tell if you're in the wrong
or if Kirino's in the wrong.
But there's one thing I can say.
The feelings that
Kirino's daughter has are pure!
Unlike your corrupted son,
her feelings are pure!
What did you say?!
As a father, I envy Mr. Kirino
for having a daughter like her.
More than I envy you.
What kind of nonsense is this?!
"Shinkin Bank"
"Account Number 80765471
Ms. Saki Kirino
Matsunobe Shinkin Bank"
"Account Number 80765471
Ms. Saki Kirino
Matsunobe Shinkin Bank"
Your father had created an account
in your name, Ms. Saki Kirino.
He had kept these in a safe-deposit box,
but the contract has expired,
which is why I contacted you.
Now, if you would be willing,
we would be happy to have you
keep your account with us.
If that's all you could save after
working hard at an honest job,
I can understand why you might
want to resort to blackmail.
And to die like that... I don't
know if it's pitiable or wretched.
Yes?
Hello, it's Shibata.
I'm going to bring Kusunoki
over to you now.
I'll have him apologize
for the incident.
Wait for me. Okay?
-It's all right.
-What?
It doesn't matter anymore.
What I should do is clear to me now.
Then, you're going to give up
on trying to get revenge?
Nothing can ever take
the place of my father.
No matter what he may have done,
he was a very kind father to me.
And those people...
Hold on a minute!
What happens to this town
is no concern of mine.
This is all I can do for my father.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Father...
Your grievance has been heard.
Hello? Hello?!
What's wrong?!
My old man...
My old man disappeared...
Where am I?
You are in a boat ferrying you to Hell.
Hell...
Yes.
I see. It must be that girl.
She's the one who...
Would it not be possible for me
to say a word of apology to her?
That would not be possible.
I see. So I can't do that.
I thought I had lived so I wouldn't
have any regrets, no matter when I died,
but it seems I've died
with just one regret.
I consign this grievance to Hell...
"Matsunobe Town Mayor's
Mysterious Disappearance!!"
Ryouzo Kusunoki,
"Matsunobe Town Mayor's
Mysterious Disappearance!!"
The mayor of Matsunobe Town,
"Matsunobe Town Mayor's
Mysterious Disappearance!!"
Has been missing for a week now
"Matsunobe Town Mayor's
Mysterious Disappearance!!"
And his whereabouts are still unknown.
That turned out well.
Why?
Because, that man did
some bad things, right?
So it was good.
Don't say it was good.
You're weird.
"Himawari Home has been closed
as of October 13.
Himawari Home"
"Saki Kirino"
Your grievance shall be avenged.
ltsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
"This is a work of fiction and any
similarities between the names of
characters or organizations in this story
and actual names are entirely coincidental."
Your name?
Mina Minato.
You want to leave your birthplace?
I don't want to live out
my life on this island.
Why does she get in my way?!
Why does she have to
go to such lengths to...
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Island Woman"
Your grievance has been heard.
"Hell Girl
Island Woman"
Next time, "Island Woman".
"Hell Girl
Island Woman"