It is said that life's encounters
are governed by fate.
Tangled up in the threads of fate...
...are the ill-fated blossoms,
pitiful and frail.
Lost in anger, sorrow, and tears...
Beyond the veil of midnight,
the retribution that you are
helpless to reap shall be yours.
Itsuka hikari ni mukau sakasama no chou
Kimi to kami o kiru kagami no naka
Jugyou-chuu no rouka hibiku ashioto
Taezu ame no oto ga tsuite-kuru yo
Kanjiru mama no katachi wa mabushii
amai hana ni naru
Doku no mi ni mo naru
Kyou mo ame
Ano hi to ima o
sora to sora de tsunagitai no
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no omoi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
ln this craziness, you gave me life
Hitotsu no omoi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
In this craziness, uncertainty
Hitori hitori no katachi o bokura wa
dokoka ni nokoseru darou ka
In this craziness, you gave me life
Sorezore no katachi o bokura wa
doko made mamoreru darou ka
''Gold Animal Clinic''
Candy!
I'm sorry, but...
No!
I'm begging you!
Doctor, please save Candy!
Well, if I could, I certainly...
I just know you can save her, Doctor!
Candy's the only family I've got!
Doctor!
Candy, don't die!
The...The doctor's going
to make you better real soon!
I'm begging you! Please save Candy!
Candy, please, don't die!
Don't leave me alone!
Nooo!
''Silent Cries''
Okay, let's see what's inside.
Junko's been wanting a doggy!
Thank you, Mother! Father!
Poor thing.
''Kanno Family Grave''
To lose her parents
when she's only 10 years old...
Junko, why don't we get going?
Candy, let's be strong for each other.
Aww!
Oh, Candy!
Wait for me, Candy!
Candy!
Candy, what am I supposed to do now?
Junko, your dinner's getting cold.
I'll leave it right here.
''Gold Animal Clinic''
Dr. Honjo, it's terrible!
The Suzukis' Koro was in an auto accident
and seems to have broken her leg.
I just got a call that they would
be bringing her over right away.
Suzuki?
Oh, I'll leave it to you
to take care of that dog.
I have to go see
Assemblyman Koizumi's dog now.
But Doctor...
Bones grow back together by themselves.
More importantly, don't forget
to give the poodle its 5 o'clock shot.
It'll be bad if we let
that actress's dog die.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Junko.
Ms. Sekimoto.
Um, thank you for everything
you did for Candy.
I was so upset at the time
and I didn't thank you properly, so...
Where's the doctor?
Oh, he stepped out just now
to go see a patient.
I see.
Don't worry, I'll pass along
your thanks to the doctor.
So anyway, are you feeling
a little better now?
Yes. I still can't get used to being alone,
but moping about it forever
won't help anything, either.
Besides, I think Candy was happy.
After all, she was in the care of a
good doctor like Dr. Honjo until the end.
Well, please give the doctor my regards.
Candy...
I just gave you some painkiller,
so you should feel better soon.
...please, don't die!
Don't leave me alone!
Ms. Sekimoto!
I'm sorry for calling you out here.
It's all right. It's not as
if I have anything to do at home.
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
What do you mean?!
So, the truth is, right then,
a phone call came in
from Assemblyman Kawai and...
Golf, is it?
I don't mind, but with someone
of my caliber accompanying you,
wouldn't it be more of a hindrance for you?
Doctor...
Yes?
Oh, no, not at all.
-Doctor!
-That was just a fluke.
Never mind that. Your approach shot
on the 5th hole was brilliant.
No, mine was a fluke. I just got lucky.
Yes. Okay.
-Doctor!
-The last Tuesday of the month?
I happen to have that free.
''Mon 2pm- (house calls)
Tues Charity Animal Consultation
Weds 9-11am (vaccinations)''
I happen to have that free.
''Mon 2pm- (house calls)
Tues Charity Animal Consultation
Weds 9-11am (vaccinations)''
No, no, it's completely fine.
''Mon 2pm- (house calls)
Weds 9-11am (vaccinations)''
No, no, it's completely fine.
Doctor!
It can't be...
Then, did Candy receive
no treatment at all?!
He treated her after he got off the phone,
but it was already too late by then.
If only I'd forced him to
get off the phone right then,
this wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
I know an apology doesn't
make it any more forgivable,
but seeing you, I just
couldn't keep it quiet anymore.
That's the kind of place that clinic is.
It can't be true...
She was in so much pain!
For a phone call like that?!
It just can't be true!
Forgive me...Junko.
Candy...
If only I hadn't taken you
to a doctor like that...
Did you see the paranormal special
on TV yesterday?
It was super scary, wasn't it?!
That reminds me,
have you heard of Hell Link?
Yeah, I've heard of that!
That site you have to go to at midnight
that'll avenge your grievance
or something, right?
Yup, that's right.
I heard someone really used it
at Fuurin High School.
What?! No way!
Hell Link...Hell Link...
''Search Results
The site you are looking for was not found.
Keyword Search''
Why can't I find it?!
''Search Results
The site you are looking for was not found.
Keyword: Hell Link Search''
''Your grievance shall be avenged.
Send''
This is it...
Ai, you have a message.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
''Search Results
The site you are looking for was not found.
Keyword: Hell Link Search''
Why did it go down?!
Please, let me get to it!
Who are you?!
I am Ai Emma.
You summoned me, remember?
Then, you're Hell Girl?
Take it.
If you really want retribution,
untie that red thread.
You will enter into a covenant with me.
The object of your vengeance
will immediately be banished to Hell.
So I just have to untie this?
However,
once you have your retribution,
you will have to pay the price
for it as well.
Price?
Curses come home to roost.
If you enter into the covenant,
your soul will also go to Hell.
You will never see Heaven,
and you will wander for eternity
in pain and agony.
Well, that's only after you die, though.
Stop!
All that remains is for you to decide.
I just have to pull this...
I just have to untie this thread
and I can have my revenge.
I can't do it! I just can't do it!
Forgive me, Candy!
You suffered so much
as you were dying, but I...
But I...
Next up is coverage of the
massive misappropriation of funds.
Our reporters at Asamaru
got up close and personal
with the man embroiled in this incident.
There's proof of what you did.
Why don't you acknowledge your guilt?
''Massive Misappropriation of Funds!!
Closing In On The Truth!''
Why don't you acknowledge your guilt?
''Massive Misappropriation of Funds!!
Closing In On The Truth!''
You think they'll let you off the hook
after what you've done?!
Please answer us!
The company president has...
Proof?
Yes, as long as we have proof,
some TV station should be willing
to do a piece on that doctor...
-That won't work.
-What?
The clientele of that clinic includes lots
of politicians and celebrities.
Even if we gave the media this story,
it'd get hushed up right away.
But at this rate, Candy will have...
No, not just Candy!
This concerns other dogs, too!
I'm never going to forgive that doctor.
Everyone brings their pets to him
because they trust him!
Please, Ms. Sekimoto!
I understand.
''Gold Animal Clinic''
It's dark, so watch your step.
What happened to this one?
She broke her leg in an auto accident.
If she'd had surgery right away,
it wouldn't have gotten this bad, but...
More importantly, let's hurry.
We need to get out of here by 10,
before Honjo gets back.
The patient charts are useless.
They've all been forged, so it
looks like proper care was rendered.
Instead, help me over here.
He charges for expensive medicine
that he never even used,
so the inventory might not match up.
Seven boxes of Anmytal.
Um...Yes, seven boxes.
Why? They all match up.
That's strange. It shouldn't...
What are you doing?!
You're...
I've heard about it all from Ms. Sekimoto!
Candy was suffering, while you were
on the phone talking about golf!
What are you talking about?
I don't know what Sekimoto told you,
but I did everything in my power for Candy.
I won't be fooled!
You killed Candy!
I'll tell the media about
everything you're doing!
I see.
And that's why you were looking for proof.
So? Did you find your proof?
If you don't even have proof,
I'd rather you didn't make
groundless accusations.
You could ask the parties
directly involved, if you like.
What?
How about it?
Am I such a terrible doctor?
I can't really understand
what you're saying.
Talk to me properly so I can understand!
That's awful...That's too awful...
Come now, what's wrong?
If there's something
you want to say, say it.
Please stop!
I've heard enough!
They may just be a means
of making money for you,
but to their owners,
they are their precious pets!
Take Candy! She was
the only family Junko had!
Family?
You call that filthy dog family?
You probably found it
on the street somewhere, right?
Besides, it's because dogs
like that come here
that the hospital becomes dirty and smelly.
What do you think this place is?
It was also for the good of the hospital
that a dog like that hurried up and died!
-Ow!
-Go on! Get out of here!
Please stop, Doctor!
I'll let you off the hook just this once,
but if you come around making
groundless accusations again,
I'll sue you for slander!
Don't think you'll ever find
another job in this industry!
It was better that she hurried up and died?
I won't forgive him. I won't forgive him!
Your grievance has been heard.
Ai, I'll leave your under-kimono here.
Thank you, Grandma.
Calling me up in the middle of the night
for a measly dog...
Just you watch, I'll charge you
a fortune for it.
Damn it...
What was someone doing there...
I have a broken bone...
He sure got himself
into a spectacular crash.
Let's move him out.
What're you...
What's this place?
The hospital?
What's going on?
Are you a doctor?
Hey, I've got a broken leg!
Do something about it for me!
Did you see yesterday's game?
Wasn't that an amazing homerun?
Who cares about baseball?!
-No, that was because
the pitcher slipped up.
-Hurry up and look at my leg!
A pitcher slip up? Come on!
It was a miscommunication, I'm sure.
I mean, it was a straight pitch
smack dab in the middle.
-Hey, you people,
you've got a patient here!
-You were watching, too?
-Quit chitchatting and start treating me!
-I say the credit should go to the batter.
-He had his elbow
tucked in like this and bam!
-Come on, I told you
-He had his elbow
tucked in like this and bam!
-No one cares about baseball!
-He had his elbow
tucked in like this and bam!
-Hurry up and do something about my leg!
-That was a slip up.
That's right.
Even I could've hit that homerun.
You people, are you listening to me?!
Please, I'm begging you,
do something about this leg!
We will now begin the operation.
What?
What the heck's wrong with him?
The thing is, we can't understand
a word of what the patient's saying.
It's my leg!
-I have a broken bone in my leg!
-I guess we'll start
by cutting in around here.
What?
Where do you people
think you're cutting into?!
That's not the right place! It's my leg!
It's my leg that's injured!
Stop it!
Do you feel like repenting
for what you did now?
To you, animals may be a means
for making money,
but for pet-lovers,
they're a part of the family.
Family?! Don't be ridiculous!
They're no different than I am!
They dress up their animals in weird outfits
and take them to parties!
They use their animals
as a means of showing off!
Why am I the only one
that has to be treated like this?!
I haven't done anything wrong!
So he says, Miss.
O pitiful shadow lost in the darkness...
Demeaning and bringing harm to others...
A damned soul, wallowing in sin...
Care to give death a try?
Wh-Where am I?
What is this place?
Where are we going?
Answer me!
Doctor, it hurts.
-What?!
-It hurts!
-Doctor, it hurts.
-It hurts, Doctor!
-Stop this! Stay away! Stay away from me!
-Doctor!
-Doctor, it hurts!
I consign this grievance to Hell...
Ms. Sekimoto!
Junko, you came to see me off!
I heard you were leaving the city
and going back home...
I'm sorry. Because of me...
It's okay. I should be the one apologizing.
Besides, I think I can find work
with animals away from the city, too.
The 10:09 Nozomi destined
for Fukuoka will be departing.
-The 10:09 Nozomi destined
-Well, I have to go.
I'll let you know when I find a job.
Bye.
Father, Mother, Candy...
I'm sad that l can't be with you,
but I'm going to try to
hang in there a little longer.
So, please watch over me from up there.
''Junko Kanno''
Your grievance shall be avenged.
Itsudatte yukidomari de
Keshite nigerarenai
Sora no tori e kanashimi nose
Tobasu no
Koko wa karinui
Watashi o shibaru eien
Yuki mo kaeri mo
Sugite yuku wa yume
''This is a work of fiction
and any similarities between the names
of characters or organizations
in this story and actual names
are entirely coincidental.''
Your name?
Misato Urano.
You find her unforgivable?
She thinks nothing of human life.
To her, this world is
about prestige and glory.
She said life is ultimately just a game.
Your wish?
Banish her to Hell for me!
Your grievance has been heard.
''Hell Girl
The Woman in the Tall Tower''
Next time, ''The Woman in the Tall Tower''.
''Hell Girl
The Woman in the Tall Tower''